She O
tok O
say O
di O
center O
don O
agree O
and O
stand O
gidigba O
for O
INEC B-ORG
for O
di O
review O
and O
realignment O
of O
some O
of O
im O
department O
make O
im O
dey O
very O
very O
capable O
to O
fit O
produce O
result O
and O
efficient O
for O
di O
management O
of O
im O
human O
resources O
and O
assets O
. O

dem O
don O
add O
6 O
NIPP O
plant O
dem O
, O
22 O
new O
substation O
for O
di O
power O
grid O
wey O
dey O
6 B-DATE
years I-DATE
report O
. O

Generation O
companies O
( O
GenCos O
) O
and O
22 O
power O
substation O
wey O
dem O
build O
and O
dey O
operate O
between O
2015 B-DATE
and O
now O
, O
don O
make O
improvement O
dey O
for O
di O
national O
eletcricity O
grid O
to O
di O
5 O
, O
800 O
megourtt O
wey O
be O
di O
highest O
peak O
energy O
wey O
dem O
record O
for O
March B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
. O

Dis O
dey O
according O
to O
di O
latest O
NIPP O
report O
on O
top O
power O
project O
execution O
since O
2015 B-DATE
, O
wey O
Daily B-ORG
trust I-ORG
obtained O
from O
di O
Niger B-ORG
Delta I-ORG
power I-ORG
holding I-ORG
company I-ORG
( O
NDPHC B-ORG
) O
. O

Di O
NIPP O
na O
di O
intervention O
vehicle O
warehouse O
wey O
di O
federal O
, O
state O
and O
local O
goment O
own O
for O
NDPHC B-ORG
. O

For O
2015 B-DATE
, O
di O
power O
grid O
don O
dey O
between O
4 O
, O
500 O
megourtts O
( O
MW O
) O
wey O
don O
bikom O
useful O
by O
di O
commissioning O
and O
utilisation O
of O
Geregu B-LOC
, O
Omotosho B-LOC
, O
Olorunshogo B-LOC
, O
Alaoji B-LOC
, O
calabar B-LOC
, O
Ihovbor B-LOC
NIPP O
GesCos O

Dat O
one O
add O
nearly O
1 O
, O
000MW O

Howeva O
, O
di O
grid O
continue O
to O
dey O
rise O
wit O
all O
- O
time O
peak O
electricity O
wey O
don O
reach O
5 O
, O
801 O
. O
60MW O
as O
of O
March B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
, O
according O
to O
di O
statistics O
wey O
we O
get O
from O
independent O
system O
operation O
( O
ISO O
) O
arm O
of O
di O
Transmission B-ORG
company I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nigeria I-ORG
. O

( O
TCN B-ORG
) O

NDPHC B-ORG
don O
start O
di O
NIPP O
intervention O
wit O
di O
first O
phase O
wey O
dey O
power O
generation O
. O

E O
don O
begin O
dey O
build O
10 O
power O
GenCos O
wey O
dem O
dey O
call O
' O
The O
Big O
Ten' O
around O
gas O
- O
producing O
state O
dem O
wey O
include O
Ondo B-LOC
, O
Ogun B-LOC
, O
and O
Kogi B-LOC
states I-LOC
. O

Howeva O
, O
work O
still O
dey O
go O
on O
dem O
till O
2015 B-DATE

Dem O
lunch O
the O
second O
phase O
for O
2015 B-DATE
to O
include O
intervention O
project O
, O
wey O
go O
focus O
on O
transmission O
, O
distribution O
, O
and O
energy O
wey O
dem O
don O
renew O
towards O
meeting O
NDPHC B-ORG
mandate O
for O
lighting O
di O
nation O
. O

currently O
, O
dem O
bin O
dey O
six O
power O
GenCos O
wey O
dey O
produce O
about O
3 O
, O
400MW O
electricity O
for O
di O
national O
grid O
while O
di O
four O
oda O
GenCos O
dey O
ongoing O
. O

Even O
among O
di O
four O
, O
some O
of O
im O
turbines O
don O
dey O
commission O
and O
dey O
operational O
since O
2015 B-DATE
. O

Explanation O
of O
di O
report O
show O
say O
di O
NIPP O
intervention O
for O
di O
transmission O
section O
wey O
dey O
di O
power O
sector O
value O
di O
chain O
, O
NDPHC B-ORG
don O
complete O
22 O
substations O
wey O
bin O
dey O
compromise O
10 O
units O
of O
330 O
/ O
132 O
kilovolts O
( O
KV O
) O
level O
and O
12 O
units O
of O
132 O
/ O
33KV O
substations O
. O

E O
don O
also O
complete O
2 O
, O
194 O
kilometres O
wey O
dey O
330KV O
power O
transmission O
line O
and O
887km O
wey O
dey O
132KV O
transmission O
lines O
. O

Dis O
infracstructure O
since O
2015 B-DATE
, O
don O
add O
5 O
, O
590MVA O
energy O
supply O
capacity O
wey O
dey O
330KV O
level O
and O
3 O
, O
793MVA O
wey O
dey O
132KV O
level O
. O

To O
promote O
energy O
wey O
dey O
clean O
and O
improve O
, O
di O
NIPP O
for O
di O
second O
phase O
don O
turn O
to O
major O
driver O
of O
di O
federal O
goment O
energy O
mix O
by O
2030 B-DATE
wey O
dem O
dey O
call O
vision O
30 O
- O
30 O
- O
30 O
wich O
seek O
energy O
wey O
go O
improve O
to O
at O
least O
30 O
percent O
of O
di O
energy O
grid O
by O
2030 B-DATE
. O

While O
e O
don O
install O
20 O
, O
000 O
solar O
home O
systems O
for O
some O
northen O
states O
, O
di O
NIPP O
don O
dey O
deliver O
a O
huge O
part O
of O
the O
ongoing O
five O
million O
SHS O
to O
domot O
nationwide O
under O
di O
Economic O
Sustainability O
plan O
( O
ESP O
) O
. O

Dia O
bin O
dey O
intervention O
for O
di O
gas O
sector O
wey O
go O
solve O
major O
challenge O
of O
di O
power O
plant O
wich O
be O
di O
availability O
of O
gas O
- O
to O
- O
power O
. O

According O
to O
di O
oga O
patapata O
for O
NDPHC B-ORG
, O
Mr O
Chiedu B-PER
Ugbo I-PER
, O
for O
interview O
wey O
im O
get O
with O
Daily B-ORG
Trust I-ORG
, O
di O
company O
dey O
achieve O
dis O
tru O
di O
fuel O
and O
gas O
or O
public O
private O
partnership O
model O
. O

E O
don O
create O
a O
department O
for O
dis O
to O
spearhead O
im O
gas O
pipeline O
and O
feed O
stock O
wey O
dey O
connect O
all O
di O
10 O
NIPP O
GenCon O
. O

wen O
dem O
tok O
power O
distribution O
, O
di O
report O
tok O
say O
di O
NIPP O
intervention O
bin O
don O
see O
di O
completion O
of O
ovr O
360 O
NIPP O
injection O
substations O
wit O
a O
combined O
capacity O
wey O
reach O
3 O
, O
540 O
MW O
. O

To O
complement O
dis O
substations O
, O
NDPHC B-ORG
don O
build O
about O
2 O
, O
600KM O
of O
11KV O
power O
distribution O
lines O
and O
4600KM O
of O
33KM O
distribution O
lines O
wey O
dey O
supply O
electricity O
directly O
to O
transformer O

Dia O
bin O
dey O
296 O
appointed O
project O
wey O
dem O
don O
distribute O
, O
wich O
injection O
substations O
dey O
inside O
, O
1924 B-DATE
of O
33kv O
lines O
, O
4600km O
of O
11kv O
lines O
wit O
dem O
oda O
infastruction O

NDPHC B-ORG
sef O
don O
increase O
im O
distribution O
capacity O
wit O
di O
installation O
of O
25 O
, O
900 O
completely O
self O
- O
protected O
( O
CSP O
) O
transformer O
wey O
dey O
across O
obodo O
, O
nah O
Mr O
Ugbo B-PER
add O
dis O
one O
. O

On O
top O
all O
dis O
achivement O
wey O
don O
help O
to O
improve O
di O
operation O
of O
national O
grid O
, O
di O
report O
highlight O
threat O
to O
di O
infastructure O
especially O
for O
di O
one O
wey O
dey O
di O
power O
distribution O
level O
. O

Some O
of O
di O
wahala O
wey O
NDPHC B-ORG
dey O
see O
for O
dis O
distribution O
be O
say O
dem O
dey O
tif O
dia O
equipment O
and O
infrastructure O
, O
vandalism O
, O
and O
lack O
of O
cooperation O
from O
Distribution O
companies O
( O
DisCos O

Di O
oda O
nah O
community O
wahala O
wey O
dey O
regard O
land O
and O
Right O
of O
way O
( O
ROIs O
) O
, O
motor O
accident O
wey O
don O
damage O
some O
power O
infrastructure O
and O
rising O
insecurity O
wey O
dey O
facility O
areas O
, O
e O
start O

for O
a O
comment O
wey O
go O
empty O
di O
property O
of O
di O
NIPP B-ORG
intervention O
to O
Nigerian O
wey O
dey O
comsume O
electricity O
, O
di O
President O
for O
di O
Nigeria B-ORG
consumer I-ORG
Protection I-ORG
Network I-ORG
( O
NCPN B-ORG
) O
, O
Barrister O
Kunle B-PER
Kola I-PER
Olubiyo I-PER
, O
im O
tok O
say O
di O
reason O
for O
di O
power O
sector O
privatatization O
exercise O
wey O
dem O
conclude O
for O
November B-DATE
2013 I-DATE
hapen O
to O
promote O
competitive O
economy O
and O
inclusive O
growth O
by O

Im O
howeva O
tok O
say O
despite O
dis O
, O
di O
sector O
neva O
reach O
dat O
kin O
viability O
, O
so O
di O
goment O
need O
to O
deepen O
di O
interventions O
tru O
NIPP B-ORG
. O

On O
top O
all O
di O
tremendous O
milestone O
wey O
NIPP B-ORG
/ O
NDPHC B-ORG
don O
achieve O
, O
dia O
bin O
major O
area O
of O
impediment O
wey O
dey O
full O
realizeation O
of O
di O
lofty O
idea O
wey O
di O
management O
of O
NDPHC B-ORG
championed O
. O

Mr O
Olubiyo B-PER
tok O
say O
di O
wahala O
dem O
dey O
face O
include O
delay O
in O
taking O
over O
projects O
by O
di O
DisCos O
wich O
dem O
suppose O
capture O
for O
dia O
capital O
Expenditure O
( O
CAPEX O
) O

Im O
continue O
im O
tok O
say O
nah O
di O
Nigerian B-ORG
Electricity I-ORG
Regulatory I-ORG
Commission I-ORG
( O
NERC B-ORG
) O
bin O
di O
inderance O
for O
di O
delay O
in O
di O
implementaion O
of O
di O
regulations O
of O
eligeable O
consumer O

wit O
di O
kin O
huge O
power O
assets O
wey O
NIPP B-ORG
don O
provide O
, O
di O
Manufacturers B-ORG
Association I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nigeria I-ORG
( O
MAN B-ORG
) O
and O
oda O
dedicated O
power O
users O
fit O
decide O
to O
connect O
to O
di O
NIPP B-ORG
plants O
and O
facilities O
directly O
and O
dey O
enjoy O
uninterrupted O
power O
supply O
, O
but O
dis O
bin O
dey O
delay O
. O

Anoda O
wahala O
wey O
NDPHC B-ORG
dey O
get O
nah O
funding O
, O
wich O
im O
think O
say O
di O
equity O
stakeholders O
suppose O
raise O
for O
more O
power O
sector O
projects O
. O

Di O
leadearship O
of O
di O
power O
sector O
go O
need O
to O
address O
di O
low O
tariff O
wey O
dey O
NIPP B-ORG
plants O
and O
di O
low O
load O
( O
Energy O
) O
dispatch O
wey O
dey O
available O
units O
from O
TCN B-ORG

Consumer O
dem O
dey O
look O
for O
more O
electricity O
, O
why O
energy O
from O
NIPP B-ORG
GenCos O
con O
dey O
restricted O
? O

Nah O
so O
Olubiyo B-PER
ask O
. O

unlike O
oda O
places O
, O
Ramadan B-DATE
season I-DATE
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
don O
unfortunately O
turn O
into O
a O
season O
wey O
dey O
get O
unnecessary O
controversy O

Di O
controvercy O
don O
start O
from O
di O
arrival O
of O
di O
Ramadan O
crescent O
wey O
dey O
usher O
in O
di O
new B-DATE
month I-DATE
and O
di O
moon O
go O
waka O
commot O
to O
show O
e O
end O
. O

di O
Ramadan O
peroid O
dey O
equally O
witness O
controversy O
ova O
ideological O
, O
jurisprudential O
or O
political O
stances O
wey O
some O
Ulama O
expressed O
for O
di O
course O
of O
dia O
Quranic O
trfseer O
sessions O

ova O
many O
many O
years O
, O
dia O
bin O
don O
dey O
unnecessary O
controversy O
ova O
say O
wich O
charitable O
work O
better O
pass O
between O
make O
dem O
dey O
suponsor O
broadcast O
Quranic O
tafseer O
abi O
make O
dem O
dey O
do O
charitable O
mass O
feeding O
of O
di O
needy O
for O
Ramadan O
. O

As O
e O
dey O
go O
for O
oda O
Muslim O
societies O
, O
Ramadan O
dey O
always O
inspire O
a O
phenomenal O
risefor O
individual O
and O
for O
societal O
spirituality O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
wer O
plenty O
wealthy O
pipo O
dey O
sponsorlive O
or O
recorded O
broadcast O
for O
Quranic O
tafseer O
by O
different O
Ulama O

Many O
oda O
pipo O
dey O
spend O
more O
on O
top O
charitable O
feeding O
of O
di O
poor O
. O

Howeva O
, O
while O
almost O
, O
if O
no O
be O
all O
, O
who O
dey O
sponsor O
di O
broadcast O
tafseerb O
dey O
spend O
for O
di O
charitable O
feeding O
too O
, O
no O
be O
all O
wey O
dey O
spend O
for O
charitable O
feeding O
dey O
suponsor O
di O
broadcast O
of O
tafseer O
. O

Ramadan B-DATE
period I-DATE
for O
northern B-LOC
Nigeria I-LOC
, O
television O
and O
radio O
stations O
dey O
make O
profit O
wit O
di O
sale O
of O
airtime O
for O
tafseer O
and O
oda O
religious O
lectures O
wey O
individual O
, O
firms O
and O
groups O
sponsor O

from O
di O
kin O
number O
of O
sponsor O
broadcast O
of O
tafseer O
an O
dem O
oda O
religious O
lecture O
wey O
dey O
for O
like O
10 O
radio O
stations O
for O
Kano B-LOC
, O
for O
example O
, O
one O
fit O
begin O
dey O
wonda O
weda O
dem O
dey O
do O
oda O
programme O
for O
Ramadam B-DATE
period I-DATE
. O

E O
good O
say O
dem O
dey O
sponsor O
tafseer O
broadcast O
, O
especially O
for O
Ramadan O
, O
di O
amount O
wey O
dem O
dey O
spend O
for O
dis O
regard O
be O
like O
say O
im O
dey O
imbalance O
if O
we O
consider O
di O
kin O
hunger O
wey O
dey O
wire O
di O
needy O

afta O
all O
, O
if O
dem O
get O
chance O
to O
choose O
, O
dem O
go O
certainly O
choose O
food O
hangout O
ova O
dat O
kin O
sponsored O
broadcast O
, O
as O
e O
don O
be O
say O
public O
tafseer O
session O
dey O
evriwia O
for O
Ramadan O
wey O
persin O
fit O
choose O
wich O
to O
attend O
. O

Besides O
, O
di O
kin O
underlying O
dynamics O
and O
politics O
wey O
dey O
for O
sponsoring O
Ramadan O
tafseer O
broadcast O
, O
persin O
no O
fit O
rule O
out O
Riyaa O
, O
sectarian O
and O
even O
political O
interest O
wey O
be O
di O
main O
motives O
for O
di O
sponsor O
of O
tafseer O
and O
dem O
oda O
religious O
lectures O
. O

Wetin O
dey O
interesting O
be O
say O
, O
while O
some O
sponsor O
dey O
compete O
for O
who O
go O
sponsor O
di O
broadcast O
of O
tafseer O
wey O
some O
prominent O
Ulama O
dey O
anchor O
, O
some O
of O
di O
Ulama O
dey O
sponsor O
dia O
own O
broadcast O
tafseer O
even O
if O
dem O
no O
see O
persin O
wey O
wan O
sponsor O
; O
odas O
even O
dey O
beg O
for O
sponsor O
wey O
go O
sponsor O
dia O
programme O
. O

Also O
, O
di O
content O
wey O
some O
tafseer O
and O
oda O
religious O
lectures O
dey O
feature O
get O
some O
serious O
flaws O
, O
to O
dey O
sponsor O
dis O
kin O
broadcast O
nah O
big O
misplacement O
of O
priority O

anoda O
thing O
wey O
dey O
interesting O
be O
say O
, O
some O
dey O
sponsor O
di O
broadcast O
of O
Adhan O
( O
Kiran O
sallah O
) O
for O
inside O
city O
like O
Kano B-LOC
. O

wia O
, O
thank O
you O
to O
sheer O
wey O
dey O
increase O
for O
Mosques O
, O
regular O
Adhan O
don O
dey O
reach O
evri O
corner O

Anyway O
, O
Ikhlas O
bin O
di O
ogbonge O
yardstick O
way O
dey O
determine O
if O
weda O
charitable O
feeding O
and O
di O
sponsoring O
of O
Ramadan O
tafseer O
broadcast O
dey O
worthy O
or O
not O
, O
striking O
appropriate O
balance O
between O
di O
two O
go O
give O
better O
outkom O
. O

Even O
though O
say O
Ramadan O
be O
di O
month O
of O
di O
Quran O
wey O
be O
say O
Muslims O
suppose O
dey O
commited O
in O
terms O
of O
reading O
, O
learning O
wetin O
im O
mean O
and O
to O
dey O
live O
dia O
lives O
accordingly O

Di O
month O
nah O
di O
month O
of O
generous O
charity O
wey O
be O
say O
Muslims O
, O
particularly O
di O
ones O
wey O
dey O
wealthy O
suppose O
dey O
do O
charity O
work O
, O
especially O
mass O
feeding O
. O

Howeva O
, O
while O
dat O
one O
com O
be O
di O
bottom O
line O
, O
wich O
explain O
why O
di O
controversy O
no O
dey O
necessary O
, O
di O
Liberal O
Musilims O
don O
over O
do O
am O

capitalizing O
on O
top O
public O
frustration O
wey O
dey O
inside O
di O
hunger O
wey O
dey O
wire O
di O
society O
, O
dem O
dey O
kwesion O
weda O
di O
sponsoring O
of O
di O
broadcast O
Ramadan O
tafseer O
dey O
worthy O
or O
relevance O
for O
under O
dis O
kin O
condition O
wey O
we O
dey O
find O
ourselves O
. O

As O
dem O
don O
pretend O
show O
empathy O
and O
concern O
, O
dey O
tok O
say O
di O
two O
charity O
work O
be O
di O
same O
and O
make O
pipo O
choose O
between O
dem O
. O

Under O
di O
hard O
condition O
wey O
pipo O
dey O
, O
e O
no O
surprise O
to O
dey O
see O
many O
pipo O
, O
including O
di O
ones O
wey O
fit O
discern O
, O
fall O
for O
di O
propaganda O
wey O
dem O
no O
know O
e O
context O
, O
nah O
im O
be O
di O
raging O
face O
- O
off O
wey O
dey O
between O
di O
Liberal O
Muslims O
, O
for O
anoda O
side O
, O
dem O
bin O
wan O
undermine O
Islamic O
and O
moral O
values O
for O
di O
society O
by O
force O
, O
togada O
with O
di O

Also O
, O
contrary O
to O
wetin O
dem O
claim O
, O
di O
Liberal O
Muslims O
no O
dey O
disturb O
by O
di O
kin O
wahala O
wey O
dey O
for O
di O
vulnerable O
, O
dis O
don O
explain O
why O
dem O
neva O
urge O
those O
wey O
dey O
spend O
huge O
resources O
on O
top O
oda O
things O
, O
no O
mater O
how O
worthless O
im O
be O
, O
make O
dem O
divert O
di O
resources O
to O
charitable O
course O
. O

Dem O
neva O
urge O
dat O
di O
kin O
massive O
amounts O
of O
resources O
dia O
elite O
role O
spend O
on O
top O
say O
dey O
wan O
maintain O
dia O
big O
lifestyles O
suppose O
dey O
diverted O
for O
di O
feeding O
of O
di O
poor O
or O
to O
take O
give O
dem O
shelter O

Instead O
, O
dia O
conscience O
go O
kom O
alive O
wen O
resources O
dey O
for O
only O
, O
say O
, O
Hajj O
, O
Umrah O
, O
Daourh O

Federers B-PER
conqueror O
dey O
amazed O
by O
dream O
day O
wey O
dey O
di O
office O

Afta O
im O
don O
wreck O
, O
Roger B-PER
Federers I-PER
return O
to O
di O
tennis O
courts O
, O
Pablo B-PER
Andujar I-PER
tok O
say O
dat O
na O
di O
sweetest O
moment O
a O
lengthy O
career O
. O

Spaniard B-PER
beat O
Federer B-PER
6 O
- O
4 O
, O
4 O
- O
6 O
, O
6 O
- O
4 O
on O
top O
di O
Geneva B-LOC
clay O
for O
Tuesday B-DATE
to O
scata O
di O
swiss O
tennis O
great O
hopes O
wey O
dem O
wan O
use O
run O
di O
match O
togeda O
ahead O
different O
major O
tournaments O
wey O
French O
open O
, O
Wimblendon O
and O
di O
Tokyo B-LOC
olympics O
. O

For O
match O
point O
on O
Tuesday B-DATE
, O
Andujar B-PER
, O
wey O
be O
di O
world O
number O
75 O
, O
hold O
im O
head O
for O
im O
hand O
in O
disbelief O
afta O
he O
don O
beat O
di O
20 O
- O
time O
Grand O
slam O
champion O
. O

I O
no O
fit O
believe O
am O
, O
nah O
wetin O
di O
35 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
tell O
ATPTour O
. O
com O
. O

Di O
memories O
of O
Nigeria B-LOC
colo O
wey O
dey O
for O
black O
and O
white O
( O
iii O
) O

sometimes O
afta O
dat O
, O
and O
afta O
I O
don O
get O
like O
two O
popular O
strip O
wey O
dey O
for O
di O
now O
default O
news O
paper O
wey O
dem O
dey O
call O
The O
Democrat O
, O
I O
get O
my O
first O
four O
letters O
wey O
reject O
me O
from O
Mavel B-ORG
Comics I-ORG
, O
I O
gada O
myself O
remain O
a O
young O
man O
wey O
still O
get O
hope O
. O

with O
di O
kin O
ups O
and O
downs O
wey O
dey O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
im O
still O
allow O
me O
get O
dream O
, O
to O
be O
artist O
wey O
dey O
work O
for O
a O
ogbonge O
culture O
company O
wey O
for O
anoda O
kontiri O
, O
anoda O
continent O

Fast O
- O
forward O
to O
20002 B-DATE
, O
one O
day O
as O
I O
dey O
sit O
down O
for O
di O
post O
office O
wey O
dey O
di O
centre O
of O
di O
city O
to O
drop O
off O
my O
latest O
art O
sample O
to O
Marvel B-ORG
Submission O
Editor O
, O
I O
no O
fit O
get O
bus O

Plenty O
pipo O
dey O
use O
leg O
take O
waka O
, O
some O
gada O
for O
group O
, O
dem O
dey O
worry O
. O

I O
dey O
weird O
out O
, O
waka O
go O
home O
, O
only O
to O
hear O
say O
raiot O
don O
start O
. O

again O
, O
many O
pipo O
die O
for O
di O
riot O
, O
farmilies O
and O
friends O
tear O
apart O
as O
Christian O
dey O
beingn O
move O
to O
Kaduna B-LOC
South I-LOC
and O
Muslims O
begin O
move O
from O
Kaduna B-LOC
South I-LOC
to O
di O
North O

My O
Kaduna B-LOC
, O
my O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
don O
dey O
fall O
apart O
. O

Di O
small O
consolation O
wey O
I O
get O
be O
some O
Christian O
friend O
wey O
stay O
for O
certain O
areas O
, O
like O
me O
, O
dem O
feel O
safe O
and O
no O
go O
anywia O

So O
, O
as O
di O
violence O
dey O
intense O
for O
oda O
parts O
, O
I O
go O
dey O
play O
soccer O
for O
my O
street O
, O
dey O
exchange O
VHS O
tapes O
and O
bootlegs O
VCDs O

Di O
idea O
to O
dey O
hate O
persin O
bikos O
of O
im O
religion O
or O
ethnic O
dey O
incredible O
for O
us O
. O

But O
one O
teen O
, O
wey O
just O
move O
to O
our O
domot O
some O
years O
, O
nah O
im O
make O
me O
get O
encounter O
with O
intolerance O
. O

if O
to O
say O
we O
be O
Muslims O
, O
playing O
soccer O
, O
dis O
new O
guy O
call O
us O
make O
we O
go O
attack O
di O
infidel O
wey O
dey O
live O
down O
di O
road O
. O

we O
com O
look O
each O
oda O
jokingly O
, O
we O
dey O
confuse O
, O
afta O
wich O
we O
burst O
to O
laughter O
, O
we O
com O
tell O
say O
make O
im O
get O
out O
. O

As O
if O
dat O
one O
no O
bad O
reach O
, O
my O
heartbreak O
for O
don O
worse O
as O
I O
see O
di O
apprearance O
of O
labels O
and O
slur O
from O
both O
of O
dem O
. O

My O
perfect O
Kaduna B-LOC
don O
dey O
fall O
apart O
, O
and O
families O
and O
friends O
don O
dey O
part O
ways O
, O
no O
be O
say O
dem O
no O
love O
each O
oda O
but O
bikos O
say O
dat O
na O
di O
safest O
thing O
to O
do O
. O

afta O
di O
wahala O
don O
end O
, O
I O
begin O
face O
university O
with O
cautious O
optimism O
. O

literally O
, O
many O
old O
friend O
dey O
there O
, O
as O
Zaria B-LOC
no O
too O
far O
from O
Kaduna B-LOC
. O

Many O
pipo O
dey O
get O
new O
friend O
, O
some O
dey O
till O
today B-DATE
, O
some O
don O
dey O
stronger O

The O
best O
part O
be O
say O
, O
all O
dis O
friend O
dem O
weda O
new O
or O
old O
, O
no O
dey O
base O
on O
religion O
or O
ethnicity O

Some O
of O
us O
wey O
notice O
know O
say O
, O
di O
Kaduna B-LOC
wey O
we O
know O
, O
love O
and O
don O
lose O
, O
neva O
really O
destroy O
. O

E O
no O
fit O
go O
bikos O
say O
nah O
for O
our O
heart O
im O
reside O
, O
so O
e O
go O
hard O
to O
kil O
patapata O

Afta O
all O
di O
almost O
29 B-DATE
years I-DATE
wey O
I O
don O
spend O
as O
a O
journalist O
, O
show O
me O
things O
wey O
plenty O
pipo O
no O
fit O
experience O
for O
dia O
life O
. O

I O
get O
front O
row O
seat O
to O
fight O
for O
, O
gbege O
attack O
, O
concerts O
by O
superstars O
dem O
, O
movies O
premieres O
and O
all O
kin O
generation O
- O
defining O
moments O

I O
also O
get O
to O
dey O
interview O
for O
some O
big O
big O
newsmaker O
wey O
dey O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
during O
moment O
wey O
dem O
get O
most O
chutzpah O
, O
or O
nothin O
at O
all O
. O

Nah O
di O
Nigeria B-LOC
wey O
no O
get O
worrior O
wey O
no O
fit O
fight O
for O
social O
justice O
, O
virtue O
- O
signalers O
, O
outrage O
- O
peddlers O
, O
or O
cancel O
culture O
- O
purveyor O
. O

Nah O
di O
Nigeria B-LOC
wey O
dey O
flawed O
, O
still O
dey O
remind O
me O
of O
my O
old O
Kaduna B-LOC
, O
even O
though O
di O
image O
different O
to O
each O
oda O
. O

But O
bodi O
no O
fit O
take O
all O
of O
dem O
for O
too O
long O
. O

On O
top O
of O
bed O
, O
I O
con O
look O
around O
my O
old O
room O
again O
, O
evrithin O
just O
dey O
as O
I O
leave O
am O
before O
im O
coronavirus O
lockdown O
. O

I O
com O
smile O
to O
myself O
, O
nah O
from O
dat O
moment O
I O
begin O
to O
dey O
decide O
on O
di O
kin O
steps O
wey O
I O
go O
take O
. O

I O
com O
twist O
di O
rubber O
band O
round O
di O
sack O
of O
fotos O
two O
times O
, O
com O
put O
am O
back O
for O
inside O
longbox O
. O

Maybe O
one O
day O
I O
go O
look O
oda O
ones O
, O
di O
colour O
foto O
, O
wey O
carry O
more O
recent O
memories O
. O

Maybe O
I O
no O
go O
do O
am O
. O

One O
thing O
dey O
clear O
say O
: O
nah O
my O
mother O
, O
and O
father O
, O
and O
di O
kin O
relationship O
wey O
dem O
get O
or O
wey O
dem O
no O
get O
wit O
me O
, O
nah O
im O
make O
me O
di O
kin O
child O
wey O
I O
be O
. O

Wetin O
I O
be O
to O
oda O
kids O
wey O
know O
me O
, O
also O
di O
kin O
man O
wey O
I O
be O
, O
to O
pipo O
wey O
know O
me O
. O

But O
I O
find O
am O
as O
wahahla O
, O
and O
e O
dey O
relieve O
more O
for O
my O
sack O
of O
black O
and O
white O
fotos O
, O
I O
don O
realize O
say O
while O
my O
head O
guide O
di O
kin O
persin O
wey O
I O
be O
, O
nah O
my O
heart O
don O
dey O
keep O
me O
Nigerian O
all O
dis O
years O
. O

42 O
Niger B-LOC
communities O
wey O
dey O
under O
Boko B-ORG
Haram I-ORG
dey O
control O
Senator O
Musa B-PER
. O

Di O
Senator O
wey O
dey O
represent O
Niger B-LOC
East I-LOC
for O
di O
National O
Assembly O
, O
Senator O
Mohammed B-PER
Sani I-PER
Musa I-PER
, O
im O
tok O
say O
about O
42 O
communities O
wey O
dey O
Niger B-LOC
State I-LOC
don O
fall O
under O
Boko B-ORG
Haram I-ORG
control O
. O

Dem O
don O
showcase O
5 O
, O
000 O
villagers O
for O
di O
last B-DATE
three I-DATE
days I-DATE
. O

Dis O
dey O
kom O
after O
Niger B-LOC
state I-LOC
governor O
, O
Sani B-PER
Bello I-PER
, O
don O
raise O
alarm O
say O
di O
insurgents O
don O
hoist O
dia O
flag O
for O
some O
communities O
. O

Speaking O
on O
di O
ground O
of O
senate O
on O
Tuesday B-DATE
while O
dem O
dey O
move O
on O
a O
motion O
on O
di O
kilins O
wey O
dey O
apun O
for O
Shiroro B-LOC
, O
Muya B-LOC
and O
Rafi B-LOC
local I-LOC
goment I-LOC
areas I-LOC
for O
Niger B-LOC
state I-LOC
, O
Senator O
Musa B-PER
tok O
say O
bandit O
and O
terrorist O
don O
kil O
ova O
475 O
persins O
for O
Niger B-LOC
East I-LOC
between O
2020 B-DATE
till I-DATE
date I-DATE
. O

Di O
lawmakers O
don O
express O
im O
worry O
dat O
almost O
seven B-DATE
years I-DATE
now O
Niger B-LOC
East I-LOC
Senatorial I-LOC
Districts I-LOC
wey O
dey O
Niger B-LOC
Delta I-LOC
don O
dey O
under O
eviriday O
and O
dey O
sustain O
plenty O
deadly O
attack O
by O
heartless O
, O
venomous O
, O
hydraheaded O
Boko B-ORG
Haram I-ORG
terrorist O
. O

Di O
result O
don O
dey O
total O
collapse O
wey O
dey O
di O
local O
economies O
of O
di O
affected O
victims O
, O
total O
collapse O
of O
educational O
system O
for O
di O
affected O
areas O
, O
famine O
don O
dey O
bikos O
of O
di O
collapse O
of O
agricultural O
activities O
, O
displacement O
wey O
be O
as O
a O
result O
of O
distortion O
of O
crisis O
prone O
areas O
, O
depopulation O
as O
a O
result O
of O
wanton O
death O
, O
wey O
dey O
among O
odas O
. O

Im O
tok O
say O
di O
attack O
are O
taking O
places O
for O
di O
absence O
of O
di O
slightest O
hindrances O
, O
resistance O
of O
confrotation O
from O
authorities O
. O

Dem O
don O
kidnap O
many O
and O
don O
seize O
dem O
wives O
from O
dem O
com O
forcefully O
attached O
dem O
to O
Boko B-ORG
Haram I-ORG
members O
. O

Three O
military O
camps O
wey O
dey O
Allour B-LOC
, O
Bassa B-LOC
and O
Zagzaga B-LOC
for O
di O
two O
local O
goment O
area O
don O
get O
sack O
, O
di O
insurgents O
don O
kil O
some O
security O
personnel O
in O
di O
last B-DATE
one I-DATE
month I-DATE
of O
di O
renewed O
attack O

I O
fit O
confirm O
am O
authoritatively O
say O
Boko B-ORG
Haram I-ORG
terrorist O
don O
mount O
dia O
flags O
for O
many O
places O
wey O
dem O
don O
capture O
like O
Kure B-LOC
, O
Alour B-LOC
and O
Magani B-LOC

Dey O
don O
abandoned O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
dis O
wat O
- O
torn O
part O
of O
di O
states O
and O
leave O
dem O
make O
dem O
face O
dia O
wahala O
, O
make O
dem O
dey O
in O
agony O
wey O
no O
get O
end O
and O
dey O
deep O
inside O
poverty O
. O

futhermore O
, O
for O
dis O
moment O
primary O
schools O
for O
Gwada B-LOC
, O
Kuta B-LOC
, O
Pandogari B-LOC
and O
Minna B-LOC
dem O
don O
carry O
dem O
do O
IDP B-LOC
camp I-LOC
as O
dem O
dey O
follow O
di O
sacking O
of O
almost O
5600 O
villagers O
from O
dia O
ancestral O
homes O
in O
Shiroro B-LOC
, O
Rafi B-LOC
and O
Munya B-LOC
local I-LOC
goment I-LOC
area I-LOC
for O
di O
last O
few O
weeks O
by O
di O
armed O
rubber O
wey O
don O
raid O
di O
town O
and O
villages O
. O

Wetin O
dis O
mean O
be O
say O
if O
dey O
fit O
attack O
without O
hindrance O
for O
Niger B-LOC
East I-LOC
Senatorial I-LOC
districts I-LOC
. O

I O
no O
know O
how O
we O
wan O
take O
bikom O
safe O
for O
Abujan O
again O
. O

Im O
tok O
say O
March B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
to O
date O
some O
jaguda O
don O
kil O
more O
25 O
gallant O
soldier O
dem O
, O
policemen O
and O
oda O
security O
personnel O
while O
16 O
civillians O
die O
, O
and O
dem O
no O
fit O
account O
for O
many O
odas O
. O

If O
dem O
no O
address O
dis O
threat O
drastically O
, O
di O
attack O
go O
continue O
and O
di O
danger O
wey O
day O
dat O
one O
be O
say O
e O
fit O
bikom O
wetin O
we O
no O
fit O
handle O
further O
to O
oda O
communities O
. O

Wey O
bin O
farming O
communities O
and O
dem O
bin O
farmers O
, O
dem O
fit O
comot O
dia O
farm O
dis O
season O
and O
dis O
fit O
negatively O
affect O
food O
surficiency O
and O
economic O
diversification O
policy O
of O
di O
Federal O
Goment O
, O
im O
added O
. O

My O
visit O
go O
Adamour B-LOC
state I-LOC

Working O
wit O
di O
goment O
for O
any O
level O
don O
offer O
innovators O
like O
me O
di O
chance O
to O
dey O
bring O
more O
beta O
and O
transformation O
wey O
we O
ordinarily O
no O
fit O
do O
for O
our O
field O

I O
strongly O
believe O
say O
di O
goment O
, O
as O
institution O
, O
be O
di O
greatest O
vehicle O
for O
systemic O
change O
and O
positive O
transformation O
wey O
persin O
no O
fit O
find O
anywia O
. O

For O
dat O
, O
weneva O
I O
kom O
across O
opportunities O
to O
work O
wit O
dem O
goment O
bodi O
, O
weda O
local O
or O
nah O
for O
outside O
country O
, O
I O
dey O
always O
dey O
hapi O
bikos O
say O
e O
represent O
a O
great O
opportunity O
for O
me O
learn O
from O
and O
fit O
contribute O
to O
di O
civil O
service O
wey O
dey O
fields O
dat O
are O
exciting O
and O
dey O
transformative O
for O
pipo O
beyond O
wetin O
my O

One O
of O
my O
recent O
visit O
of O
such O
nature O
nah O
to O
Adamour B-LOC
state I-LOC
, O
wey O
dey O
fascinating O
for O
me O
bikos O
of O
im O
diversity O
, O
resilience O
and O
outstanding O
potencial O
. O

I O
begin O
dey O
work O
actively O
for O
Adamour B-LOC
state I-LOC
some B-DATE
years I-DATE
ago I-DATE
, O
wit O
di O
international O
organisation O
, O
OXFAM B-ORG
, O
on O
top O
a O
project O
wey O
dey O
in O
line O
wit O
European B-ORG
Union's I-ORG
support O
to O
food O
security O
and O
resilience O
for O
Nothen O
Nigeria B-LOC
were O
we O
deployed O
a O
mobile O
solution O
to O
integrating O
di O
agricultural O
value O
chain O
. O

We O
don O
work O
wit O
field O
officers O
wey O
dey O
represent O
Fufore B-LOC
, O
Guyuk B-LOC
, O
Mubi B-LOC
South I-LOC
and O
Song B-LOC
local I-LOC
goment I-LOC
areas O
wey O
dey O
Adamour B-LOC
state I-LOC
to O
enhance O
agriculture O
and O
Agricbusiness O
practices O
wit O
tecnology O
. O

Howeva O
, O
my O
return O
to O
Adamour B-LOC
state I-LOC
last B-DATE
year I-DATE
dey O
towards O
a O
grannder O
and O
dey O
get O
more O
exciting O
task O
. O

E O
don O
involve O
a O
preposition O
to O
take O
work O
wit O
di O
state O
goment O
to O
transform O
di O
ministry O
of O
Entrepreneurship O
and O
Development O
and O
poverty B-ORG
Alliviation I-ORG
togeda I-ORG
wit I-ORG
di I-ORG
wealth I-ORG
creation I-ORG
Agency I-ORG
( O
PAWECA B-ORG
) O
wit O
di O
general O
aim O
of O
how O
to O
dey O
reduce O
poverty O
and O
dey O
sustainably O
dey O
improve O
prosperity O
for O
di O
teeming O
young O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
di O
state O
. O

For O
some O
context O
, O
I O
dey O
very O
delighted O
to O
learn O
dat O
di O
state O
goment O
don O
establish O
di O
ministry O
of O
entrepreneurship O
and O
Development O
wey O
go O
help O
lay O
focus O
on O
entrepreneurship O
and O
to O
acquire O
technical O
skil O
. O

E O
no O
exist O
untill O
di O
goment O
of O
Ahmadu B-PER
Umar I-PER
Fintiri I-PER
administration O
com O
establish O
am O
, O
di O
ministry O
don O
bikom O
di O
key O
pillar O
of O
di O
administration O
strategies O
wey O
dey O
towards O
economic O
development O
of O
di O
state O
. O

Di O
role O
of O
dis O
institution O
dey O
sailent O
as O
im O
supporse O
be O
for O
Adamour B-LOC
state I-LOC
, O
wit O
im O
fair O
share O
of O
youth O
unemployment O
, O
security O
and O
oda O
challenges O
. O

Im O
dey O
, O
howeva O
, O
very O
very O
evident O
dat O
the O
Adamour B-LOC
state I-LOC
ministry O
of O
Entrepreneurship O
and O
development O
, O
togeda O
wit O
Poverty B-ORG
Alleviation I-ORG
and I-ORG
Wealth I-ORG
Creation I-ORG
Agency I-ORG
( O
PAWECA B-ORG
) O
, O
e O
fit O
dey O
adequately O
utilised O
for O
trasforming O
di O
local O
economy O
, O
boosting O
youth O
entrepreneurship O
and O
to O
dey O
reduce O
unemployment O
drastically O
for O
di O
state O
. O

But O
as O
im O
be O
for O
most O
goment O
institutions O
, O
dis O
dey O
require O
discipline O
and O
dedicated O
effort O
to O
fit O
achieve O
dem O

Typically O
, O
for O
wia O
dey O
exist O
, O
complex O
international O
organisational O
challenges O
don O
shackle O
di O
growth O
and O
efficiency O
of O
dis O
kin O
institutions O
. O

For O
persin O
to O
understand O
dis O
conundrum O
, O
I O
tok O
to O
Adamour B-LOC
state's I-LOC
secretary O
to O
di O
state O
goment O
, O
Malam O
Bashiru B-PER
Ahmed I-PER
, O
who O
no O
dey O
only O
passionate O
about O
di O
issue O
but O
dey O
remarkably O
informed O
about O
local O
and O
global O
effort O
wey O
dey O
around O
am O
and O
as O
such O
uniquely O
position O
to O
help O
chat O
oury O
solving O
am O

Im O
repeat O
Governor O
Fintiri B-PER
commitment O
to O
take O
solve O
youth O
wey O
no O
get O
job O
and O
enhance O
di O
local O
economy O
by O
boosting O
entrepreneurship O
. O

Malam O
Bashiru B-PER
don O
express O
im O
idea O
and O
understanding O
wey O
dey O
around O
reforming O
and O
improving O
di O
capacity O
of O
ministries O
and O
agencies O
of O
goment O
, O
arguing O
dat O
di O
desire O
transformation O
only O
fit O
be O
possible O
if O
dem O
enhance O
di O
culture O
of O
innovation O
, O
embrace O
di O
use O
of O
technology O
, O
and O
if O
dem O
improve O
internal O
processeces O
and O
procedures O
so O
dat O

Nah O
bikos O
of O
di O
challege O
wey O
most O
public O
and O
private O
institution O
dey O
seek O
to O
solve O
continue O
to O
dey O
generate O
demands O
wey O
only O
technologically O
savvy O
, O
innovation O
- O
driven O
, O
forward O
thinking O
, O
and O
efficient O
institution O
fit O
do O
. O

In O
di O
course O
of O
di O
weeks O
to O
follow O
afta O
dis O
encounter O
, O
I O
also O
meet O
di O
Commissioner O
of O
di O
Ministry B-ORG
of I-ORG
Entrepreneurship I-ORG
and I-ORG
Youth I-ORG
Development I-ORG
, O
Ilya B-PER
James I-PER
and O
di O
head O
of O
Poverty B-ORG
Alliviation I-ORG
and I-ORG
Wealth I-ORG
Creation I-ORG
( O
PAWECA B-ORG
) O
Hajiya O
Aisha B-PER
Bello I-PER
, O
make O
dem O
examine O
wetin O
dem O
have O
and O
dia O
lay O
grounds O
for O
developing O
initiatives O
base O
on O

we O
wan O
establish O
organisational O
culture O
wey O
dey O
efficient O
and O
fit O
give O
result O
and O
go O
equip O
di O
ministry O
and O
agency O
to O
bikom O
innovation O
- O
driven O
through O
di O
use O
of O
technology O
. O

In O
a O
way O
wey O
dey O
demostrable O
and O
fit O
give O
result O
we O
go O
initiate O
human O
- O
centre O
design O
thinking O
among O
staff O
and O
optimaize O
internal O
processes O
to O
ensure O
quality O
service O
delivery O

last O
last O
, O
we O
go O
offer O
tools O
wey O
go O
dey O
for O
di O
monioring O
and O
measuring O
of O
organaisational O
performance O
of O
di O
ministry O
agency O
. O

Dis O
go O
go O
hand O
in O
hand O
for O
di O
already O
existing O
togada O
wit O
newly O
- O
hatched O
programs O
and O
campaings O
of O
di O
two O
institutions O

Governor O
fintiri B-PER
administration O
, O
by O
im O
sheer O
resolve O
and O
commitment O
wey O
dey O
towards O
capacity O
development O
ey O
dey O
in O
partnership O
wit O
various O
global O
and O
indeed O
local O
partner O
like O
di O
United B-ORG
Nation I-ORG
and I-ORG
Development I-ORG
Programme I-ORG
( O
UNDP B-ORG
) O
and O
di O
Nigerian B-ORG
Content I-ORG
Development I-ORG
Board I-ORG
( O
NCDB B-ORG
) O
, O
upgrading O
vocational O
and O
fabrication O
centres O
like O
di O
vocational O

I O
dey O
quite O
inspired O
by O
di O
kin O
obsession O
wey O
Governor O
Fintiri B-PER
get O
for O
local O
content O
participation O
policies O
wey O
dey O
all O
project O
and O
programme O
, O
wey O
dey O
evident O
for O
di O
goment O
derive O
for O
local O
content O
participation O
in O
di O
NEDC B-ORG
rapid O
response O
projects O
togeda O
wit O
bin O
di O
key O
galvaniser O
and O
pivot O
wey O
dey O
di O
North B-LOC
East I-LOC
Governor's O
forum O
. O

As O
I O
land O
for O
Yola B-LOC
dis B-DATE
week I-DATE
, O
di O
state O
capital O
of O
Adamour B-LOC
, O
amidst O
all O
dis O
aspirations O
for O
di O
great O
Fombina B-LOC
, O
as O
dem O
dey O
call O
di O
religion O
historically O
, O
I O
dey O
beset O
wit O
a O
renewed O
melanchonly O
for O
di O
loss O
of O
one O
of O
di O
greatest O
sons O
of O
Adamour B-LOC
, O
and O
Nigeria B-LOC
ogbonge O
public O
servant O
and O
academic O
Dr O
. O
Mahmud B-PER
Tukur I-PER
, O
who O
for O
im O
life O
time O
don O

We O
pray O
make O
Allah O
grant O
im O
great O
rewards O
, O
and O
make O
us O
fulfill O
im O
dream O
and O
aspiration O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
as O
a O
whole O
. O

Sinner B-PER
do O
set O
up O
Nadal B-PER
clash O
for O
Rome B-LOC
second O
round O

Jannik B-PER
sinner I-PER
do O
book O
a O
second O
- O
round O
showdown O
wit O
nine O
- O
time O
champion O
Rafael B-PER
Nadal I-PER
fot O
Italian O
open O
afta O
a O
6 O
- O
2 O
, O
6 O
- O
4 O
over O
Frenchmen O
Ugo B-PER
Humbert I-PER
on O
Monday B-DATE
. O

Di O
Italian O
teenager O
go O
face O
di O
20 O
- O
time O
Grand O
slam O
winner O
for O
di O
second O
time O
, O
afta O
im O
don O
impress O
against O
Nadal B-PER
in O
last B-DATE
years I-DATE
. O

French O
Open O
quarter O
- O
finals O
even O
though O
dem O
don O
lose O
for O
straight O
sets O
. O

Nadel O
don O
have O
a O
9 O
- O
2 O
record O
on O
clay O
dis O
season O
but O
dey O
beat O
am O
for O
di O
last O
eight O
for O
both O
previous O
masters O
events O
, O
for O
Monte B-LOC
Carlo I-LOC
and O
Madrid B-LOC
. O

Aslan B-PER
Karatsev I-PER
don O
dey O
same O
wit O
Sinner B-PER
wit O
im O
20th O
win O
of O
di O
season O
. O

Di O
Russian O
beat O
Miomir B-PER
Kecmanovic I-PER
7 O
- O
6 O
( O
7 O
/ O
2 O
) O
, O
6 O
- O
4 O
for O
di O
opening O
round O
. O

Nigerians O
don O
vex O
as O
Governors O
don O
mull O
N408 O
per O
litre O
for O
fuel O
price O
. O

Nigerians O
dem O
don O
express O
dia O
anger O
ova O
di O
proposal O
of O
di O
Nigeria B-ORG
goment I-ORG
Forum I-ORG
( O
NGF B-ORG
) O
committees O
on O
top O
fuel O
subsidy O
, O
to O
push O
for O
deregulation O
of O
di O
downstream O
. O

for O
a O
virtual O
meeting O
wey O
apun O
for O
Wednesday B-DATE
, O
di O
committee O
wey O
di O
state O
governor O
of O
Kaduna B-LOC
Nasir B-PER
El I-PER
- I-PER
Rufai I-PER
chaired O
inside O
a O
report O
, O
recommended O
a O
Premium O
Motor O
Spirit O
( O
PMS O
) O
wey O
dem O
dey O
also O
call O
petrol O
price O
wey O
between O
N408 O
. O
5 O
per O
litre O
and O
N380 O
per O
litre O
while O
dem O
dey O
call O
for O
immediate O
removal O
of O
fuel O
subsidy O

El B-PER
- I-PER
Rufai I-PER
tok O
say O
dem O
no O
fit O
sustain O
di O
current O
subsidy O
regime O
, O
and O
only O
smugglers O
dem O
and O
dem O
illegal O
markets O
dey O
benefit O
from O
am O
. O

Im O
also O
tok O
say O
Nigeria B-LOC
no O
fit O
benefit O
from O
di O
recent O
production O
wey O
Petroleum B-ORG
Exporting I-ORG
Countries I-ORG
( O
OPEC B-ORG
) O
, O
which O
dem O
suppose O
keep O
di O
fuel O
price O
high O
, O
bikos O
of O
subsidies O
. O

Nah O
between O
N70 O
billion O
and O
210 O
bn O
dem O
estimate O
to O
be O
dey O
spend O
evri B-DATE
month I-DATE
for O
di O
price O
of O
gasoline O
to O
remain O
165 O
per O
litre O
, O
dis O
dey O
below O
di O
cost O
price O
and O
di O
moni O
wey O
den O
give O
to O
di O
federation O
account O
go O
shrink O
to O
less O
dan O
50bn O
per O
month O
or O
even O
zero O
if O
threats O
persist O
, O
im O
tok O
. O

Di O
committee O
don O
recommend O
PMS O
pump O
price O
increment O
from O
di O
current O
N162per O
litre O
to O
N408 O
. O
5 O
per O
litre O

Reacting O
to O
dis O
on O
Thursday B-DATE
, O
Nigerians O
across O
di O
states O
don O
show O
dia O
anger O
on O
di O
governors O
. O

ForAnambra O
state O
, O
a O
civil O
servant O
, O
Mr O
. O
Uzoma B-PER
Okeke I-PER
tok O
say O
di O
proposal O
dey O
unthinkable O
if O
we O
dey O
look O
di O
state O
of O
economy O
of O
the O
nation O
. O

A O
driver O
wey O
im O
name O
be O
, O
Michael B-PER
Okafor I-PER
tok O
say O
im O
don O
dey O
struggle O
to O
buy O
petrol O
for O
N170 O
/ O
litre O
inside O
di O
state O
. O

Inside O
Jos B-LOC
for O
Plateau B-LOC
State I-LOC
, O
Malam O
Nura B-PER
Alhassan I-PER
wey O
be O
tailor O
, O
don O
express O
im O
disappointment O
on O
top O
di O
development O
. O

If O
di O
proposal O
don O
turn O
reality O
, O
di O
poor O
inside O
dis O
kontiri O
go O
suffer O
plenty O
bikos O
say O
whateva O
figure O
dem O
don O
increase O
, O
nah O
ordinary O
Nigerian O
go O
feel O
am O
. O

More O
pipo O
dem O
don O
react O
to O
dis O
inside O
Kaduna B-LOC
, O
Port B-LOC
Harcourt I-LOC
, O
Abeokuta B-LOC
, O
Jos B-LOC
and O
Kano B-LOC
. O

For O
instance O
, O
inside O
Kano B-LOC
, O
Buhari B-PER
Abba I-PER
Rano I-PER
, O
36 B-DATE
, O
tok O
say O
Wit O
dis O
kin O
level O
of O
insecurity O
wey O
dey O
around O
Nigerian O
governors O
dem O
dey O
busy O
dey O
start O
fake O
projects O
dem O
and O
loitering O
around O
Abuja B-LOC
and O
overnight O
agitating O
for O
complete O
deregulation O
. O

Dis O
don O
show O
say O
our O
crude O
oil O
don O
dey O
useless O
and O
dem O
no O
care O
about O
di O
dem O
lives O
of O
di O
common O
man O
. O

Fatima B-PER
Baba I-PER
Kura I-PER
tok O
im O
believe O
say O
dis O
price O
wey O
dem O
propose O
go O
kos O
set O
back O
for O
di O
kontiri O
to O
a O
worse O
state O
than O
wetin O
im O
don O
be O
. O

Inside O
Lagos B-LOC
, O
many O
Nigerians O
dem O
don O
express O
shock O
ova O
di O
don O
already O
propose O
fuel O
price O
increment O
from O
di O
governors O
dem O
who O
suppose O
to O
dey O
defend O
dia O
pipo O
. O

A O
student O
, O
Miss O
Onyekachi B-PER
Emeka I-PER
tok O
say O
di O
price O
increase O
go O
fit O
trigger O
increase O
inside O
transportation O
fare O
. O

For O
inside O
Akwa B-LOC
Ibom I-LOC
, O
Abia B-LOC
and O
Edo B-LOC
states I-LOC
, O
di O
residents O
dem O
don O
corroborated O
di O
view O
of O
oda O
Nigerians O
dem O
as O
dem O
dey O
described O
di O
proposal O
as O
unfair O
to O
di O
Nigerian O
pipo O
dem O
who O
don O
already O
have O
enough O
of O
di O
inflation O
rate O
, O
high O
cost O
of O
food O
and O
fuel O
and O
di O
security O
situation O
wey O
don O
dey O
spoil O
. O

Experts O
dem O
don O
tell O
FG O
say O
make O
im O
don O
discard O
proposal O

Experts O
wey O
react O
to O
dis O
development O
don O
bin O
urge O
di O
federal O
goment O
make O
dem O
discard O
di O
governors O
dem O
proposal O
for O
di O
best O
interest O
of O
dem O
Nigerian O
. O

Di O
pesin O
wey O
dey O
for O
in O
charge O
petrol O
industry O
, O
Siraju B-PER
Oyewale I-PER
tok O
say O
arbitrary O
fixing O
of O
fuel O
price O
dey O
diffirent O
to O
di O
principle O
of O
deregulation O
. O

I O
get O
problem O
wit O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
sit O
down O
dey O
sit O
down O
dey O
fix O
prices O
for O
petrol O
. O

Dat O
one O
no O
dey O
deregulation O

Dat O
one O
still O
be O
price O
regulation O
. O

Politicians O
dem O
, O
or O
even O
dem O
goment O
agencies O
wey O
dey O
fix O
prices O
dey O
different O
to O
di O
principle O
of O
deregulation O
. O

Even O
though O
say O
im O
support O
deregulation O
, O
Oyewale B-PER
tok O
say O
di O
price O
go O
rise O
above O
di O
current O
price O
but O
e O
no O
go O
reach O
N380 O
. O

Oyewale B-PER
also O
tok O
say O
Nigeria B-LOC
must O
to O
refine O
im O
crude O
oil O
for O
locally O
level O
to O
tackle O
di O
petrol O
import O
cost O
wey O
dey O
rise O
by O
NNPC B-ORG
. O

An O
economic O
expert O
wey O
dey O
stay O
for O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Samson B-PER
Simon I-PER
Galadima I-PER
tok O
say O
selling O
petrol O
for O
price O
wey O
dey O
twice O
di O
current O
price O
go O
further O
exacerbate O
inflationary O
pressure O
, O
hence O
, O
impoverishing O
Nigerians O
dem O
even O
more O
as O
purchasing O
power O
don O
reduce O
. O

Galadima B-PER
tok O
say O
lasting O
solution O
to O
Nigeria's B-LOC
fuel O
price O
wey O
no O
stable O
go O
dey O
deeply O
diversified O
energy O
- O
mix O
bikos O
our O
overdependence O
on O
petrol O
no O
dey O
healthy O
. O

President O
of O
di O
Independent B-ORG
Marketers I-ORG
Association I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nigeria I-ORG
( O
IPMAN B-ORG
) O
, O
Chinedu B-PER
Okoronkwo I-PER
tok O
say O
e O
dey O
wrong O
for O
di O
NGF B-ORG
to O
dey O
fix O
fuel O
price O
. O

Im O
tok O
say O
full O
deregulation O
go O
encourage O
more O
local O
and O
foreign O
investors O
dem O
to O
invest O
inside O
di O
sector O
and O
grow O
di O
economy O
but O
dat O
di O
governor's O
proposal O
should O
not O
be O
honoured O
. O

NNPC B-ORG
tok O
say O
nah O
only O
FG O
fit O
tell O
us O
how O
much O
to O
dey O
sell O
fuel O

Di O
Nigerian B-ORG
National I-ORG
Petroleum I-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
( O
NNPC B-ORG
) O
don O
tok O
say O
e O
no O
go O
go O
wit O
di O
proposal O
by O
NGF B-ORG
dat O
make O
dem O
sell O
a O
litre O
of O
petrol O
for O
N380 O
. O

Persin O
wey O
dey O
speak O
for O
NNPC B-ORG
Dr O
Kennie B-PER
Obateru I-PER
wey O
torchlight O
dis O
to O
Daily B-ORG
Trust I-ORG
on O
Thursday B-DATE
tok O
say O
as O
di O
fuel O
price O
be O
now O
, O
e O
don O
dbikom O
policy O
issue O
and O
nah O
only O
di O
federal O
goment O
fit O
direct O
di O
corporation O
to O
sell O
for O
a O
specific O
price O
. O

We O
still O
dey O
wait O
for O
di O
conclusion O
of O
di O
meeting O
wey O
dey O
go O
on O
between O
di O
organised O
labour O
and O
the O
Federal O
Goment O
. O

nah O
afta O
di O
outkom O
of O
di O
meeting O
we O
fit O
announce O
di O
price O

NNPC B-ORG
don O
tok O
say O
di O
NGF B-ORG
only O
made O
a O
proposal O
wey O
fit O
be O
accepted O
or O
discarded O
by O
di O
federal O
goment O
. O

PDP B-ORG
goment O
lack O
moral O
standing O
to O
dey O
demand O
for O
restructuring O
APC B-ORG
chieftain O

A O
chieftain O
of O
di O
ruling O
All B-ORG
Progressives I-ORG
Congress I-ORG
( O
APC B-ORG
) O
and O
Director O
General O
of O
the O
Progressives B-ORG
Governors I-ORG
Forum I-ORG
( O
PGF B-ORG
) O
, O
Salihu B-PER
Mohammed I-PER
Lukman I-PER
tok O
say O
dem O
governors O
wey O
dem O
elect O
on O
di O
platform O
of O
di O
pipos B-ORG
Democratic I-ORG
parti I-ORG
( O
PDP B-ORG
) O
don O
lack O
di O
moral O
standing O
to O
demand O
for O
executive O
bill O
and O
restructuring O
of O
di O
ogbodo O
. O

Few B-DATE
days I-DATE
ago I-DATE
afta O
PDP B-ORG
governor O
dem O
don O
do O
dia O
meeting O
for O
inside O
Ibadan B-LOC
, O
dem O
ask O
President O
Muhammadu B-PER
Buhari I-PER
make O
im O
send O
executive O
bill O
to O
di O
National O
Assembly O
make O
dem O
amend O
di O
kontiri's O
Constitution O
to O
devolve O
plenty O
powers O
to O
di O
states O
among O
odas O
. O

But O
reacting O
in O
a O
statement O
yesterday B-DATE
, O
di O
PGF B-ORG
Director O
General O
tok O
say O
nothing O
dey O
new O
inside O
di O
resolutions O
as O
progressive O
governors O
in O
line O
wit O
recommendations O
wey O
dem O
contain O
for O
di O
APC B-ORG
Committee O
on O
top O
True O
Federalism O
, O
don O
already O
take O
a O
position O
on O
top O
di O
matta O
and O
since O
don O
communicate O
am O
to O
di O
top O
echelon O
of O
di O
National O
Assembly O
. O

Has O
dem O
don O
mismanage O
dem O
opportunities O
to O
initiate O
all O
di O
recommendations O
dem O
wey O
dem O
bin O
don O
propose O
by O
di O
PDP B-ORG
governors O
dem O
between O
1999 B-DATE
and O
2015 B-DATE
, O
how O
anybodi O
for O
inside O
PDP B-ORG
go O
dey O
claim O
any O
moral O
standing O
to O
dey O
demand O
for O
any O
executive O
bill O
? O

If O
to O
say O
di O
issue O
is O
dey O
as O
simple O
as O
getting O
di O
President O
to O
transmit O
executive O
bill O
, O
wetin O
stop O
all O
di O
PDP B-ORG
President O
dem O
from O
initiating O
am O
for O
sixteen B-DATE
years I-DATE
? O

Nah O
18 O
elephants O
dem O
lightning O
kil O
for O
India B-LOC
. O

Dem O
see O
herd O
of O
18 O
wild O
Asiatic O
elephants O
wey O
die O
for O
inside O
India's B-LOC
eastern I-LOC
state I-LOC
of I-LOC
Assam I-LOC
, O
di O
fit O
apun O
bikos O
of O
a O
massive O
lightning O
strike O
, O
local O
officials O
tok O
am O
for O
Friday B-DATE
. O

some O
village O
pipo O
dem O
see O
fourteen O
adult O
elephants O
on O
Thursday B-DATE

dem O
see O
anoda O
bodies O
dem O
wey O
dem O
dey O
scata O
on O
top O
di O
foothills O
of O
di O
Kundoli B-LOC
reserve I-LOC
forest I-LOC
area I-LOC
of I-LOC
Assam I-LOC
, O
wey O
dey O
160 B-LOC
kilometres I-LOC
from I-LOC
di I-LOC
state I-LOC
capital I-LOC
of I-LOC
Dispur I-LOC
, O
local O
wildlife O
official O
, O
M B-PER
. I-PER
K I-PER
Yadava I-PER
, O
tell O
Reuters B-ORG
. O

Di O
state O
goment O
don O
order O
a O
high O
- O
level O
inquiry O
wey O
dey O
into O
di O
incident O
on O
Friday B-DATE
, O
nah O
Assam's B-LOC
Forest I-LOC
and I-LOC
Wildlife I-LOC
Minister O
, O
Parimal B-PER
Suklabaidya I-PER
, O
tok O
am O
. O

A O
preliminary O
report O
reason O
say O
di O
deaths O
fit O
be O
due O
to O
lightning O
even O
though O
say O
we O
need O
to O
find O
out O
through O
forensic O
tests O
if O
im O
possible O
say O
somethin O
else O
fit O
be O
di O
reason O
like O
poisoning O
or O
disease O
, O
nah O
wetin O
di O
minister O
talk O
be O
dat O
. O

Di O
pipo O
dem O
wey O
find O
di O
elephants O
dem O
, O
tok O
say O
im O
possible O
say O
nah O
lightning O
kil O
di O
animals O
dem O
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
, O
nah O
a O
local O
forest O
ranger O
tok O
am O
, O
im O
add O
say O
im O
see O
trees O
wey O
dey O
burn O
for O
di O
area O
. O

Di O
ranger O
no O
tok O
im O
name O
as O
im O
no O
suppose O
tok O
to O
di O
media O
. O

Di O
former O
deputy O
for O
national O
publicity O
secretary O
of O
di O
All B-ORG
Progressives I-ORG
Congress I-ORG
( O
APC B-ORG
) O
, O
Comrade O
Timi B-PER
Frank I-PER
, O
im O
fault O
di O
appointment O
of O
Major O
- O
General O
Farouk B-PER
Yahaya I-PER
as O
di O
Chief O
of O
Army O
Staff O
. O

Frank B-PER
tok O
for O
inside O
a O
statement O
for O
inside O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
dat O
President O
Muhammadu B-PER
Buhari's I-PER
penchant O
wan O
elevate O
junior O
officers O
inside O
di O
security O
establishments O
to O
superintendent O
ova O
dia O
seniors O
dem O
dey O
against O
di O
much O
- O
cherished O
military O
tradition O
of O
seniority O
and O
subordination O
. O

Im O
tok O
say O
di O
elevation O
of O
Yahaya B-PER
above O
im O
seniors O
dem O
nah O
direct O
hit O
against O
di O
military O
, O
wich O
go O
see O
senior O
, O
capable O
officers O
dem O
wey O
dem O
purge O
through O
compulsory O
retirement O
as O
we O
dey O
see O
am O
for O
di O
past O
. O

Im O
tok O
say O
di O
development O
dey O
capable O
to O
dey O
breeding O
widespread O
distrust O
, O
discontent O
, O
disloyalty O
, O
low O
morale O
and O
lack O
of O
motivation O
inside O
di O
military O
and O
oda O
security O
agencies O
dem O
. O

Di O
All B-ORG
Progressives I-ORG
Congress I-ORG
( O
APC B-ORG
) O
don O
express O
im O
excitement O
ova O
di O
recent O
appointment O
of O
Ahmed B-PER
Mustapha I-PER
Habib I-PER
as O
di O
new O
Director O
- O
General O
of O
di O
National B-ORG
Emergency I-ORG
Management I-ORG
Agency I-ORG
( O
NEMA B-ORG
) O
. O

Nah O
di O
Presidential O
tok O
tok O
persin O
, O
Garba B-PER
Shehu I-PER
, O
nah O
im O
announce O
di O
appointment O

Inside O
a O
congratulatory O
letta O
wey O
dey O
signed O
by O
dem O
National O
Secretary O
, O
Caretaker B-ORG
/ I-ORG
Extraordinary I-ORG
Convention I-ORG
Planning I-ORG
Committee I-ORG
( O
CECPC B-ORG
) O
, O
Sen O
. O
John B-PER
James I-PER
Akpanudoedehe I-PER
, O
wey O
dey O
di O
ruling O
parti O
don O
thank O
President O
Muhammadu B-PER
Buhari I-PER
for O
considering O
di O
new O
appointee O
wey O
dey O
worthy O
of O
di O
position O
. O

Di O
particular O
appointment O
nah O
demonstration O
of O
reward O
say O
im O
dey O
loyal O
to O
di O
parti O
and O
say O
dem O
recognise O
im O
selfless O
service O
to O
di O
kontiri O
, O
attributes O
wey O
fit O
clearly O
describe O
your O
persona O
. O

We O
trust O
say O
you O
get O
di O
capacity O
to O
do O
well O
well O
for O
dis O
your O
new O
assignment O
. O

APC B-ORG
tok O
say O
di O
parti O
dey O
appreciative O
of O
dis O
gesture O
of O
Mr O
President O
di O
best O
in O
dis O
endeavour O
. O

Di O
new O
oga O
for O
NEMA B-ORG
get O
extensive O
experience O
wey O
don O
span O
about O
25 B-DATE
years I-DATE
across O
different O
sectors O
, O
im O
sits O
on O
top O
di O
Board O
wey O
get O
various O
corporate O
, O
political O
and O
youth O
organisations O
, O
and O
im O
be O
di O
national O
chairman O
of O
Progressive B-ORG
pipo's I-ORG
Alliance I-ORG
between O
2010 B-DATE
and O
2011 B-DATE
. O

A O
player O
wey O
dey O
active O
inside O
di O
organisational O
and O
policy O
drives O
of O
di O
APC B-ORG
goment O
, O
Habib B-PER
bin O
dey O
di O
member O
of O
the O
Presidential O
Campaign O
Council O
inside O
2019 B-DATE
and O
national O
chairman O
of O
di O
National B-ORG
Committee I-ORG
of I-ORG
Buhari I-ORG
Support I-ORG
Groups I-ORG
since O
2015 B-DATE
, O
and O
also O
the O
vice O
- O
chairman O
of O
di O
federal O
goment O
- O
run O
State O
Selection O
Committee O
on O
di O
Extended O
Special O
Public O
Works O
Programme O
in O
Jigour B-LOC
State I-LOC
. O

Abia B-LOC
goment O
don O
reject O
IPOB B-ORG
strategy O
, O
dey O
demand O
for O
apology O
ova O
di O
war O
crimes O
wey O
dem O
hold O
against O
Igbos O

Di O
Abia B-LOC
State I-LOC
Governor O
, O
Dr O
. O
Okezie B-PER
Ikpeazu I-PER
don O
explain O
why O
im O
differed O
wit O
di O
strategy O
of O
di O
Indigenous B-ORG
pipo I-ORG
of I-ORG
Biafra I-ORG
( O
IPOB B-ORG
) O
secession O
and O
dia O
strategy O
for O
gbege O
. O

Im O
tok O
on O
Friday B-DATE
wen O
im O
visit O
di O
digital B-ORG
pan I-ORG
- I-ORG
African I-ORG
news I-ORG
network I-ORG
, O
di O
TOS O
TV O
network O
, O
wey O
Ms O
. O
Osasu B-PER
Igbinedion I-PER
led O
for O
inside O
Abuja B-LOC
. O

Di O
governor O
wey O
fault O
di O
strategy O
wey O
IPOB B-ORG
deployed O
led O
by O
self O
- O
exiled O
Nnamdi B-PER
Kanu I-PER
, O
dem O
howeva O
note O
dat O
dem O
no O
dey O
treat O
di O
Ndigbo O
fairly O
inside O
di O
kontiri O
. O

According O
to O
im O
, O
di O
destructive O
strategy O
of O
IPOB B-ORG
bin O
di O
recipe O
for O
di O
breakdown O
of O
law O
and O
order O
inside O
di O
South O
East O
geopolitical O
zone O
. O

As O
dem O
bin O
dey O
listen O
to O
oda O
reasons O
why O
im O
differ O
wit O
IPOB B-ORG
, O
di O
governor O
bin O
tok O
, O
But O
some O
of O
us O
no O
agree O
with O
im O
( O
Nnamdi B-PER
Kanu I-PER
) O
style O
bikos O
I O
no O
understand O
wia O
im O
dey O
go O
, O
wen O
im O
intend O
to O
pull O
di O
brakes O
and O
wen O
im O
go O
stop O
. O

If O
to O
say O
I O
get O
a O
way O
wey O
I O
fit O
convey O
my O
view O
to O
di O
leadership O
of O
di O
group O
wetin O
I O
go O
tok O
be O
say O
make O
dem O
find O
di O
way O
to O
enter O
into O
conversation O
and O
let O
pipo O
know O
. O

I O
no O
understand O
dia O
strategy O
and O
purpose O
. O

I O
no O
understand O
why O
dem O
dey O
attack O
institutions O
of O
civil O
rule O
. O

Plenty O
pipo O
dem O
wey O
dey O
apologetic O
to O
some O
of O
dis O
dem O
strategies O
no O
even O
know O
say O
dem O
dey O
ride O
for O
tigers O
tail O
. O

If O
di O
police O
and O
military O
withdraw O
and O
den O
brigands O
becom O
enforcers O
of O
di O
law O
and O
order O
, O
if O
you O
get O
quarrel O
wit O
your O
broda O
, O
how O
you O
wan O
take O
resolve O
am O
? O

While O
we O
still O
dey O
demand O
for O
national O
apology O
for O
di O
kin O
treatment O
dem O
dey O
meted O
to O
di O
Igbos O
during O
di O
nation's O
three O
- O
year O
civil O
war O
, O
Governor O
Ikpeazu B-PER
tok O
say O
our O
national O
orientation O
suppose O
dey O
willing O
to O
say O
sorry O
. O

No O
persin O
fit O
dey O
100 O
percent O
korekt O
all O
in O
life O

Even O
wen O
we O
wey O
deal O
wit O
our O
pikin O
dem O
if O
we O
do O
things O
wey O
no O
dey O
right O
, O
we O
suppose O
get O
di O
courage O
to O
come O
down O
to O
dia O
level O
and O
tell O
dem O
sorry O
but O
to O
create O
a O
utopian O
aura O
dat O
all O
dey O
well O
is O
either O
nothing O
is O
wrong O

or O
I O
don O
do O
am O
, O
wetin O
you O
fit O
do O
? O

Who O
fit O
tell O
us O
wetin O
apun O
for O
civil O
war O
, O
who O
do O
wetin O
and O
why O
dem O
do O
am O
? O

why O
be O
say O
say O
some O
pipo O
no O
fit O
kom O
tell O
us O
say O
dem O
sorry O
for O
we O
dem O
do O
? O

you O
no O
fit O
sweep O
somethings O
under O
di O
carpet O
. O

Di O
tension O
dey O
palpable O
and O
dis O
nah O
di O
time O
for O
us O
to O
dey O
open O
up O
up O
as O
pipo O
wey O
love O
dem O
kontiri O
. O

I O
dey O
speak O
like O
dis O
bikos O
say O
I O
spend O
seven B-DATE
years I-DATE
inside O
di O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Maguduri I-ORG
. O

I O
don O
waka O
through O
all O
part O
of O
northern B-LOC
Nigeria I-LOC

and O
I O
don O
sabi O
dis O
kontiri O

I O
feel O
bad O
say O
wetin O
dey O
bring O
us O
togeda O
don O
dey O
gradually O
go O
oury O
. O

Di O
NYSC B-ORG
don O
collapse O

We O
suppose O
dey O
tok O
di O
truth O
no O
matta O
whose O
o O
dem O
form O
. O

Some O
of O
di O
issues O
wey O
Nnamdi B-PER
raise O
nah O
issues O
of O
injustice O
, O
marginalisation O
, O
inequality O
weda O
nah O
gender O
, O
generational O
whateva O
. O

Any O
particular O
arm O
of O
di O
society O
wey O
dem O
exclude O
in O
any O
way O
get O
di O
right O
to O
feel O
say O
dem O
cheat O
am O
or O
dey O
unwanted O
. O

so O
, O
some O
of O
di O
things O
Nnamdi B-PER
tok O
dey O
valid O
. O

some O
of O
us O
fit O
see O
am O
. O

we O
no O
fit O
dey O
continue O
to O
dey O
run O
oury O
from O
di O
facts O

Di O
Islamic B-ORG
Movement I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nigeria I-ORG
( O
IMN B-ORG
) O
don O
accuse O
di O
FCT B-ORG
police I-ORG
command I-ORG
of O
harassment O
and O
intimidation O
. O

Di O
group O
wey O
protest O
ova O
di O
continued O
detention O
of O
im O
leader O
, O
Ibraheem B-PER
El I-PER
- I-PER
Zakzaky I-PER
at O
Wuse B-LOC
Market I-LOC
, I-LOC
Abuja I-LOC
, O
yesterday B-DATE
, O
claim O
say O
di O
police O
throw O
teargas O
and O
shot O
at O
di O
protesters O
dem O
. O

A O
statement O
wey O
Abdullahi B-PER
Musa I-PER
sign O
, O
on O
behalf O
of O
di O
Academic O
Forum O
of O
di O
IMN B-ORG
, O
tok O
say O
the O
police O
bin O
dey O
harass O
so O
many O
innocent O
pipo O
dem O
including O
passers O
- O
by O
, O
especially O
women O
while O
dem O
dey O
attempt O
to O
scatta O
di O
protesters O
. O

We O
kom O
out O
as O
usual O
on O
di O
streets O
of O
Abuja B-LOC
dey O
halla O
on O
di O
Nigerian O
authorities O
make O
dem O
respect O
the O
rule O
of O
law O
and O
make O
dem O
free O
our O
leader O
unconditionally O
and O
also O
to O
remind O
di O
general O
public O
dat O
in O
2015 B-DATE
within O
48hrs O
d O
kil O
ova O
1000 O
of O
im O
followers O
mercilessly O
by O
the O
officers O
and O
soldiers O
of O
the O
Nigerian B-ORG
Army I-ORG
as O
dem O
don O
officially O
launch O
attack O
on O
im O
inside O
im O
own O
residence O
, O
dem O
kil O
almost O
evri O
soul O
wey O
dey O
inside O
di O
house O
and O
com O
set O
dia O
corpses O
ablaze O
. O

Musa B-PER
don O
add O
say O
dat O
di O
protest O
be O
don O
start O
for O
around O
3 B-DATE
: I-DATE
00 I-DATE
for I-DATE
afternoon I-DATE
and O
dey O
go O
serere O
from O
Sky B-ORG
Memorial I-ORG
but O
just O
dem O
wan O
scatta O
for O
Wuse B-LOC
Market I-LOC
, O
di O
police O
arrive O
and O
start O
to O
dey O
shoot O
teargas O
and O
life O
ammunition O
on O
di O
peaceful O
and O
unarmed O
protesters O
. O

Di O
police O
harass O
plenty O
innocent O
pipo O
including O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
pass O
by O
wich O
plenty O
of O
dem O
be O
women O
and O
dem O
removed O
dia O
hijabs O
, O
im O
tok O
further O
. O

di O
FCT B-ORG
police I-ORG
command I-ORG
spokespesin O
, O
ASP O
Maryam B-PER
Yusuf I-PER
, O
tok O
say O
di O
group O
dey O
disturb O
public O
peace O
wit O
dia O
protest O
. O

NAPTIP B-ORG
arraigns O
, O
dem O
reunite O
five O
trafficked O
children O
wit O
dia O
parents O
. O

Di O
FCT B-ORG
police I-ORG
command I-ORG
spokespesin O
, O
ASP O
Maryam B-PER
Yusuf I-PER
, O
tok O
say O
di O
group O
dem O
dey O
disturb O
public O
peace O
wit O
dia O
protest O
. O

NAPTIP B-ORG
, O
for O
di O
press O
briefing O
at O
di O
weekend B-DATE
, O
tok O
say O
Abdulrahman B-PER
, O
a O
32 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
man O
, O
him O
abducted O
children O
wey O
dem O
dey O
di O
age O
of O
four O
to O
seven O
and O
sell O
dem O
to O
some O
women O
wey O
dey O
different O
parts O
of O
di O
kontiri O
wey O
dey O
under O
di O
guise O
of O
say O
im O
adoption O
dem O
. O

Di O
Director O
General O
, O
Mrs O
. O
Imaan B-PER
Sulaiman I-PER
- I-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
, O
wen O
im O
dey O
hand O
ova O
di O
children O
to O
dia O
parents O
im O
say O
, O
di O
suspect O
tell O
di O
would O
be O
parents O
adoption O
papers O
purportedly O
from O
di O
Niger B-LOC
State I-LOC
Goment O
. O

She O
tok O
say O
, O
dem O
catch O
am O
red O
handed O
wen O
im O
dey O
help O
im O
clients O
fill O
dia O
adoption O
application O
forms O
. O

She O
warn O
say O
make O
parents O
dem O
dey O
guard O
dia O
children O
dem O
to O
avoid O
kidnapping O
wey O
dey O
apun O
, O
trafficking O
and O
oda O
crimes O
dem O
wey O
dey O
against O
humanity O
, O
she O
add O
say O
make O
dem O
no O
expose O
dem O
to O
pipo O
wey O
get O
criminal O
intention O
. O

She O
tok O
say O
di O
pesin O
wey O
dey O
investigate O
di O
matta O
don O
follow O
an O
intelligence O
report O
dat O
Abdulrahman B-PER
kidnapped O
children O
from O
Niger B-LOC
State I-LOC
and O
com O
sell O
dem O
into O
different O
parts O
of O
di O
kontiri O
. O

Di O
DG O
also O
tok O
say O
di O
intelligence O
report O
don O
reveal O
that O
di O
suspect O
bin O
don O
dey O
do O
dat O
claiming O
to O
be O
a O
staff O
of O
di O
Ministry B-ORG
of I-ORG
Social I-ORG
Development I-ORG
of I-ORG
Niger I-ORG
State I-ORG
wey O
dey O
in O
charge O
of O
adoption O
dem O
matta O
. O

She O
tok O
say O
Abdulrahman B-PER
don O
confess O
say O
im O
don O
collect O
di O
sum O
of O
N100 O
, O
000 O
for O
each O
of O
di O
children O
. O

Di O
parents O
dem O
don O
laud O
di O
federal O
goment O
and O
NAPTIP B-ORG
management O
for O
rescuing O
dia O
children O
and O
don O
promise O
to O
take O
proper O
care O
of O
dem O
. O

Governors O
dem O
wey O
dem O
elect O
on O
di O
platform O
of O
di O
pipos B-ORG
Democratic I-ORG
parti I-ORG
( O
PDP B-ORG
) O
don O
warn O
di O
Economic B-ORG
and I-ORG
Financial I-ORG
Crime I-ORG
Commission I-ORG
( O
EFCC B-ORG
) O
make O
dem O
no O
dey O
witch O
- O
hunt O
im O
parti O
officials O
dem O
. O

Di O
governors O
dem O
don O
dey O
respond O
to O
di O
invitation O
of O
three O
officials O
of O
di O
parti O
by O
di O
antigraft O
agency O
ova O
alleged O
misappropriation O
of O
N10 O
billion O
, O
which O
the O
Secondus B-PER
- O
led O
National B-ORG
Working I-ORG
Committee I-ORG
( O
NWC B-ORG
) O
wey O
dem O
don O
already O
deny O
. O

di O
forum O
, O
for O
di O
statement O
by O
im O
Director O
- O
General O
, O
Hon O
CID O
Maduabum B-PER
, O
tok O
say O
di O
invitation O
of O
di O
officials O
ova O
a O
spurious O
petition O
by O
a O
disgruntled O
former O
member O
of O
PDP B-ORG
don O
raise O
quesion O
on O
di O
seriousness O
and O
impartiality O
of O
di O
anti O
- O
graft O
agency O
to O
do O
im O
work O
. O

Di O
statement O
tok O
: O
While O
PDP B-ORG
as O
a O
political O
parti O
dey O
accountable O
to O
im O
members O
dem O
and O
di O
general O
public O
for O
im O
actions O
, O
we O
dey O
, O
howeva O
, O
concerned O
dat O
di O
old O
tactics O
of O
using O
di O
EFCC B-ORG
to O
dey O
silence O
political O
opposition O
don O
dey O
entre O
into O
our O
polity O
again O
. O

we O
think O
say O
di O
EFCC B-ORG
wey O
dey O
di O
new O
leadership O
go O
learn O
from O
di O
mistake O
of O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
before O
am O
. O

Nah O
misplaced O
priority O
e O
be O
for O
EFCC B-ORG
to O
dey O
abandon O
revelations O
of O
big O
big O
fraud O
wey O
many O
officials O
and O
agencies O
of O
di O
Federal O
goment O
dey O
do O
to O
pursue O
di O
PDP B-ORG
wey O
be O
di O
main O
opposition O
parti O
doing O
a O
yeoman's O
job O
to O
dey O
prevent O
di O
descent O
into O
chaos O
and O
anarchy O
for O
inside O
Nigeria B-LOC
. O

Maybe O
some O
interests O
inside O
goment O
dey O
worried O
about O
di O
increasingly O
assertive O
role O
di O
PDP B-ORG
dey O
play O
in O
calling O
out O
corruption O
inside O
goment O
and O
wan O
to O
weaken O
and O
silence O
am O
. O

Even O
di O
message O
wey O
dem O
dey O
tok O
about O
no O
make O
any O
allegation O
of O
misuse O
of O
goment O
funds O
, O
or O
cheating O
of O
any O
persin O
or O
public O
authority O
by O
di O
PDP B-ORG
. O

E O
dey O
surprising O
dat O
EFCC B-ORG
wan O
use O
im O
scarce O
human O
and O
oda O
resources O
to O
begin O
investigation O
into O
PDP B-ORG
finances O
. O

If O
EFCC B-ORG
dey O
even O
- O
handed O
and O
dey O
non O
- O
partisan O
, O
e O
suppose O
conduct O
investigation O
into O
oda O
political O
parties O
including O
APC B-ORG
, O
wey O
be O
di O
ruling O
party O
. O

PDP B-ORG
dey O
up O
to O
date O
for O
making O
financial O
returns O
as O
di O
required O
by O
the O
Constitution O
to O
INEC B-ORG

We O
no O
know O
say O
INEC B-ORG
don O
make O
complaints O
to O
EFCC B-ORG
on O
PDP's B-ORG
return O
. O

We O
dey O
face O
existential O
threats O
as O
a O
nation O
and O
PDP B-ORG
suppose O
remain O
focus O
on O
im O
role O
as O
a O
watchdog O
on O
behave O
of O
Nigerians O
. O

Di O
Senator O
wey O
dey O
represent O
Kaduna B-LOC
Central I-LOC
, O
Uba B-PER
Sani I-PER
, O
don O
lament O
say O
children O
be O
di O
one O
wey O
dem O
dey O
suffer O
most O
for O
di O
kontiri O
recurring O
economic O
and O
security O
wahala O
dem O
. O

For O
di O
children's O
day O
message O
, O
Sani B-PER
note O
say O
children O
don O
dey O
face O
di O
deprivation O
bikos O
of O
di O
insecurity O
wey O
dey O
many O
kontiri O
. O

some O
of O
dem O
don O
dey O
stuck O
for O
inside O
Internally O
Displaced O
Persins O
( O
IDPs O
) O
camps O
. O

dia O
education O
don O
suffer O

plenty O
of O
dem O
no O
get O
access O
to O
healthcare O
. O

Dem O
no O
get O
any O
recreation O
for O
dem O

Dem O
dey O
abuse O
some O
of O
di O
girls O
. O

Dem O
dey O
live O
inside O
di O
fear O
of O
di O
unknown O
. O

Make O
we O
dey O
reflect O
on O
top O
our O
children O
loss O
of O
dia O
innocence O
and O
our O
duties O
dem O
and O
obligation O
wey O
we O
don O
lose O
as O
leaders O
and O
pipo O
. O

plenty O
of O
dem O
die O
bikos O
say O
dem O
no O
get O
health O
care O

Di O
economic O
impact O
of O
COVID O
- O
19 O
on O
dia O
parent O
dey O
affect O
di O
children O
in O
a O
nagative O
way O
. O

Di O
quality O
of O
food O
wey O
dem O
dey O
chop O
don O
reduce O
to O
and O
some O
of O
dem O
no O
fit O
go O
school O
again O
, O
nah O
wetin O
im O
tok O
be O
dat O
. O

Di O
lawmaker O
don O
call O
for O
effective O
implementation O
of O
policies O
and O
programmes O
wey O
go O
aim O
at O
providing O
betta O
education O
and O
betta O
health O
care O
for O
di O
children O

Di O
investment O
wey O
put O
for O
our O
children O
nah O
di O
investment O
wey O
we O
put O
for O
di O
future O
of O
our O
kontiri O
. O

Im O
add O
say O
, O
make O
we O
no O
fail O
for O
dis O
regards O
. O

Wetin O
dey O
fuel O
insurgency O
? O

Wen O
a O
group O
of O
pipo O
wey O
no O
dey O
informed O
get O
an O
idealogy O
wey O
dey O
fit O
die O
for O
, O
dem O
go O
do O
di O
illogical O
for O
am O
. O

Di O
kind O
intercourse O
wey O
dey O
between O
ideology O
and O
ignorance O
no O
dey O
follow O
logic O
. O

Dem O
consider O
murder O
as O
di O
sin O
wey O
dealy O
pass O
for O
Igbo O
land O
. O

In O
fact O
, O
for O
di O
old O
days O
if O
dem O
committe O
murder O
, O
di O
community O
go O
proceed O
on O
many O
days O
of O
cleansing O
of O
di O
land O
and O
atonement O
for O
di O
crime O
. O

Wetin O
change O
now O
? O

plenty O
pipo O
don O
assume O
dat O
di O
Igbo O
are O
natively O
no O
dey O
violence O
and O
dat O
dey O
cannot O
in O
any O
circumstances O
dey O
take O
innocent O
lives O
violently O
. O

Di O
Igbo O
pipo O
dey O
very O
peaceful O
, O
but O
wetin O
dey O
apun O
recently O
inside O
South O
- O
east O
don O
make O
us O
to O
dey O
doubt O
di O
assumption O

All O
di O
regions O
inside O
di O
kontiri O
don O
dey O
marginalise O
as O
regards O
say O
di O
equitable O
distribution O
of O
resources O
to O
di O
pipo O
. O

To O
dey O
clear O
, O
nah O
evri O
region O
don O
dey O
marginalise O

Di O
statement O
wey O
dey O
more O
factual O
go O
be O
all O
Nigerians O
wey O
dey O
di O
bottom O
rung O
of O
di O
social O
ladder O
dey O
marginalise O
. O

Nah O
Nigerians O
be O
victims O
of O
di O
carnivory O
of O
di O
elite O
. O

E O
no O
mata O
say O
dem O
com O
from O
di O
North O
or O
di O
south O
. O

Nah O
all O
of O
us O
be O
victims O
of O
elite O
conspiracy O
e O
no O
mata O
wia O
we O
kom O
from O
. O

E O
dey O
so O
agonising O
say O
di O
scion O
of O
di O
south O
- O
east O
don O
dey O
turn O
dia O
region O
into O
Aleppo B-LOC
inside O
Syria B-LOC
. O

Nah O
who O
bring O
war O
and O
violence O
into O
im O
own O
home O
? O

As O
of O
2019 B-DATE
, O
di O
south O
- O
east O
dey O
reputed O
say O
e O
dey O
very O
safe O
pass O
any O
oda O
region O
for O
inside O
Nigeria B-LOC
. O

E O
dey O
very O
buoyant O
and O
dey O
well O
fared O
on O
top O
di O
development O
inside O
index O
. O

All O
of O
dat O
don O
dey O
tremble O
down O
. O

Di O
kilin O
of O
police O
officers O
some O
of O
dem O
Igbo O
di O
targeting O
of O
northern O
residents O
; O
di O
destruction O
of O
property O
and O
arsoning O
of O
police O
stations O
dem O
be O
di O
tragedies O
wey O
no O
suppose O
apun O
. O

Dem O
dey O
fed O
di O
cancer O
and O
dem O
allow O
am O
spread O
throughout O
di O
bodi O
. O

Di O
Igbo O
dem O
nourish O
dis O
beast O
wey O
dey O
gnawing O
at O
dia O
groin O
. O

Wen O
dem O
start O
di O
serial O
murder O
of O
police O
officers O
, O
some O
clap O
for O
di O
effort O
of O
dia O
kilers O
on O
di O
inscrutable O
assumption O
say O
di O
police O
dey O
inside O
cahoots O
wit O
criminals O
to O
destroy O
Igbo O
land O
. O

Now O
, O
di O
destruction O
of O
di O
region O
no O
dey O
for O
di O
hands O
of O
some O
herdsmen O
or O
bandits O
, O
but O
for O
di O
might O
of O
di O
sons O
of O
di O
land O
. O

How O
you O
wan O
take O
define O
irony O
? O

Dem O
dey O
threaten O
di O
Igbo O
pipo O
wey O
get O
different O
opinions O
to O
di O
group O
sentiments O
wit O
violence O
. O

Dem O
no O
know O
di O
Igbo O
to O
get O
strong O
head O
or O
conscripted O
into O
tyranny O
of O
opinions O
and O
actions O

Dem O
know O
Igbo O
to O
be O
republican O
; O
dem O
dey O
open O
to O
robust O
arguments O
and O
dem O
dey O
subject O
evri O
thought O
to O
scrutiny O
. O

Wetin O
com O
change O
? O

He O
be O
like O
say O
di O
kilin O
of O
police O
officers O
inside O
di O
south O
- O
east O
bin O
don O
dey O
unmitigated O
and O
security O
agencies O
don O
appear O
to O
don O
leave O
di O
pipo O
to O
dia O
own O
fate O
. O

Armed O
robber O
dem O
don O
return O
at O
scale O
. O

Nah O
dis O
be O
pipo O
lamentation O
evriwia O
. O

A O
lady O
wey O
share O
her O
experience O
of O
how O
a O
mechanic O
wey O
she O
pay O
upfront O
to O
fix O
her O
car O
inside O
Anambra B-LOC
runaway O
wit O
di O
moni O
and O
automobile O
, O
and O
even O
threatened O
her O
while O
im O
dey O
brag O
, O
police O
no O
dey O
inside O
di O
south O
- O
east O
again O
. O

Jaguda O
don O
take O
control O
of O
interest O
areas O
inside O
di O
region O
. O

Fear O
and O
wahala O
dey O
evriwia O
. O

Life O
don O
bikom O
nasty O
, O
brutish O
and O
short O
inside O
a O
region O
wey O
dey O
peaceful O
before O
. O

As O
a O
mata O
of O
fact O
, O
we O
dey O
on O
a O
familiar O
path O
albeit O
dey O
dangerous O

Di O
signs O
dey O
very O
tragic O

Pikin O
wey O
dem O
born O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
in O
2000 O
fit O
tell O
how O
Boko B-ORG
Haram I-ORG
take O
start O
inside O
North O
- O
east O
. O

Di O
militant O
groups O
dey O
ourys O
target O
di O
security O
agents O
and O
formations O
eviritime O
. O

Wen O
dey O
take O
dem O
out O
, O
di O
pipo O
no O
go O
fit O
defence O
demselves O
and O
di O
armed O
gangs O
go O
start O
a O
new O
order O
of O
violence O
. O

Dem O
don O
kill O
securities O
and O
dem O
destroy O
security O
facilities O
in O
di O
South O
- O
east O
now O

Afta O
di O
security O
scaffold O
don O
dey O
decimated O
, O
innocent O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
live O
di O
area O
and O
even O
those O
wey O
dey O
satisfied O
ova O
di O
revelry O
of O
blood O
fit O
bikom O
di O
next O
victims O
. O

Dem O
be O
displaced O
persins O
wey O
dey O
live O
inside O
IDP O
camps O
for O
inside O
part O
of O
Eboyi B-LOC
state I-LOC
displace O
, O
dis O
apun O
as O
a O
result O
of O
interncine O
clashes O
among O
communities O
. O

Wit O
di O
kin O
prevailing O
savagery O
wey O
di O
secessionist O
group O
, O
there O
go O
be O
more O
refugee O
problem O
inside O
south O
- O
east O
if O
dem O
continue O
wit O
di O
attack O
. O

wia O
dey O
wan O
put O
pipo O
wey O
be O
say O
wetin O
dem O
dey O
do O
nah O
buying O
and O
selling O
? O

we O
no O
fit O
end O
dis O
barbarity O
if O
we O
no O
agree O

If O
some O
pipo O
choose O
to O
keep O
native O
sympathies O
for O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
take O
innocent O
lives O
, O
how O
go O
fit O
stop O
di O
bloodletting O
stop O
? O

E O
dey O
for O
our O
hand O
. O

Marwa B-PER
don O
meet O
wit O
IGP O
, O
tok O
say O
Buhari B-PER
don O
demand O
mopping O
up O
of O
dugs O
wey O
no O
dey O
legal O
. O

President O
Muhammadu B-PER
Buhari I-PER
dan O
order O
di O
National B-ORG
Drug I-ORG
Law I-ORG
Enforcement I-ORG
Agency I-ORG
( O
NDLEA B-ORG
) O
make O
dem O
mop O
up O
all O
drugs O
wey O
no O
dey O
legal O
and O
substances O
inside O
di O
kontiri O
make O
Nigeria B-LOC
bikom O
a O
drug O
- O
safe O
haven O
. O

Mohammed B-PER
Buba I-PER
Marwa I-PER
( O
Retd O
) O
tok O
for O
Wednesday B-DATE
inside O
Abuja B-LOC
wen O
im O
host O
di O
acting O
Inspector O
General O
of O
Police O
, O
Alkali B-PER
Baba I-PER
Usman I-PER
. O

dis O
dey O
as O
im O
urge O
di O
police O
to O
hand O
over O
drugs O
wey O
dey O
no O
dey O
legal O
and O
make O
dem O
arrest O
suspects O
wey O
dey O
in O
connection O
wit O
drug O
trafficking O
to O
di O
NDLEA B-ORG
for O
prosecution O
as O
e O
no O
fall O
under O
Police O
jurisdiction O
. O

Im O
also O
tok O
say O
dat O
within O
three B-DATE
months I-DATE
, O
di O
agency O
don O
seize O
ova O
two O
million O
kgs O
of O
assorted O
drugs O
wey O
be O
say O
the O
value O
at O
N80bn O
. O

According O
to O
wetin O
im O
tok O
, O
di O
agency O
don O
arrest O
2 O
, O
100 O
criminals O
wey O
dey O
associated O
wit O
di O
illicit O
trade O
and O
dem O
don O
secure O
ova O
350 O
convictions O
so O
far O
. O

So O
far O
, O
we O
know O
say O
about O
15 O
million O
Nigerians O
dey O
use O
drug O
, O
number O
dey O
very O
high O
and O
we O
dey O
work O
on O
di O
mandate O
wey O
di O
President O
give O
us O
to O
mop O
up O
all O
illicit O
substances O
and O
make O
Nigeria B-LOC
bikom O
a O
drug O
- O
safe O
haven O
, O
di O
NDLEA B-ORG
don O
remain O
upstanding O
by O
radiating O
up O
our O
activities O
. O

within O
three B-DATE
months I-DATE
, O
we O
don O
seize O
ova O
2 O
million O
kilogrammes O
of O
assorted O
drugs O
. O

We O
don O
seized O
dis O
drugs O
to O
di O
value O
of O
N80bn O
, O
we O
do O
arrest O
2 O
, O
100 O
criminals O
wey O
dey O
associated O
wit O
dis O
illicit O
trade O
and O
we O
don O
secure O
ova O
350 O
convictions O
so O
far O
. O

We O
stil O
dey O
count O
by O
di O
grace O
of O
God O

Some O
of O
our O
officers O
dem O
dey O
involve O
in O
seizures O
of O
drugs O
wich O
dey O
okay O
. O

But O
dem O
suppose O
hand O
over O
to O
NDLEA B-ORG
afta O
dat O
. O

Marwa B-PER
tok O
say O
nah O
very O
few O
pipo O
proceed O
wit O
prosecuting O
those O
cases O
, O
dem O
no O
suppose O
do O
am O
since O
nah O
NDLEA B-ORG
dey O
in O
charge O
. O

While O
dem O
dey O
seek O
make O
dem O
join O
bodi O
wit O
di O
police O
for O
di O
next O
phase O
of O
flushing O
out O
drug O
barons O
, O
im O
express O
optimism O
say O
more O
of O
dis O
barons O
dem O
go O
kom O
into O
di O
agency O
net O
. O

We O
belive O
say O
di O
NPF B-ORG
go O
support O
us O
wit O
intelligence O
tracking O
, O
e O
dey O
possible O
say O
di O
NPF B-ORG
don O
alredy O
do O
am O
. O

We O
ask O
for O
slot O
for O
inside O
police O
institutes O
so O
we O
fit O
bikom O
beneficiaries O
. O

We O
go O
appoint O
liaison O
officer O
between O
us O
so O
we O
go O
fit O
ensure O
definite O
contact O
. O

We O
need O
to O
dey O
renew O
di O
join O
bodi O
wey O
dey O
between O
us O
bikos O
di O
use O
of O
drugs O
don O
dey O
confirmed O
as O
a O
major O
precursor O
to O
criminal O
activities O
wey O
dey O
inside O
Nigerial O
. O

Marwa B-PER
tok O
say O
nah O
dis O
time O
dem O
suppose O
join O
bodi O
more O
. O

As O
im O
dey O
speak O
ealier O
, O
IGP O
recall O
say O
im O
bin O
Borno B-LOC
State I-LOC
Police O
Public O
Relation O
Officer O
for O
dat O
time O
. O

Nah O
Marwa B-PER
be O
di O
Military O
Administrator O
. O

Experience O
nah O
im O
be O
di O
best O
teacher O
, O
you O
don O
dey O
for O
dis O
business O
of O
crime O
prevention O
and O
control O
. O

We O
dey O
here O
to O
declare O
to O
you O
my O
unalloyed O
cooperation O
. O

We O
go O
join O
bodi O
and O
synergize O
wit O
di O
angency O
so O
we O
go O
fit O
police O
dis O
kontiri O
. O

For O
evri O
crime O
, O
we O
dey O
always O
get O
issue O
of O
drug O
. O

Usman B-PER
tok O
say O
if O
we O
fit O
synergize O
, O
cooperate O
and O
join O
, O
e O
go O
dey O
very O
beneficial O
to O
Nigerians O
and O
law O
enforcement O
as O
a O
whole O
. O

Obaseki B-PER
tok O
say O
, O
nah O
my O
victory O
end O
godfatherism O
for O
inside O
Edo B-LOC
. O

Edo B-LOC
State I-LOC
Governor O
Godwin B-PER
Obaseki I-PER
tok O
say O
nah O
im O
victory O
at O
di O
Supreme B-ORG
Court I-ORG
signals O
an O
end O
to O
godfatherism O
inside O
di O
state O
. O

Di O
Supreme B-ORG
Court I-ORG
on O
Friday B-DATE
cancel O
di O
certificate O
forgery O
suit O
wey O
APC B-ORG
filed O
against O
Obaseki B-PER
, O
dis O
make O
dem O
affirm O
im O
victory O
in O
di O
September B-DATE
19 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2020 I-DATE
governorship O
election O
in O
di O
state O
. O

As O
im O
dey O
address O
parti O
supporters O
dem O
at O
di O
Benin B-LOC
airport I-LOC
yesterday B-DATE
, O
Obaseki B-PER
tok O
say O
im O
victory O
also O
dey O
for O
freedom O
for O
Edo B-LOC
pipo O
. O

For O
us O
wey O
dey O
inside O
Edo B-LOC
, O
dis O
victory O
means O
freedom O
and O
emancipation O
; O
e O
means O
say O
we O
must O
rededicate O
ourselves O
to O
our O
pipo O
bikos O
democracy O
dey O
all O
about O
di O
pipo O
. O

Democracy O
no O
dey O
for O
individual O
or O
godfather O
. O

We O
don O
already O
defeat O
di O
godfather O
finally O
for O
inside O
Edo B-LOC
, O
so O
we O
fit O
to O
take O
Edo B-LOC
to O
wia O
e O
should O
be O
, O
im O
tok O
. O

Im O
believe O
say O
, O
dey O
don O
go O
through O
plenty O
hurdles O
in O
di O
last O
two O
or O
three B-DATE
years I-DATE
in O
di O
effort O
to O
reposition O
di O
politics O
of O
di O
state O
. O

Inside O
di O
congratulatory O
messages O
by O
di O
candidate O
of O
di O
APC B-ORG
, O
Osagie B-PER
Ize I-PER
- I-PER
Iyamu I-PER
and O
a O
former O
national O
chairman O
of O
the O
parti O
, O
Adams B-PER
Oshiomhole I-PER
to O
im O
, O
Obaseki B-PER
tok O
say O
im O
neva O
receive O
original O
copies O
of O
di O
letterswey O
di O
duo O
sign O
. O

The O
Independent B-ORG
National I-ORG
Electoral I-ORG
Commission I-ORG
( O
INEC B-ORG
) O
for O
Saturday B-DATE
tok O
say O
e O
wan O
convert O
di O
3 O
, O
148 O
Voting O
Points O
( O
VPs O
) O
for O
inside O
Kano B-LOC
State I-LOC
to O
full O
- O
fledged O
Polling O
Units O
( O
PUs O
) O
. O

Im O
talk O
say O
di O
decision O
nah O
to O
help O
decongest O
Pus O
and O
to O
give O
dem O
volters O
a O
healthy O
environment O
wey O
dey O
fit O
exercise O
dia O
civic O
responsibilities O
durring O
election O

Prof O
Shehu B-PER
tok O
say O
, O
There O
bin O
ova O
five O
million O
registered O
voters O
for O
inside O
Kano B-LOC
State I-LOC
, O
with O
8 O
, O
074 O
PUs O
and O
3 O
, O
148 O
VPs O
. O

if O
dem O
approve O
am O
, O
Kano B-LOC
go O
have O
a O
total O
number O
11 O
, O
222 O
pus O
. O

im O
tok O
say O
, O
INEC B-ORG
don O
create O
points O
wia O
pipo O
fit O
Vote O
, O
Baby O
Polling O
Units O
and O
Voting O
Polling O
Settlements O
inside O
PUs O
wit O
voters O
wey O
pass O
500 O
, O
but O
e O
still O
neva O
solve O
di O
hardships O
wey O
voters O
dey O
face O
for O
election O
days O
. O

Di O
INEC B-ORG
REC O
tok O
say O
all O
di O
new O
PUs O
go O
dey O
stationed O
inside O
di O
public O
places O
, O
dem O
don O
add O
dat O
no O
one O
go O
dey O
situated O
for O
individual O
residences O
, O
palaces O
, O
houses O
of O
politicians O
or O
places O
of O
worship O
. O

Okoye B-PER
tok O
say O
, O
di O
last O
time O
INEC B-ORG
created O
new O
Pus O
nah O
for O
1996 B-DATE
wen O
we O
get O
only O
50 O
million O
voters O
wey O
dey O
registered O

But O
for O
2019 B-DATE
, O
di O
number O
don O
increase O
to O
ova O
84 O
million O
. O

Im O
clare O
am O
say O
di O
exercise O
no O
go O
fit O
add O
to O
number O
of O
voters O
wey O
dey O
registered O
. O

Di O
INEC B-ORG
Commissioner O
also O
don O
tok O
, O
wit O
di O
Continuous O
Voter O
Registration O
Exercise O
wey O
go O
begin O
for O
June B-DATE
28 I-DATE
, O
di O
commission O
don O
introduce O
innovation O
wey O
be O
say O
voters O
who O
be O
technology O
guru O
go O
fit O
do O
dia O
registration O
online O
, O
com O
go O
to O
dia O
respective O
registration O
areas O
to O
do O
dia O
biometrics O
and O
pictures O
captured O
. O

Im O
believe O
say O
dis O
go O
reduce O
di O
kin O
crowd O
wey O
go O
dey O
di O
centres O
, O
e O
go O
also O
make O
di O
process O
dey O
easy O
. O

Daily B-ORG
Trust I-ORG
don O
report O
say O
di O
meeting O
wey O
dem O
do O
in O
attendance O
representatives O
of O
political O
parties O
inside O
di O
state O
, O
heads O
of O
all O
security O
agencies O
inside O
di O
state O
, O
traditional O
and O
religious O
leaders O
and O
non O
- O
gomental O
organisations O
. O

As O
part O
of O
di O
processes O
of O
nomination O
of O
di O
All B-ORG
Progressives I-ORG
Congress I-ORG
( O
APC B-ORG
) O
candidates O
wey O
go O
dey O
for O
di O
forthcoming O
Federal B-LOC
Capital I-LOC
Territory I-LOC
( O
FCT B-LOC
) O

Minister O
of O
sports O
, O
Sunday B-PER
Dare I-PER
, O
don O
dey O
honour O
by O
di O
Association B-ORG
of I-ORG
National I-ORG
Olympics I-ORG
Committees I-ORG
of I-ORG
Africa I-ORG
wit O
di O
Highest O
Order O
of O
Sports O
Administrator O
ourrd O
. O

ANOCA B-ORG
President O
, O
Mr O
. O
Mustapha B-PER
Berraf I-PER
wey O
carry O
di O
ourrd O
give O
im O
yesterday B-DATE
inside O
Abuja B-LOC
tok O
say O
nah O
for O
di O
Ministers O
immense O
contributions O
to O
di O
growth O
of O
di O
Olympics O
Movement O
and O
sports O
inside O
Africa B-LOC
. O

Im O
tok O
say O
ANOCA B-ORG
dey O
hapi O
wit O
di O
role O
you O
played O
in O
ensuring O
the O
completion O
of O
our O
headquarters O
in O
Abuja B-LOC
. O

We O
dey O
very O
proud O
for O
wetin O
you O
don O
do O
for O
sport O
Development O
inside O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
Africa B-LOC
. O

We O
present O
dis O
ourrd O
to O
you O
for O
di O
great O
work O
wey O
you O
don O
do O
and O
di O
contributions O
you O
don O
put O
for O
di O
sport O
Development O
. O

We O
dey O
very O
proud O
of O
you O
and O
dey O
look O
forward O
to O
an O
enduring O
relationship O
for O
our O
sports O
wetin O
you O
don O
do O
for O
sports O

Dare B-PER
say O
thanks O
for O
dis O
honour O
and O
ourrd O
wich O
dey O
special O
. O

Some O
leaders O
of O
di O
ruling O
All B-ORG
Progressives I-ORG
Congress I-ORG
( O
APC B-ORG
) O
tok O
say O
di O
President O
Muhammadu B-PER
Buhari I-PER
- O
led O
goment O
don O
record O
plenty O
achievements O
for O
inside O
six B-DATE
years I-DATE
dan O
di O
goment O
wey O
don O
dey O
before O
under O
di O
pipos B-ORG
Democratic I-ORG
parti I-ORG
( O
PDP B-ORG
) O
between O
1999 B-DATE
and O
2015 B-DATE
. O

Dis O
dey O
contain O
inside O
a O
statement O
wey O
di O
former O
National O
Publicity O
Secretary O
of O
the O
APC B-ORG
, O
Mr O
. O
Lanre B-PER
Issa I-PER
- I-PER
Onilu I-PER
sign O
, O
wey O
be O
di O
current O
Chairman O
of O
di O
Progressive B-ORG
Governors I-ORG
Forum I-ORG
( O
PGF B-ORG
) O
, O
Salihu B-PER
Mohammed I-PER
Lukman I-PER
; O
di O
Senior O
Special O
Assistant O
wey O
dey O
for O
National O
Social O
Investment O
Programme O
to O
President O
Buhari B-PER
, O
Barr O
. O

Political O
parti O
dem O
dey O
worry O
ova O
di O
wahala O
of O
insecurity O
