Mixed B-ORG
Martial I-ORG
Arts I-ORG
joinbodi O
, O
Ultimate B-ORG
Fighting I-ORG
Championship I-ORG
, O
UFC B-ORG
don O
decide O
say O
dem O
go O
enta O
back O
di O
octagon O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
, I-DATE
9 I-DATE
May I-DATE
, O
for O
Jacksonville B-LOC
, O
Florida B-LOC
. O

Di O
Florida B-ORG
State I-ORG
Commission I-ORG
say O
dem O
dey O
collabo O
with O
di O
UFC B-ORG
to O
make O
sure O
say O
health O
and O
safety O
protocols O
dey O
ground O
to O
ensure O
say O
evri O
pesin O
wey O
attend O
di O
event O
day O
safe O
. O

UFC B-ORG
presido O
Dana B-PER
White I-PER
tok O
for O
press O
release O
say O
im O
no O
fit O
wait O
to O
bring O
beta O
matches O
dem O
give O
di O
fans O
. O

Di O
matches O
no O
go O
get O
any O
fans O
for O
inside O
di O
stadium O
and O
infact O
na O
only O
essential O
staff O
dem O
go O
dey O
di O
area O
wey O
dem O
go O
fight O
di O
matches O
. O

Di O
mayor O
of O
Jacksonville B-LOC
Mayor O
Lenny B-PER
Curry I-PER
say O
di O
joinbodi O
give O
am O
safe O
plan O
to O
do O
dia O
waka O
. O

So O
far O
, O
di O
UFC B-ORG
don O
schedule O
three O
match O
for O
May B-DATE
9 I-DATE
, O
13 B-DATE
and O
16 B-DATE
for O
dia O
UFC B-ORG
249 O
fighting O
. O

On O
di O
first O
day O
, O
di O
number O
one O
lightweight O
fighter O
Tony B-PER
Ferguson I-PER
go O
face O
number O
four O
Justin B-PER
Gaethje I-PER
, O
for O
di O
UFC B-ORG
banterweight O
Championship O
wia O
Henry B-PER
Cejudo I-PER
dey O
look O
to O
flog O
multiple O
- O
time O
title O
holder O
Dominick B-PER
Cruz I-PER
. O

Di O
return O
of O
di O
UFC B-ORG
dey O
come O
even O
as O
football O
matches O
for O
Europe B-LOC
and O
oda O
parts O
of O
di O
world O
dey O
consider O
to O
return O
. O

German O
league O
, O
Bundesliga O
say O
dem O
go O
restart O
matches O
for O
16 B-DATE
May I-DATE
and O
for O
South B-LOC
Korea I-LOC
live O
league O
football O
games O
don O
already O
start O
. O

Di O
return O
of O
German O
football O
Bundesliga O
competition O
dey O
currently O
under O
discussion O
for O
one O
news O
conference O
wey O
di O
governing O
body O
dey O
hold O
. O

Christian B-PER
Seifert I-PER
, O
di O
CEO O
of O
di O
kontri O
football O
league O
( O
DFL O
) O
, O
don O
express O
hope O
say O
di O
league O
dey O
ready O
to O
return O
on O
9 B-DATE
May I-DATE
and O
dem O
go O
play O
di O
games O
behind O
closed O
doors O
, O
although O
Im O
add O
am O
say O
dem O
go O
need O
di O
approval O
from O
politicians O
. O

He O
tok O
: O
"""" O
Games O
without O
spectators O
no O
be O
wetin O
we O
want O
but O
at O
di O
moment O
na O
di O
only O
thing O
we O
fit O
do O
be O
that O
. O
"""" O

Cooking O
burns O
, O
dog O
bites O
na O
some O
of O
di O
injury O
dem O
wey O
some O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
players O
don O
get O
during O
di O
coronavirus O
lockdown O
. O

Ole B-PER
Gunnar I-PER
Solskjaer I-PER
team O
dey O
train O
for O
dia O
house O
as O
football O
dey O
suspended O
sake O
of O
coronavirus O
pandemic O
. O

United B-ORG
doctor O
Steve B-PER
McNally I-PER
say O
even O
though O
say O
di O
break O
don O
give O
di O
players O
time O
to O
recover O
, O
dem O
dey O
see O
increase O
for O
some O
kain O
funny O
- O
funny O
injuries O
. O

"""" O
Fortunately O
, O
most O
of O
di O
boys O
dey O
well O
and O
we O
no O
get O
any O
real O
issues O
at O
all O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
di O
McNally B-PER
tok O
for O
di O
club O
official O
app O
. O

"""" O
Fortunately O
for O
us O
we O
no O
get O
injuries O
, O
although O
we O
get O
few O
unusual O
complains O
because O
dem O
dey O
try O
to O
cook O
, O
or O
tins O
like O
dia O
dog O
bite O
dem O
, O
dat O
kain O
thing O
. O

"""" O
Di O
nutritionist O
put O
di O
boys O
for O
one O
Instagram O
page O
wia O
dem O
go O
take O
cooking O
lessons O
, O
so O
a O
lot O
of O
dem O
don O
start O
to O
dey O
develop O
new O
skill O
- O
and O
one O
or O
two O
of O
dem O
don O
get O
injury O
. O
"""" O

Even O
though O
dem O
dey O
away O
from O
dia O
training O
base O
for O
Carrington B-LOC
, O
Solskjaer's B-PER
staff O
still O
dey O
monitor O
di O
players O
fitness O
, O
weight O
and O
nutrition O

Bundesliga O
don O
set O
record O
as O
di O
first O
major O
league O
to O
restart O
during O
di O
coronavirus O
pandemic O
and O
for O
millions O
of O
football O
fans O
, O
di O
main O
kweshion O
na O
how O
to O
watch O
di O
matches O
, O
live O
. O

Two O
rival O
clubs O
Dortmund B-ORG
and O
Schalke B-ORG
go O
jam O
inside O
one O
of O
di O
six O
Saturday B-DATE
matches O
wey O
dem O
go O
play O
for O
stadium O
wey O
no O
get O
fans O
inside O
. O

If O
dem O
win O
, O
Dortmund B-ORG
go O
close O
reduce O
to O
one O
point O
di O
gap O
wey O
Bayern B-ORG
dey O
give O
dem O
. O

Bayern B-ORG
Munich I-ORG
dey O
play O
on O
Sunday B-DATE
, I-DATE
17 I-DATE
May I-DATE
. O

Popular O
cable O
satellite O
broadcaster O
DsTV B-ORG
, O
no O
get O
right O
to O
Bundesliga O
live O
matches O
for O
di O
2019 B-DATE
/ I-DATE
2020 I-DATE
season O
so O
na O
pipo O
wey O
get O
StarTimes B-ORG
dey O
in O
luck O
because O
na O
dem O
get O
broadcast O
rights O
for O
Sub B-LOC
- I-LOC
Saharan I-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

In O
fact O
, O
di O
only O
kontris O
for O
Africa B-LOC
wey O
StarTimes B-ORG
no O
cover O
na O
Algeria B-LOC
, O
Morocco B-LOC
, O
Libya B-LOC
and O
Tunisia B-LOC
Meanwhile O
BetWay B-ORG
wey O
be O
sports O
betting O
website O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
tweet O
say O
all O
dia O
customers O
fit O
watch O
di O
matches O
live O
ontop O
dia O
website O
. O

Whichever O
way O
wey O
you O
watch O
just O
know O
say O
you O
dey O
part O
of O
one O
billion O
pipo O
wey O
Bayern B-ORG
CEO O
Karl B-PER
- I-PER
Heinz I-PER
Rummenigge I-PER
don O
gauge O
say O
go O
watch O
dis O
weekend B-DATE
live O
matches O
See O
Saturday B-DATE
games O
. O

SATURDAY B-DATE
16TH I-DATE
MAY I-DATE
2020 I-DATE
B B-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG
14 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
Schalke B-ORG
Augsburg I-ORG
14 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
Wolfsburg B-ORG
Düsseldorf I-ORG
14 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
Paderborn B-ORG
RB I-ORG
Leipzig I-ORG
14 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
Freiburg B-ORG
Hoffenheim I-ORG
14 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
Hertha B-ORG
Berlin I-ORG
Frankfurt I-ORG
17 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
B B-ORG
Mgladbach I-ORG

Two B-DATE
long I-DATE
months I-DATE
don O
reach O
now O
since O
football O
fans O
last O
see O
major O
league O
match O
live O
. O

By O
now O
, O
Liverpool B-ORG
suppose O
don O
carry O
cup O
as O
di O
Premier O
League O
champions O
for O
di O
first O
time O
in O
dia O
history O
, O
we O
go O
don O
know O
how O
di O
Barcelona B-ORG
and O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
fight O
to O
be O
number O
1 O
take O
end O
, O
and O
Europe B-LOC
go O
don O
ready O
for O
Euro O
2020 B-DATE
. O

If O
no O
be O
for O
di O
break O
wey O
Coronavirus O
cause O
. O

But O
tins O
don O
dey O
pick O
up O
across O
Europe B-LOC
now O
, O
as O
kontris O
don O
decide O
to O
find O
way O
to O
finish O
di O
season O
of O
dia O
top O
divisions O
, O
although O
e O
go O
come O
with O
conditions O
. O

Make O
we O
torchlight O
who O
don O
ready O
, O
when O
dem O
go O
restart O
and O
di O
conditions O
wey O
dey O
ground O
. O

Germany B-LOC
top O
football O
league O
- O
Bundesliga O
- O
don O
confam O
say O
football O
action O
go O
return O
on O
16 B-DATE
May I-DATE
, O
as O
dem O
go O
become O
di O
first O
major O
football O
league O
to O
restart O
afta O
di O
coronavirus O
lockdown O
. O

Di O
kontri O
Chancellor O
Angela B-PER
Merkel I-PER
say O
di O
goment O
bin O
approve O
di O
plan O
although O
restrictions O
go O
dey O
. O

Conditions O
Di O
Premier O
League O
, O
wey O
be O
di O
league O
wey O
football O
fans O
dey O
watch O
pass O
for O
di O
world O
no O
go O
resume O
anytime O
before O
1 B-DATE
June I-DATE
, O
afta O
di O
British O
goment O
on O
Monday B-DATE
comot O
to O
say O
no O
sport O
event O
fit O
hold O
in O
di O
kontri O
before O
dis O
date O
. O

Conditions O
Spain B-LOC
top O
league O
and O
working O
place O
of O
Lionel B-PER
Messi I-PER
dey O
torchlight O
June B-DATE
12 I-DATE
as O
di O
date O
when O
dem O
go O
resume O
di O
season O
. O

Conditions O
Di O
french O
league O
bin O
cancel O
dia O
current O
season O
for O
April B-DATE
, O
say O
whichever O
position O
club O
dey O
for O
table O
, O
na O
final O
. O

Dis O
don O
vex O
some O
clubs O
wey O
dey O
bottom O
and O
di O
mata O
don O
even O
turn O
to O
court O
mata O
. O

Italy B-LOC
never O
decide O
how O
dem O
go O
do O
dia O
own O
top O
league O
but O
some O
clubs O
don O
return O
to O
training O
. O

So O
maybe O
dem O
go O
soon O
announce O
dia O
own O
date O
. O

Game O
of O
Thrones O
actor O
, O
Hafthor B-PER
Bjornsson I-PER
don O
set O
world O
deadlifting O
record O
as O
im O
lift O
501kg O
( O
1 O
, O
104lb O
) O
. O

Bjornsson B-PER
, O
wey O
be O
powerlifter O
play O
di O
role O
of O
Ser O
Gregor O
"""" O
Di O
Mountain O
"""" O
Clegane O
for O
di O
HBO B-ORG
series O
, O
break O
di O
record O
for O
Im O
own O
gym O
for O
Im O
hometown O
, O
Iceland B-LOC
. O

He O
lift O
di O
barbell O
for O
two B-DATE
seconds I-DATE
, O
before O
im O
drop O
drop O
di O
weights O
. O

Na O
sports O
broadcaster O
ESPN B-ORG
stream O
di O
event O
and O
dem O
film O
am O
for O
Bjornsson's B-PER
YouTube O
channel O
. O

Bjornsson B-PER
, O
wey O
be O
2 O
. O
05m O
tall O
( O
6ft O
9in O
) O
, O
bin O
win O
di O
World O
Strongest O
Man O
competition O
for O
2018 B-DATE
. O

As O
im O
dey O
tok O
for O
di O
"""" O
behind O
- O
di O
- O
scenes O
"""" O
video O
wey O
Im O
post O
for O
YouTube O
, O
Bjornsson B-PER
say O
: O
"""" O
I O
dey O
extremely O
proud O
, O
you O
know O
. O

I O
dey O
extremely O
happy O
. O

"""" O
E O
dey O
great O
- O
nothing O
better O
pass O
make O
you O
prove O
pipo O
wrong O
. O

so O
many O
pipo O
don O
tok O
say O
, O
'501kg O
no O
go O
ever O
go O
up' O
. O
. O
. O

But O
I O
also O
get O
plenti O
support O
. O
"""" O

He O
add O
am O
: O
"""" O
I O
feel O
healthy O
, O
I O
feel O
god O
. O

I O
just O
dey O
speechless O
, O
even O
though O
I O
dey O
talk O
too O
much O
now O
, O
But O
I O
dey O
happy O
- O
Dis O
na O
big O
deal O
for O
me O
Na O
Eddie B-PER
Hall I-PER
, O
one O
British O
man O
who O
become O
di O
first O

Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
and O
Nigerian O
striker O
Odion B-PER
Ighalo I-PER
dey O
among O
di O
richest O
players O
wey O
dey O
30 B-DATE
years I-DATE
and O
below O
. O

Ighalo B-PER
wey O
join O
United B-ORG
on O
loan O
from O
China B-LOC
club O
Shanghai B-ORG
Shenhua I-ORG
dey O
15th O
for O
di O
2020 B-DATE
Sunday B-ORG
Times I-ORG
Rich O
List O
. O

Di O
Nigerian O
wey O
go O
turn O
31 B-DATE
for O
June B-DATE
na O
di O
only O
African O
player O
wey O
make O
di O
list O
as O
im O
dey O
valued O
at O
£ O
18m O
. O

Nigerian O
born O
British O
boxer O
Anthony B-PER
Joshua I-PER
dey O
number O
two O
position O
for O
di O
list O
and O
im O
be O
di O
only O
pesin O
wey O
no O
dey O
play O
football O
wey O
make O
di O
list O
. O

Joshua B-PER
worth O
£ O
107m O
according O
to O
Sunday B-ORG
Times I-ORG
and O
e O
make O
majority O
of O
im O
money O
from O
di O
two O
fights O
against O
Andy B-PER
Ruiz I-PER
Jnr I-PER
. O

Top O
of O
di O
list O
of O
sports O
stars O
wey O
dey O
30 B-DATE
years I-DATE
and O
below O
na O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
player O
, O
Gareth B-PER
Bale I-PER
, O
wey O
dey O
valued O
at O
£ O
114m O
. O

Aside O
Ighalo B-PER
, O
four O
other O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
players O
including O
: O
Paul B-PER
Pogba I-PER
, O
Davide B-PER
de I-PER
Gea I-PER
, O
Anthony B-PER
Martial I-PER
and O
Luke B-PER
Shaw I-PER
make O
di O
18 O
- O
man O
list O
. O

Di O
Ligue O
1 O
and O
Ligue O
2 O
seasons O
no O
go O
resume O
afta O
France B-LOC
don O
ban O
all O
sporting O
events O
, O
plus O
di O
one O
wey O
dem O
wan O
do O
behind O
closed O
doors O
, O
until O
September B-DATE
. O

Prime O
Minister O
Edouard B-PER
Philippe I-PER
tok O
say O
di O
2019 B-DATE
- I-DATE
20 I-DATE
sporting O
season O
don O
dey O
over O
as O
im O
announce O
plans O
to O
ease O
France B-LOC
coronavirus O
lockdown O
on O
11 B-DATE
May I-DATE
. O

French O
football O
goment O
join O
- O
bodi O
bin O
dey O
hope O
to O
resume O
di O
season O
on O
17 B-DATE
June I-DATE
and O
finish O
di O
campaign O
on O
25 B-DATE
July I-DATE
. O

Dem O
bin O
suspend O
football O
unti O
further O
notice O
for O
France B-LOC
on O
13 B-DATE
March I-DATE
. O

We O
neva O
know O
weda O
Ligue B-ORG
de I-ORG
Football I-ORG
Professional I-ORG
( O
LFP B-ORG
) O
go O
choose O
to O
abandon O
di O
season O
without O
promotion O
or O
relegation O
and O
no O
champions O
or O
dem O
go O
base O
di O
outcome O
of O
di O
campaign O
on O
current O
standings O
. O

Defending O
champions O
Paris B-ORG
St I-ORG
- I-ORG
Germain I-ORG
dey O
12 O
points O
clear O
of O
Marseille B-ORG
for O
di O
top O
of O
Ligue O
1 O
, O
wit O
10 O
rounds O
of O
matches O
and O
one O
outstanding O
fixture O
wey O
remain O
to O
play O
. O

Toulouse B-ORG
dey O
bottom O
of O
di O
table O
, O
17 O
points O
from O
safety O
, O
and O
10 O
points O
behind O
Amiens B-ORG
. O

Nimes B-ORG
na O
18th O
and O
dem O
dey O
relegation O
play O
- O
off O
spot O
, O
three O
points O
behind O
St B-ORG
Etienne I-ORG
wey O
dey O
17th O
position O
. O

Di O
top O
five O
sides O
for O
Ligue O
2 O
dey O
separated O
by O
just O
four O
points O
, O
with O
Lorient B-ORG
and O
Lens B-ORG
currently O
dey O
occupy O
di O
automatic O
promotion O
spots O
. O

Di O
LFP B-ORG
bin O
meet O
10 B-DATE
of I-DATE
April I-DATE
and O
dem O
vote O
to O
resume O
di O
Ligue O
1 O
season O
. O

However O
, O
Philippe B-PER
tok O
say O
: O
"""" O
Di O
2019 B-DATE
- I-DATE
20 I-DATE
season O
of O
professional O
sports O
, O
including O
football O
, O
no O
go O
fit O
resume O
. O

"""" O
E O
go O
dey O
possible O
, O
on O
sunny O
days O
, O
to O
practice O
individual O
sporting O
activity O
outdoors O
, O
as O
dem O
go O
respect O
di O
rules O
of O
social O
distancing O
. O

"""" O
E O
no O
go O
dey O
possible O
, O
whether O
to O
practice O
sport O
for O
covered O
places O
, O
nor O
team O
or O
contact O
sports O
. O
"""" O

European O
leagues O
get O
until O
25 B-DATE
May I-DATE
to O
tell O
European O
football O
goment O
join O
- O
bodi O
Uefa B-ORG
weda O
dem O
wan O
complete O
or O
cancel O
dia O
seasons O
. O

Dem O
abandon O
di O
Dutch O
top O
flight O
on O
Friday B-DATE
wit O
no O
promotion O
or O
relegation O
and O
no O
champions O
, O
and O
on O
Monday B-DATE
Belgian O
clubs O
postpone O
di O
vote O
to O
confam O
weda O
dem O
go O
cancel O
dia O
top O
flight O
till O
next B-DATE
week I-DATE
. O

Di O
head O
of O
di O
Dutch B-ORG
FA I-ORG
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
say O
im O
tink O
say O
e O
dey O
"""" O
very O
doubtful O
"""" O
say O
Premier O
League O
go O
fit O
complete O
di O
2019 B-DATE
- I-DATE
20 I-DATE
campaign O
. O

Uefa B-ORG
don O
tok O
say O
dem O
go O
use O
on O
- O
field O
performance O
to O
determine O
which O
clubs O
go O
make O
up O
di O
next O
season O
European O
club O
competitions O
. O

If O
dem O
no O
fit O
finish O
, O
e O
mean O
say O
national O
associations O
go O
need O
select O
di O
clubs O
to O
qualify O
for O
Europe B-LOC
. O

Na O
30 O
match O
balls O
, O
each O
of O
dem O
, O
ball O
boys O
go O
disinfect O
am O
and O
keep O
for O
special O
spots O
rather O
than O
handing O
am O
over O
to O
players O
. O

Dis O
na O
one O
of O
di O
many O
tins O
wey O
go O
change O
for O
football O
reality O
sake O
of O
Coronavirus O
. O

German O
Bundesliga O
action O
go O
continue O
on O
Sunday B-DATE
as O
league O
leaders O
Bayern B-ORG
Munich I-ORG
face O
Union B-ORG
Berlin I-ORG
later O
. O

But O
di O
first O
match O
go O
be O
Köln B-ORG
vs O
Mainz B-ORG
by O
2 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30pm I-DATE
Sunday I-DATE
. O

And O
like O
Saturday B-DATE
, O
clubs O
fit O
substitute O
pass O
3 O
players O
up O
to O
5 O
maximum O
- O
anoda O
changes O
to O
di O
round O
leather O
game O
. O

Substitutes O
all O
sidon O
for O
dia O
lane O
wit O
enof O
space O
from O
each O
oda O
and O
wear O
masks O
. O

Dis O
screen O
inside O
di O
stadium O
for O
RB B-ORG
Leipzig I-ORG
tell O
pipo O
to O
wash O
dia O
hands O
. O

Add O
to O
empty O
stadium O
, O
some O
goals O
na O
social O
- O
distancing O
alias O
dey O
your O
lane O
dem O
use O
celebrate O
. O

On O
Saturday B-DATE
, O
Borussia B-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG
players O
run O
to O
go O
celebrate O
in O
front O
of O
di O
empty O
South O
Bank O
RB B-ORG
Leipzig I-ORG
striker O
Yussuf B-PER
Poulsen I-PER
na O
from O
a O
safe O
distance O
fit O
stay O
interview O
am O
sake O
of O
corona O
. O

Police O
make O
sure O
say O
fans O
no O
gada O
outside O
. O

Uefa B-ORG
don O
call O
emergency O
meeting O
for O
Tuesday B-DATE
wia O
dem O
go O
discuss O
di O
possibility O
of O
postponing O
Euro O
2020 B-DATE
by O
one B-DATE
year I-DATE
. O

European O
football O
governing O
body O
go O
hold O
video O
conference O
meetings O
to O
discuss O
dia O
response O
to O
di O
coronavirus O
outbreak O
. O

Discussions O
go O
cover O
all O
domestic O
and O
European O
competitions O
, O
including O
Euro O
2020 B-DATE
. O

Euro O
2020 B-DATE
suppose O
take O
place O
from O
12 B-DATE
June I-DATE
- I-DATE
12 I-DATE
July I-DATE
for O
venues O
all O
ova O
Europe B-LOC
. O

Uefa B-ORG
don O
invite O
representatives O
of O
dia O
55 O
member O
associations O
, O
plus O
di O
boards O
of O
di O
European B-ORG
Club I-ORG
Association I-ORG
, O
di O
European O
leagues O
and O
representative O
of O
world O
player O
union O
Fifpro B-ORG
. O

Meanwhile O
, O
dem O
don O
postpone O
di O
second O
leg O
of O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
last O
- O
16 O
second O
leg O
Champions O
League O
tie O
against O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
, O
wey O
dem O
wan O
play O
on O
Tuesday B-DATE
17 I-DATE
March I-DATE
. O

La O
Liga O
don O
also O
suspend O
dia O
league O
for O
at O
least O
di O
next O
two O
rounds O
of O
matches O
"""" O
sake O
of O
say O
dem O
quarantine O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
squad O
because O
of O
coronavirus O
. O

In O
addition O
, O
Danish B-ORG
Football I-ORG
Association I-ORG
don O
cancel O
all O
football O
activities O
for O
di O
kontri O
for O
two B-DATE
weeks I-DATE
while O
di O
Netherlands' B-LOC
Eredivisie O
don O
dey O
suspended O
until O
31 B-DATE
March I-DATE
. O

For O
Italy B-LOC
, O
Serie O
A O
dey O
suspended O
until O
3 B-DATE
April I-DATE
, O
and O
di O
kontri O
dey O
on O
lockdown O
. O

Two O
players O
- O
Juventus' B-ORG
Daniele B-PER
Rugani I-PER
and O
Sampdoria's B-ORG
Manolo B-PER
Gabbiadini I-PER
- O
test O
positive O
to O
coronavirus O
. O

Football O
fans O
dey O
use O
Liverpool B-ORG
do O
yeye O
for O
social O
media O
with O
funny O
- O
funny O
comments O
and O
memes O
afta O
dem O
crash O
out O
for O
Champions O
League O
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

Liverpool B-ORG
wey O
be O
di O
defending O
champions O
lose O
3 O
- O
2 O
to O
Atletico B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
for O
Anfield B-LOC
and O
4 O
- O
2 O
on O
aggregate O
for O
dia O
round O
of O
16 O
second O
leg O
match O
. O

Di O
first O
leg O
wey O
dem O
play O
for O
Atletico B-ORG
house O
for O
Spain B-LOC
end O
1 O
- O
0 O
. O

Jurgen B-PER
Klopp I-PER
team O
start O
di O
second O
leg O
well O
, O
dem O
put O
di O
Spanish O
team O
under O
pressure O
for O
di O
first O
90 B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
of O
di O
match O
and O
di O
pressure O
pay O
off O
with O
goal O
from O
Georginio B-PER
Wijnaldum I-PER
for O
first O
- O
half O
. O

For O
extra O
time O
Roberto B-PER
Firmino I-PER
score O
to O
make O
am O
2 O
- O
0 O
but O
di O
lead O
no O
last O
long O
. O

Two O
quick O
goals O
from O
Atletico B-ORG
substitute O
Marcos B-PER
Llorente I-PER
change O
di O
game O
before O
Alvaro B-PER
Morata I-PER
score O
for O
injury O
time O
to O
add O
insult O
to O
injury O
to O
send O
im O
team O
to O
di O
last O
eight O
of O
di O
competition O
. O

Many O
football O
fans O
no O
waste O
time O
to O
yab O
Liverpool B-ORG
wey O
don O
win O
dis O
competition O
six O
times O
for O
social O
media O
. O

See O
some O
of O
di O
funny O
memes O
and O
comments O
Di O
Reds O
go O
now O
focus O
dia O
attention O
on O
winning O
di O
Premier O
League O
title O
, O
dem O
dey O
gap O
second O
position O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
with O
25 O
points O
with O
nine O
games O
to O
go O
. O

Already O
dis O
season O
dem O
don O
win O
di O
Uefa B-ORG
Super O
Cup O
and O
di O
Club O
World O
Cup O
title O
. O

Di O
organisers O
of O
di O
Tokyo B-LOC
2020 B-DATE
Olympic O
Games O
, O
wey O
suppose O
start O
on O
24 B-DATE
July I-DATE
, O
don O
agree O
to O
postpone O
di O
event O
for O
one B-DATE
year I-DATE
sake O
of O
di O
coronavirus O
. O

Japan's B-LOC
Prime O
Minister O
Shinzo B-PER
Abe I-PER
say O
di O
International B-ORG
Olympic I-ORG
Committee I-ORG
don O
agree O
to O
di O
delay O
. O

"""" O
I O
proposed O
to O
postpone O
for O
one B-DATE
year I-DATE
and O
[ O
IOC B-ORG
] O
president O
Thomas B-PER
Bach I-PER
don O
give O
100 O
% O
support O
, O
"""" O
Im O
tok O
. O

Di O
one B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
delay O
go O
also O
apply O
to O
di O
Tokyo B-LOC
Paralympic O
Games O
. O

Prime O
Minister O
Abe B-PER
add O
: O
"""" O
Dis O
go O
make O
am O
possible O
for O
athletes O
to O
play O
in O
di O
best O
condition O
, O
and O
will O
make O
di O
event O
a O
safe O
and O
secure O
place O
for O
spectators O
. O
"""" O

Di O
agreement O
come O
as O
di O
British B-ORG
Olympic I-ORG
Association I-ORG
( O
BOA B-ORG
) O
dey O
meet O
for O
Tuesday B-DATE
to O
discuss O
di O
matter O
. O

BOA B-ORG
chairman O
Hugh B-PER
Robertson I-PER
don O
already O
say O
Great B-LOC
Britain I-LOC
dey O
unlikely O
to O
send O
team O
to O
Tokyo B-LOC
for O
dis O
summer B-DATE
. O

Nigeria B-ORG
Football I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
and O
di O
League B-ORG
Management I-ORG
Company I-ORG
dey O
mourn O
di O
death O
of O
Nasarawa B-ORG
United I-ORG
defender O
Chineme B-PER
Martins I-PER
wey O
die O
during O
dia O
league O
match O
against O
Katsina B-ORG
United I-ORG
for O
Lafia B-LOC
on O
Sunday B-DATE
. O

For O
inside O
statement O
LMC B-ORG
chairman O
, O
Shehu B-PER
Dikko I-PER
, O
tell O
di O
late O
player O
family O
and O
im O
club O
sorry O
. O

Im O
add O
say O
"""" O
LMC B-ORG
expect O
to O
get O
standard O
autopsy O
to O
find O
out O
di O
cause O
of O
di O
player O
death O
. O

Di O
Nigeria B-ORG
football I-ORG
federation I-ORG
say O
dem O
dey O
sad O
about O
di O
player O
death O
. O

Tori O
be O
say O
Martins B-PER
collapse O
for O
inside O
di O
43 B-DATE
minute I-DATE
of O
di O
match O
and O
medical O
officers O
from O
di O
two O
clubs O
attend O
to O
am O
for O
pitch O
before O
dem O
rush O
am O
go O
Dalhatu B-ORG
Araf I-ORG
Specialist I-ORG
Hospital I-ORG
, O
Lafia B-LOC
wia O
dem O
confam O
say O
im O
don O
die O
. O

Nasarawa B-ORG
United I-ORG
go O
on O
to O
win O
di O
match O
3 O
- O
0 O
, O
Chinedum B-PER
Ohanachom I-PER
score O
hat O
trick O
for O
di O
game O
. O

Di O
result O
mean O
say O
dem O
dey O
13 O
position O
for O
table O
with O
28 O
points O
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
international O
striker O
Ifeanyi B-PER
George I-PER
don O
die O
for O
motor O
accident O
at O
di O
age B-DATE
of I-DATE
26 I-DATE
. O

George B-PER
, O
wey O
get O
two O
caps O
for O
di O
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
, O
dey O
involved O
for O
one O
accident O
wey O
happun O
for O
Benin B-LOC
- I-LOC
Agbor I-LOC
road I-LOC
wen O
im O
dey O
travel O
to O
Lagos B-LOC
on O
Sunday B-DATE
morning I-DATE
. O

Two O
oda O
passengers O
dey O
inside O
di O
26 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
striker O
car O
- O
anoda O
player O
from O
George B-PER
club O
side O
Enugu B-ORG
Rangers I-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
and O
dia O
friend O
. O

Dem O
don O
confam O
di O
condition O
of O
both O
of O
dem O
. O

Di O
players O
bin O
dey O
travel O
from O
Enugu B-LOC
, O
east B-LOC
of I-LOC
di I-LOC
kontri I-LOC
to O
Lagos B-LOC
, O
south B-LOC
west I-LOC
of I-LOC
di I-LOC
kontri I-LOC
sake O
of O
di O
break O
wey O
dem O
get O
for O
di O
Nigerian O
league O
on O
Friday B-DATE
20 I-DATE
March I-DATE
, I-DATE
2020 I-DATE
sake O
of O
coronavirus O
pandemic O
. O

British O
- O
Nigeria B-LOC
heavyweight O
, O
Anthony B-PER
Joshua I-PER
fight O
against O
Bulgaria B-LOC
Kubrat B-PER
Pulev I-PER
to O
defend O
im O
IBF O
, O
WBA O
, O
WBO O
and O
IBO O
world O
titles O
don O
march O
break O
till O
further O
notice O
. O

Di O
fight O
bin O
suppose O
hold O
for O
Tottenham B-LOC
Hotspur I-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
, I-DATE
20 I-DATE
June I-DATE
. O

Dem O
bin O
postpone O
di O
fight O
on O
top O
di O
coronavirus O
palava O
for O
world O
. O

Dis O
dey O
come O
from O
statement O
from O
Joshua B-PER
promoter O
Matchroom B-ORG
Boxing I-ORG
wey O
tok O
say O
dem O
dey O
work O
on O
new O
date O
for O
di O
fight O
. O

Joshua B-PER
neva O
fight O
since O
December B-DATE
wen O
im O
win O
di O
fight O
against O
Andy B-PER
Ruiz I-PER
Jr I-PER
for O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
to O
collect O
back O
im O
belts O
wey O
di O
Mexican O
- O
American O
bin O
collect O
for O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC
wen O
dem O
first O
fight O
for O
June B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
. O

Pulev B-PER
na O
compulsory O
fight O
for O
Joshua B-PER
IBF O
belt O
. O

Im O
bin O
suppose O
fight O
Joshua B-PER
for O
October B-DATE
2017 I-DATE
but O
n O
fit O
do O
am O
because O
of O
sholder O
injury O
. O

Di O
British B-ORG
Boxing I-ORG
Board I-ORG
of I-ORG
Control I-ORG
bin O
suspend O
all O
di O
fights O
under O
them O
until O
di O
end O
of O
May B-DATE
ontop O
di O
coronavirus O
. O

Di O
President O
of O
Gabon B-ORG
football I-ORG
federation I-ORG
Pierre B-PER
Alain I-PER
Mounguengui I-PER
, O
don O
advise O
Pierre B-PER
- I-PER
Emmerick I-PER
Aubamayeng I-PER
to O
comot O
Arsenal B-ORG
because O
im O
no O
go O
win O
anything O
dia O
. O

Aubamayeng B-PER
wey O
be O
Arsenal B-ORG
captain O
don O
build O
reputation O
as O
one O
of O
di O
world O
ogbonge O
forwards O
since O
im O
join O
from O
Borussia B-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG
for O
January B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
, O
and O
im O
next O
Premier O
League O
goal O
go O
be O
im O
50th O
for O
di O
competition O
. O

But O
e O
never O
fit O
help O
di O
Gunners B-ORG
to O
win O
anything O
during O
im O
time O
for O
the O
club O
, O
except O
for O
runners O
- O
up O
medals O
for O
Carabao O
Cup O
and O
Europa O
League O
. O

"""" O
I O
no O
wan O
say O
Arsenal B-ORG
no O
dey O
ginger O
, O
but O
Arsenal B-ORG
no O
get O
ambitions O
wey O
high O
as O
some O
oda O
clubs O
as O
far O
as O
Europe B-LOC
dey O
concerned O
, O
"""" O
President O
Mounguengui B-PER
tell O
ESPN B-ORG
. O

"""" O
So O
, O
if O
Pierre B-PER
fit O
get O
contract O
with O
anoda O
club O
wey O
dey O
more O
ambitious O
club O
, O
he O
go O
definitely O
find O
im O
place O
dia O
. O

"""" O
On O
individual O
level O
, O
all O
of O
us O
sabi O
say O
im O
dey O
among O
di O
best O
players O
for O
di O
world O
. O

"""" O
But O
the O
advice O
I O
give O
am O
na O
to O
continue O
to O
work O
and O
to O
attract O
di O
attention O
of O
di O
biggest O
clubs O
and O
di O
most O
ambitious O
clubs O
. O
"""" O

No O
be O
only O
Mounguengui B-PER
get O
dis O
belief O
, O
- O
even O
Arsenal B-ORG
legend O
Ian B-PER
Wright I-PER
tok O
say O
Aubameyang B-PER
fit O
dey O
play O
at O
a O
higher O
level O
. O

Wright B-PER
tell O
Premier O
League O
Productions O
: O
"""" O
If O
you O
fit O
imagine O
am O
in O
a O
better O
team O
, O
he O
go O
dey O
be O
win O
Premier O
Leagues O
and O
dey O
ginger O
for O
place O
forChampions O
League O
finals O
and O
I O
think O
say O
im O
deserve O
am O
"""" O
You O
no O
dey O
see O
am O
dey O
shout O
for O
pitch O
, O
[ O
no O
] O
dey O
point O
and O
scream O
, O
but O
na O
wetin O
im O
dey O
do O
in O
respect O
of O
im O
leadership O
with O
di O
goals O
wey O
im O
dey O
score O
. O

"""" O
If O
you O
comot O
di O
goals O
out O
of O
dat O
team O
dendem O
dey O
for O
correct O
trouble O
. O
"""" O

Im O
tok O
. O

Everton B-ORG
boss O
Carlo B-PER
Ancelotti I-PER
don O
tok O
say O
e O
go O
be O
emotional O
moment O
for O
am O
as O
e O
dey O
face O
Chelsea B-ORG
today B-DATE
for O
Stamford B-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
. O

Di O
Italian O
spend O
two B-DATE
seasons I-DATE
for O
Chelsea B-ORG
, O
wia O
im O
win O
di O
Premier O
League O
and O
FA B-ORG
Cup O
Double O
in O
2009 B-DATE
- I-DATE
10 I-DATE
. O

Dem O
sack O
am O
afta O
e O
finish O
second O
for O
di O
league O
in O
2010 B-DATE
- I-DATE
11 I-DATE
. O

Today B-DATE
game O
go O
pit O
Ancelotti B-PER
against O
Chelsea B-ORG
manager O
Frank B-PER
Lampard I-PER
, O
who O
play O
under O
the O
60 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
man O
when O
e O
dey O
Stamford B-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
. O

Oga O
Ancelotti B-PER
neva O
face O
Chelsea B-ORG
wey O
im O
manage O
between O
2009 B-DATE
and O
2011 B-DATE
before O
. O

Since O
Ancelotti B-PER
first O
game O
on O
Boxing B-DATE
Day I-DATE
as O
Everton B-ORG
oga O
, O
only O
Liverpool B-ORG
( O
30 O
) O
and O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
( O
19 O
) O
don O
win O
more O
Premier O
League O
points O
. O

Everton B-ORG
don O
score O
in O
all O
10 O
of O
dia O
league O
games O
under O
the O
Italian O
- O
di O
current O
longest O
scoring O
run O
for O
di O
division O
. O

Israel B-PER
Adesanya I-PER
na O
still O
di O
middleweight O
champion O
afta O
e O
defeat O
Yoel B-PER
Romero I-PER
for O
fight O
wey O
many O
dey O
say O
e O
no O
sweet O
. O

For O
di O
UFC B-ORG
248 O
event O
, O
di O
two O
fighters O
wey O
dey O
undefeated O
before O
dis O
match O
bin O
dey O
hope O
to O
go O
back O
house O
with O
di O
middleweight O
belt O
. O

By O
unanimous O
decision O
by O
di O
judges O
declare O
say O
na O
di O
Nigerian O
- O
born O
Israel B-PER
, O
na O
im O
fight O
pass O
on O
di O
night B-DATE
. O

Afta O
round O
5 O
di O
judges O
drop O
scores O
of O
49 O
- O
46 O
, O
48 O
- O
47 O
, O
48 O
- O
47 O
wey O
make O
Romero B-PER
para O
and O
later O
complain O
about O
. O

Di O
fight O
wey O
many O
sabi O
pipo O
say O
no O
two O
sweet O
to O
watch O
, O
bin O
happun O
for O
di O
T B-LOC
- I-LOC
Mobile I-LOC
Arena I-LOC
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
, O
American O
early O
mor O
mor O
on O
Sunday B-DATE
. O

Israel B-PER
Adesanya I-PER
wey O
im O
nickname O
na O
Stylebender B-PER
, O
dey O
represent O
New B-LOC
Zealand I-LOC
wey O
be O
di O
kontri O
im O
parents O
migrate O
to O
. O

British O
world O
champion O
Anthony B-PER
Joshua I-PER
go O
fight O
Kubrat B-PER
Pulev I-PER
for O
Tottenham B-LOC
Hotspur I-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
20 I-DATE
June I-DATE
. O

Pulev B-PER
wey O
be O
38 B-DATE
years I-DATE
, O
come O
from O
Bulgaria B-LOC
and O
na O
him O
IBF O
, O
wey O
be O
boxing O
join O
- O
body O
say O
Joshua B-PER
wey O
get O
di O
WBA O
, O
IBF O
and O
WBO O
titles O
must O
fight O
. O

Joshua B-PER
win O
im O
belts O
back O
with O
points O
victory O
over O
Andy B-PER
Ruiz I-PER
Jr I-PER
. O
for O
December B-DATE
. O

"""" O
I O
dey O
very O
happy O
to O
get O
dis O
opportunity O
to O
show O
di O
world O
how O
strong O
I O
dey O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Pulev B-PER
tok O
. O

Dis O
go O
be O
Joshua B-PER
first O
fight O
for O
UK B-LOC
since O
im O
beat O
Alexander B-PER
Povetkin I-PER
for O
Wembley B-LOC
for O
September B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
. O

Im O
bin O
suppose O
fight O
Pulev B-PER
for O
Cardiff B-LOC
Principality I-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
for O
October B-DATE
2017 I-DATE
but O
di O
fight O
no O
happun O
Di O
Bulgarian O
withdraw O
after O
im O
get O
shoulder O
injury O
during O
training O
alias O
sparring O
, O
Carlos B-PER
Takam I-PER
gatzs O
step O
up O
to O
replace O
am O
with O
just O
12 B-DATE
days' I-DATE
notice O
. O

Last B-DATE
week I-DATE
, O
Joshua B-PER
promoter O
Eddie B-PER
Hearn I-PER
tok O
say O
tok O
- O
tok O
dey O
go O
on O
for O
di O
all O
- O
British O
unification O
fight O
between O
Joshua B-PER
and O
Tyson B-PER
Fury I-PER
. O

Fury B-PER
beat O
Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
to O
collect O
di O
WBC O
title O
last B-DATE
month I-DATE
, O
e O
mean O
say O
na O
British O
heavyweights O
hold O
all O
di O
belts O
dem O
for O
di O
division O
. O

But O
Wilder B-PER
wey O
be O
American O
do O
use O
di O
rematch O
clause O
, O
wey O
mean O
say O
Fury B-PER
vs O
Wilder B-PER
part O
three O
go O
happun O
before O
Fury B-PER
and O
Joshua B-PER
go O
fight O
. O

Pulev B-PER
, O
na O
former O
European O
heavyweight O
champion O
. O

Di O
Bulgaria B-LOC
don O
lose O
once O
for O
im O
29 O
fights O
. O

Wladimir B-PER
Klitschko I-PER
knockout O
for O
fifth O
round O
for O
November B-DATE
2015 I-DATE
. O

For O
2015 B-DATE
, O
im O
beat O
Britain B-LOC
Hughie B-PER
Fury I-PER
on O
points O
for O
IBF O
final O
eliminator O
for O
Bulgaria B-LOC
for O
October B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
, O
im O
first O
fight O
since O
im O
pull O
out O
of O
im O
original O
meeting O
with O
Joshua B-PER
. O

Im O
last O
fight O
, O
im O
win O
with O
unanimous O
points O
victory O
, O
against O
American O
Rydell B-PER
Booker I-PER
, O
for O
November B-DATE
. O

Di O
family O
of O
di O
football O
star O
Kazeem B-PER
Tiamiyu I-PER
wey O
die O
for O
Sagamu B-LOC
- O
Ogun B-LOC
state I-LOC
South I-LOC
West I-LOC
Nigeria I-LOC
, O
don O
tok O
about O
wetin O
dem O
remember O
am O
for O
, O
and O
how O
di O
loss O
go O
forever O
affect O
dem O
. O

Tiamiyu B-PER
na O
rising O
footballer O
with O
Remo B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
club I-ORG
wey O
im O
life O
cut O
short O
afta O
one O
unfortunate O
incident O
wey O
involve O
police O
, O
but O
for O
di O
family O
and O
friends O
wey O
im O
leave O
behind O
, O
di O
memory O
of O
dia O
love O
one O
still O
fresh O
for O
mind O
. O

Tiamiyu B-PER
Fasasi I-PER
, O
wey O
bi O
Kazeem B-PER
papa O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Yoruba I-ORG
say O
e O
never O
reach O
like O
two B-DATE
weeks I-DATE
wen O
im O
pikin O
tell O
am O
say O
im O
get O
invitation O
to O
go O
play O
[ O
football O
] O
trial O
for O
Sweden B-LOC
. O

E O
say O
na O
on O
Friday B-DATE
, I-DATE
21 I-DATE
February I-DATE
Kazeem B-PER
say O
im O
dey O
go O
meet O
with O
im O
manager O
- O
wey O
arrive O
for O
Sagamu B-LOC
- O
ontop O
di O
Sweden B-LOC
mata O
. O

And O
say O
di O
plan O
na O
to O
sleep O
for O
im O
manager O
side O
and O
come O
back O
house O
di O
next O
dey O
. O

Na O
during O
im O
waka O
come O
back O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
morning I-DATE
, O
di O
Remo B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
player O
die O
from O
wetin O
im O
club O
say O
na O
police O
fault O
. O

Although O
police O
never O
accept O
responsibility O
, O
dia O
oga O
patapata O
IGP O
Mohammed B-PER
Adamu I-PER
don O
order O
investigation O
into O
am O
. O

Kazeem B-PER
mama O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
how O
e O
don O
promise O
her O
better O
life O
as O
thank O
you O
for O
all O
di O
wahala O
she O
suffer O
ontop O
dem O
. O

"""" O
E O
dey O
very O
caring O
, O
e O
never O
fight O
anybodi O
before O
, O
and O
na O
pikin O
wey O
like O
to O
give O
. O

If O
na O
N1000 O
dey O
Kazeem B-PER
account O
and O
pesin O
ask O
am O
for O
N900 O
, O
e O
go O
give O
am O
, O
"""" O
na O
im O
Selimotu B-PER
Tiamiyu I-PER
tok O
about O
her O
son O
. O

Selimotu B-PER
recount O
how O
she O
wash O
clothes O
, O
clean O
floors O
and O
sell O
iced O
water O
, O
in O
oda O
to O
get O
money O
to O
raise O
Kazeem B-PER
im O
younger O
ones O
, O
and O
she O
don O
hope O
say O
time O
don O
reach O
for O
her O
to O
begin O
enjoy O
Kazeem B-PER
success O
. O

Im O
coach O
Daniel B-PER
Ogunmodede I-PER
, O
say O
na O
Kazeem B-PER
good O
behaviour O
make O
am O
promote O
Kazeem B-PER
to O
assistant O
captain O
, O
even O
though O
na O
four B-DATE
months I-DATE
ago I-DATE
im O
join O
dem O
. O

Tori O
break O
ontop O
social O
media O
afta O
Remo B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
football O
club O
release O
statement O
say O
SARS B-ORG
Police O
harass O
dia O
player O
Kazeem B-PER
wey O
lead O
to O
im O
death O
for O
Sagamu B-LOC
, O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
22 I-DATE
February I-DATE
. O

Dem O
say O
SARS B-ORG
bin O
claim O
Kazeem B-PER
na O
mago O
- O
mago O
pesin O
, O
even O
afta O
dia O
player O
show O
dem O
im O
ID O
card O
. O

And O
na O
during O
dis O
gbege O
with O
SARS B-ORG
anoda O
car O
hit O
and O
kill O
Kazeem B-PER
. O

Police O
earlier O
say O
Kazeem B-PER
die O
as O
e O
dey O
cross O
expressway O
in O
order O
to O
dodge O
arrest O
by O
men O
of O
di O
Special B-ORG
Anti I-ORG
- I-ORG
Robbery I-ORG
Squad I-ORG
( O
SARS B-ORG
) O
, O
according O
to O
tori O
by O
Channels B-ORG
TV I-ORG
. O

Authorities O
don O
say O
now O
dem O
go O
look O
di O
mata O
and O
investigate O
. O

"""" O
Dem O
kill O
my O
pikin O
wey O
no O
commit O
any O
crime O
, O
no O
sabi O
anything O
. O

I O
want O
fair O
and O
true O
justice O
from O
di O
federal O
goment O
and O
even O
from O
di O
police O
demsef O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Kazeem B-PER
papa O
say O
im O
want O
now O
. O

Foto O
show O
England B-LOC
international O
player O
Raheem B-PER
Sterling I-PER
wit O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
shirt O
afta O
dem O
ask O
am O
about O
im O
future O
wit O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
. O

"""" O
Wen O
you O
see O
di O
white O
shirt O
you O
go O
know O
exactly O
which O
club O
e O
dey O
stand O
for O
, O
dem O
dey O
very O
big O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Sterling B-PER
tok O
. O

City B-ORG
go O
play O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
for O
di O
last O
16 O
of O
Champions O
League O
, O
di O
first O
leg O
go O
happun O
for O
Spain B-LOC
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

Di O
return O
leg O
na O
for O
Etihad B-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
for O
Manchester B-LOC
on O
17 B-DATE
March I-DATE
. O

Dis O
dey O
come O
afta O
Uefa B-ORG
ban O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
wey O
be O
di O
current O
Premier O
League O
Champions O
, O
from O
European O
football O
for O
di O
next O
two B-DATE
seasons I-DATE
. O

Di O
ban O
dey O
start O
next B-DATE
year I-DATE
- O
2021season B-DATE
. O

Na O
because O
dem O
find O
out O
say O
dem O
find O
out O
say O
dem O
rules O
wey O
relate O
to O
how O
much O
money O
dem O
dey O
allowed O
to O
spend O
. O

Dat O
na O
why O
tori O
dey O
fly O
upandan O
weda O
di O
City B-ORG
top O
players O
go O
leave O
. O

Im O
tell O
Spanish O
tori O
pipo O
AS O
: O
"""" O
Right O
now O
I O
dey O
City B-ORG
and O
I O
dey O
really O
happy O
. O

But O
I O
go O
say O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
na O
fantastic O
club O
. O
"""" O

Dem O
ask O
am O
weda O
im O
go O
like O
play O
for O
Real B-ORG
, O
im O
tok O
say O
: O
"""" O
How O
I O
go O
carry O
answer O
dis O
one O
? O

Di O
camera O
dey O
live O
or O
e O
just O
dey O
take O
pictures O
? O
"""" O

Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
manager O
Pep B-PER
Guardiola I-PER
say O
im O
players O
dey O
"""" O
free O
to O
tok O
as O
e O
be O
. O

We O
no O
dey O
here O
to O
tell O
them O
wetin O
dem O
need O
to O
tok O
"""" O
. O

Sterling B-PER
don O
score O
11 O
goals O
dis O
season O
. O

Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
don O
blame O
im O
big O
costume O
wey O
im O
wear O
enta O
ring O
for O
why O
Tyson B-PER
Fury I-PER
defeat O
am O
for O
di O
WBC O
heavyweight O
title O
. O

Di O
American O
, O
34 B-DATE
, O
say O
im O
costume O
heavy O
so O
tey O
"""" O
legs O
weak O
am O
"""" O
for O
di O
fight O
. O

Fury B-PER
from O
Britain B-LOC
use O
ogbonge O
fight O
to O
win O
di O
title O
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
after O
Wilder B-PER
pipo O
ask O
say O
make O
referee O
end O
di O
match O
for O
seventh O
round O
. O

Wilder B-PER
also O
tell O
US B-LOC
tori O
pipo O
say O
im O
go O
request O
for O
rematch O
to O
fight O
Fury B-PER
for O
di O
third O
time O
. O

"""" O
Fury B-PER
no O
wound O
me O
at O
all O
, O
but O
di O
simple O
fact O
be O
say O
my O
uniform O
too O
heavy O
for O
me O
, O
"""" O
Wilder B-PER
told O
Yahoo B-ORG
. O

Wilder B-PER
say O
di O
costume O
, O
wey O
dem O
sew O
plenty O
tins O
ontop O
am O
, O
also O
come O
wit O
mask O
and O
crown O
, O
weigh O
at O
least O
18 O
. O
1kg O
and O
na O
tribute O
to O
Black B-DATE
History I-DATE
Month I-DATE
. O

Fury B-PER
on O
di O
oda O
hand O
no O
use O
im O
leg O
waka O
enta O
ring O
as O
im O
sidon O
ontop O
throne O
wey O
four O
pipo O
carri O
. O

"""" O
My O
legs O
weak O
me O
from O
di O
from O
di O
beginning O
of O
di O
fight O
- O
and O
for O
di O
third O
round O
, O
my O
legs O
no O
fit O
carri O
me O
again O
, O
"""" O
tok O
Wilder B-PER
. O

"""" O
I O
no O
reason O
am O
say O
e O
go O
heavy O
like O
that O
. O
"""" O

Although O
dem O
carri O
Wilder B-PER
go O
hospital O
after O
di O
fight O
, O
e O
say O
im O
no O
get O
concussion O
, O
say O
im O
ear O
drum O
no O
bust O
or O
im O
jaw O
break O
, O
like O
di O
way O
pipo O
dey O
tok O
. O

Former O
Brazil B-LOC
forward O
Ronaldinho B-PER
dey O
police O
custody O
for O
Paraguay B-LOC
ontop O
accuse O
say O
im O
use O
fake O
passport O
enta O
di O
kontri O
, O
according O
to O
authorities O
. O

Police O
search O
di O
hotel O
for O
di O
capital O
, O
Asuncion B-LOC
, O
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
, O
wia O
im O
dey O
stay O
wit O
im O
brother O
. O

Paraguay B-LOC
interior O
minister O
bin O
tell O
ESPN B-ORG
Brazil I-ORG
say O
dem O
never O
arrest O
di O
two O
of O
dem O
but O
dem O
dey O
under O
investigation O
. O

Minister O
Euclides B-PER
Acevedo I-PER
also O
confam O
say O
di O
brothers O
don O
deny O
di O
accuse O
and O
dem O
dey O
co O
- O
operate O
wit O
authorities O
. O

For O
July B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
, O
di O
player O
lose O
im O
Brazilian O
and O
Spanish O
passports O
ontop O
tax O
money O
wey O
im O
no O
pay O
. O

"""" O
Ronaldinho B-PER
go O
get O
chance O
by O
8amt O
on O
Thursday B-DATE
to O
tok O
im O
side O
of O
di O
tori O
for O
di O
prosecutor's O
office O
, O
"""" O
minister O
Euclides B-PER
Acevedo I-PER
tell O
AFP B-ORG
. O

E O
also O
add O
say O
dem O
go O
investigate O
dia O
own O
customers O
authorities O
join O
. O

"""" O
I O
respect O
say O
im O
na O
big O
man O
for O
sports O
but O
di O
law O
no O
dey O
respect O
pesin O
. O

No O
mata O
who O
you O
be O
, O
di O
law O
still O
apply O
to O
you O
, O
"""" O
Oga O
Acevedo B-PER
tell O
local O
tori O
pipo O
. O

Ronaldinho B-PER
dey O
Paraguay B-LOC
to O
promote O
one O
book O
and O
do O
campaign O
for O
underprivileged O
pikin O
dem O
. O

Di O
39 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
win O
World O
Player O
Of O
The O
Year O
two O
times O
( O
2004 B-DATE
and O
2005 B-DATE
) O
and O
im O
win O
di O
World O
Cup O
for O
2002 B-DATE
wit O
fellow O
superstar O
strikers O
Ronaldo B-PER
and O
Rivaldo B-PER
. O

One O
former O
rugby O
league O
player O
, O
im O
wife O
and O
dia O
three O
children O
die O
inside O
fire O
for O
di O
Australian O
city O
of O
Brisbane B-LOC
. O

Emergency O
workers O
find O
di O
bodi O
of O
Rowan B-PER
Baxter I-PER
and O
im O
pikin O
dem O
, O
wey O
dey O
under O
age B-DATE
of I-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
inside O
car O
, O
police O
tok O
. O

Hannah B-PER
Baxter I-PER
, O
wey O
be O
31 B-DATE
years I-DATE
, O
die O
later O
for O
hospital O
from O
serious O
burns O
all O
ova O
her O
bodi O
. O

Report O
bin O
say O
she O
jump O
comot O
from O
car O
dey O
shout O
: O
"""" O
E O
pour O
me O
petrol O
"""" O
. O

"""" O
Dis O
na O
horrific O
scene O
, O
"""" O
Det O
Insp O
Mark B-PER
Thompson I-PER
tel O
tori O
pipo O
: O
"""" O
We O
still O
dey O
investigate O
di O
mata O
, O
but O
wen O
police O
reach O
di O
crime O
scene O
di O
car O
dey O
burn O
. O

Police O
find O
Rowan B-PER
Baxter I-PER
, O
42 B-DATE
, O
and O
im O
three O
pikin O
- O
age B-DATE
three I-DATE
, O
four B-DATE
and O
six B-DATE
- O
wey O
don O
die O
inside O
di O
car O
. O

Rowan B-PER
Baxter I-PER
bin O
dey O
for O
di O
front O
passenger O
seat O
and O
Hannah B-PER
Baxter I-PER
bin O
dey O
drive O
di O
car O
, O
police O
tok O
. O

Pipo O
wey O
dey O
live O
for O
di O
area O
tell O
Australian O
tori O
pipo O
say O
dem O
see O
madam O
Baxter B-PER
, O
31 B-DATE
, O
jump O
comot O
from O
di O
car O
wen O
she O
dey O
on O
fire O
. O

She O
bin O
dey O
critical O
condition O
wen O
dem O
cari O
her O
go O
Royal B-ORG
Brisbane I-ORG
and I-ORG
Women's I-ORG
Hospital I-ORG
, O
police O
tok O
. O

But O
dem O
confam O
am O
say O
she O
later O
die O
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

Tori O
be O
say O
di O
couple O
bin O
don O
separate O
late O
last B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
and O
dem O
dey O
try O
to O
agree O
on O
who O
dia O
children O
go O
dey O
live O
with O
. O

pair O
had O
reportedly O
separated O
late O
last B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
and O
were O
trying O
to O
work O
out O
custody O
arrangements O
. O

Prime O
Minister O
Scott B-PER
Morrison I-PER
say O
im O
"""" O
heart O
dey O
go O
out O
to O
di O
families O
and O
community O
wey O
dey O
go O
through O
dis O
tragic O
time O
and O
di O
emergency O
workers O
wey O
dey O
di O
horrible O
scene O
. O
"""" O

Federal O
MP O
Terri B-PER
Butler I-PER
say O
di O
mata O
shake O
am O
well O
- O
well O
reach O
bone O
. O

Tyson B-PER
Fury I-PER
and O
Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
go O
face O
each O
oda O
again O
for O
early O
mor O
- O
mor O
on O
Sunday B-DATE
, O
almost O
15 B-DATE
months I-DATE
afta O
dia O
last O
fight O
end O
for O
draw O
for O
Los B-LOC
Angeles I-LOC
. O

Tickets O
for O
dia O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
fights O
dey O
go O
for O
thousands O
of O
dollars O
, O
already O
di O
fighters O
dey O
badmouth O
each O
oda O
ahead O
of O
di O
fight O
. O

Di O
big O
prize O
na O
Wilder B-PER
WBC O
world O
title O
. O

If O
Fury B-PER
win O
am O
e O
mean O
say O
all O
four O
heavyweight O
belts O
go O
dey O
shared O
between O
two O
British O
fighters O
- O
him O
and O
Anthony B-PER
Joshua I-PER
, O
go O
hold O
di O
IBF O
, O
WBA O
and O
WBO O
titles O
. O

Wilder B-PER
dey O
start O
as O
favourite O
according O
to O
betting O
pipo O
before O
di O
fighters O
go O
waka O
enta O
di O
ring O
around O
05 B-DATE
: I-DATE
00 I-DATE
GMT I-DATE
on O
Sunday B-DATE
morning I-DATE
. O

Dis O
na O
everything O
you O
need O
to O
know O
about O
di O
fight O
. O

Na O
few O
tickets O
remain O
for O
di O
fight O
wey O
go O
happun O
for O
MGM B-LOC
Grand I-LOC
Garden I-LOC
Arena I-LOC
, O
di O
ticket O
prize O
na O
from O
$ O
425 O
( O
£ O
330 O
) O
for O
open O
market O
to O
$ O
10 O
, O
000 O
( O
£ O
7 O
, O
754 O
) O
for O
black O
market O
. O

For O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
Strip O
, O
fans O
fit O
pay O
$ O
100 O
( O
£ O
77 O
) O
to O
watch O
di O
fight O
for O
big O
screen O
while O
di O
fight O
go O
cost O
$ O
74 O
. O
99 O
( O
£ O
58 O
) O
to O
buy O
for O
house O
for O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
live O
for O
US B-LOC
, O
e O
mean O
say O
dem O
fit O
raise O
up O
to O
$ O
150m O
( O
£ O
116m O
) O
even O
before O
dem O
collect O
ticket O
money O
. O

In O
terms O
of O
money O
for O
di O
two O
men O
dia O
money O
fit O
reach O
eight O
- O
figure O
for O
dat O
night B-DATE
alone O
. O

Na O
di O
biggest O
heavyweight O
fight O
for O
20 B-DATE
, O
30 B-DATE
, O
or O
even O
50 B-DATE
years I-DATE
- O
dat O
na O
if O
you O
listen O
to O
wetin O
Fury B-PER
dey O
tok O
. O

"""" O
I O
don O
dey O
here O
for O
25 B-DATE
years I-DATE
and O
I O
neva O
see O
dis O
kind O
investment O
for O
pay O
- O
per O
- O
view O
fight O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
BBC B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
boxing O
correspondent O
Mike B-PER
Costello I-PER
tok O
. O

Im O
5 O
Live O
Boxing O
sidekick O
Steve B-PER
Bunce I-PER
add O
say O
: O
"""" O
Two O
men O
wey O
dey O
unbeaten O
, O
elite O
versus O
elite O
. O

Make O
wey O
no O
forget O
say O
we O
dey O
see O
something O
wey O
we O
no O
dey O
every O
day O
. O

Dis O
na O
monster O
. O
"""" O

Some O
UK B-LOC
betting O
company O
dey O
put O
Wilder B-PER
as O
slight O
favourite O
for O
di O
sports O
betting O
facility O
for O
MGM B-LOC
Grand I-LOC
, O
wia O
some O
big O
spenders O
fit O
force O
di O
prize O
to O
change O
as O
di O
fight O
dey O
near O
. O

Costello B-PER
add O
say O
: O
I O
feel O
say O
Wilder B-PER
don O
learn O
from O
im O
first O
fight O
and O
e O
go O
dey O
better O
dis O
time O
to O
close O
di O
space O
dem O
. O

I O
know O
when O
im O
go O
catch O
Fury B-PER
but O
I O
feel O
say O
im O
go O
catch O
am O
. O
"""" O

Bunce B-PER
respond O
: O
"""" O
I O
feel O
say O
we O
go O
see O
Wilder B-PER
box O
small O
and O
Fury B-PER
go O
dey O
more O
aggressive O
. O

I O
no O
think O
say O
dis O
changes O
dem O
go O
last O
. O

I O
believe O
say O
Fury B-PER
go O
survive O
some O
difficult O
moment O
and O
then O
win O
on O
points O
. O

And O
yes O
, O
e O
go O
dey O
controversial O
. O
"""" O

Sabi O
pipo O
and O
betting O
pipo O
dey O
divided O
. O

"""" O
Dis O
na O
di O
moment O
we O
don O
dey O
wait O
for O
tey O
- O
tey O
, O
"""" O
dat O
na O
wetin O
Wilder B-PER
tok O
dis B-DATE
week I-DATE
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
latest O
twist O
for O
dis O
rivalry O
. O

At O
least O
di O
waiting O
dey O
nearly O
over O
. O

Wilder B-PER
neva O
too O
change O
, O
so O
di O
result O
of O
dis O
fight O
go O
depend O
on O
di O
success O
of O
failure O
of O
di O
changes O
Fury B-PER
don O
make O
. O

Outside O
di O
gym O
, O
im O
profile O
for O
US B-LOC
don O
rise O
, O
wey O
don O
also O
bring O
new O
demands O
. O

Inside O
di O
gym O
, O
im O
get O
one O
new O
trainer O
. O

SugarHill B-PER
Steward I-PER
, O
wey O
be O
policeman O
before O
, O
dey O
call O
imself O
"""" O
di O
knockout O
architect O
"""" O
, O
afta O
im O
learn O
how O
to O
box O
for O
di O
legendary O
Detroit B-ORG
Kronk I-ORG
Gym I-ORG
. O

Fury B-PER
get O
new O
cuts O
man O
- O
in O
case O
di O
wound O
wey O
need O
47 O
stitches O
after O
im O
September B-DATE
win O
over O
Otto B-PER
Wallin I-PER
open O
again O
- O
and O
im O
also O
hire O
di O
chef O
wey O
UFC B-ORG
star O
Conor B-PER
McGregor I-PER
dey O
use O
. O

Im O
no O
dey O
drink O
Diet O
coke O
, O
drink O
wey O
im O
like O
well O
- O
well O
. O

Di O
most O
important O
one O
of O
all O
dem O
na O
im O
promise O
to O
move O
away O
from O
im O
style O
and O
any O
try O
to O
knock O
out O
deadly O
puncher O
. O

"""" O
Wetin O
I O
do O
di O
last O
time O
clearly O
no O
dey O
good O
enough O
, O
so O
we O
go O
for O
di O
knockout O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Fury B-PER
tok O
. O

"""" O
I O
feel O
say O
Wilder B-PER
go O
come O
out O
of O
di O
gates O
like O
horse O
wey O
dey O
run O
to O
try O
to O
knock O
me O
out O
. O
"""" O

Confederation B-ORG
of I-ORG
African I-ORG
Football I-ORG
, O
CAF B-ORG
don O
say O
deh O
di O
watch O
Cameroon B-LOC
as O
host O
for O
African O
Football O
Championship O
, O
CHAN O
as O
coronavirus O
don O
enta O
big O
African O
football O
kontris O
. O

Cameroon B-LOC
go O
host O
CHAN O
2020 B-DATE
from O
4 B-DATE
- I-DATE
25 I-DATE
April I-DATE
and O
na O
one O
of O
de O
kontris O
for O
announce O
say O
two O
pipo O
don O
test O
positive O
for O
coronavirus O
recently O
. O

CAF B-ORG
komot O
release O
on O
coronavirus O
say O
dia O
team O
of O
doctors O
di O
check O
de O
situation O
for O
continent O
. O

Eight O
major O
football O
kontris O
for O
Africa B-LOC
don O
already O
get O
de O
virus O
: O
Egypt B-LOC
, O
Algeria B-LOC
, O
Tunisia B-LOC
, O
Morocco B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
Senegal B-LOC
, O
Cameroon B-LOC
and O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

"""" O
We O
no O
di O
too O
worry O
about O
de O
situation O
but O
we O
bi O
on O
alert O
for O
future O
matches O
like O
CAF B-ORG
Champions O
League O
, O
CAF B-ORG
Confederations O
Cup O
and O
African O
Nations O
Championship O
, O
CHAN O
weh O
e O
suppose O
take O
place O
for O
Cameroon B-LOC
. O

Cameroon B-LOC
also O
apply O
for O
host O
CAF B-ORG
Champions O
League O
. O

Just O
now O
CAF B-ORG
medical O
teams O
di O
watch O
, O
di O
report O
for O
executive O
committee O
and O
if O
de O
situation O
wowo O
, O
CAF B-ORG
for O
decide O
make O
de O
play O
matches O
wit O
no O
fans O
, O
postpone O
or O
cancel O
. O

For O
now O
CAF B-ORG
di O
promote O
WHO B-ORG
guideline O
for O
keep O
safe O
from O
de O
virus O
. O

One O
player O
chop O
five B-DATE
years I-DATE
suspension O
for O
France B-LOC
sake O
of O
say O
im O
bite O
im O
opponent O
penis O
for O
fight O
wey O
happun O
afta O
dia O
match O
. O

Di O
incident O
happun O
for O
France B-LOC
for O
November B-DATE
17 I-DATE
for O
di O
second O
division O
match O
between O
Terville B-ORG
and O
Soetrich B-ORG
. O

According O
to O
one O
local O
news O
website O
for O
Lorraine B-LOC
, O
kasala O
burst O
wen O
one O
of O
di O
players O
from O
each O
of O
di O
team O
begin O
fight O
demself O
, O
another O
Terville B-ORG
player O
come O
join O
, O
tori O
be O
say O
im O
try O
to O
separate O
dem O
. O

Na O
so O
di O
Soetrich B-ORG
player O
respond O
come O
bite O
im O
penis O
. O

Tori O
be O
say O
di O
victim O
need O
10 O
stitches O
and O
e O
gatz O
take O
four B-DATE
days I-DATE
off O
work O
. O

Di O
incident O
happun O
afta O
dia O
match O
for O
di O
stadium O
car O
park O
. O

Di O
fight O
start O
small O
before O
e O
worse O
, O
' O
na O
wetin O
Emmanuel B-PER
Saling I-PER
of O
di O
Mosellan B-ORG
football I-ORG
district I-ORG
tok O
, O
'im O
blame O
di O
two O
sides' O
. O

Na O
wetin O
im O
add O
put O
. O

Saling B-PER
say O
because O
di O
'case O
dey O
quite O
original' O
, O
di O
disciplinary O
committee O
call O
expert O
witness O
before O
dem O
decide O
to O
suspend O
di O
Soetrich B-ORG
player O
for O
five B-DATE
years I-DATE
. O

While O
di O
injured O
Terville B-ORG
player O
chop O
six B-DATE
months I-DATE
suspension O
. O

Di O
match O
end O
for O
1 O
- O
1 O
draw O
wey O
for O
be O
Terville B-ORG
first O
point O
of O
di O
season O
but O
dem O
punish O
dem O
with O
two O
penalty O
points O
and O
fine O
dem O
200 O
euros O
sake O
of O
say O
dem O
no O
meet O
dia O
safety O
obligations O
as O
hosts O
and O
for O
lack O
of O
reaction O
from O
club O
officials O
when O
di O
fight O
start O
. O

Di O
king O
don O
return O
to O
di O
top O
of O
di O
throne' O
Dis O
na O
wetin O
Tyson B-PER
Fury I-PER
tok O
afta O
im O
beat O
Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
hands O
down O
to O
become O
WBC O
world O
heavyweight O
champion O
for O
dia O
rematch O
wey O
happun O
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
. O

Dis O
don O
end O
Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
five B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
reign O
as O
WBC O
heavyweight O
world O
champion O
. O

Tyson B-PER
Fury I-PER
use O
heavy O
punch O
knock O
out O
Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
for O
di O
seventh O
round O
before O
im O
corner O
throw O
in O
the O
towel O
to O
beg O
make O
di O
fight O
stop O
. O

Wilder B-PER
no O
dey O
happy O
with O
im O
corner O
wey O
dey O
pull O
am O
comot O
from O
di O
fight O
. O

"""" O
Di O
best O
man O
na O
im O
win O
dis O
night B-DATE
. O

My O
coach O
throw O
in O
di O
towel O
but O
I O
dey O
ready O
to O
go O
out O
on O
my O
shield O
. O

I O
just O
wish O
my O
corner O
for O
let O
me O
go O
out O
on O
my O
shield O
, O
I O
be O
warrior O
. O

But O
Fury B-PER
do O
wetin O
im O
do O
and O
I O
no O
get O
excuses O
. O
"""" O

Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
tok O
. O

Afta O
Fury B-PER
win O
e O
come O
begin O
dey O
bounce O
around O
with O
di O
WBC O
world O
heavyweight O
belt O
wey O
dey O
on O
top O
im O
shoulder O
. O

E O
give O
shout O
out O
to O
Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
and O
also O
call O
am O
'Warrior O
. O

"""" O
I O
want O
to O
give O
shout O
out O
to O
Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
, O
e O
show O
di O
heart O
of O
a O
champion O
. O

E O
get O
up O
and O
battle O
onto O
round O
seven O
. O

E O
be O
warrior O
, O
e O
go O
come O
back O
and O
be O
champion O
again O
. O

But O
di O
king O
don O
return O
to O
di O
top O
of O
di O
throne O
. O
"""" O

Fury B-PER
later O
tell O
tori O
pipo O
say O
im O
dey O
"""" O
expect O
Wilder B-PER
to O
ask O
for O
di O
third O
fight O
. O

I O
know O
e O
be O
warrior O
and O
I O
go O
dey O
wait O
for O
am O
. O
"""" O

E O
add O
say O
im O
career O
go O
dey O
"""" O
complete O
"""" O
if O
e O
face O
Anthony B-PER
Joshua I-PER
. O

Former O
world O
heavyweight O
champion O
David B-PER
Haye I-PER
say O
Tyson B-PER
Fury I-PER
"""" O
cannot O
do O
no O
wrong O
"""" O
. O

"""" O
E O
dey O
box O
out O
of O
im O
skin O
and O
I O
no O
know O
say O
e O
fit O
do O
dis O
. O

"""" O
I O
just O
witness O
greatness O
. O
"""" O

Haye B-PER
tell O
BT B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
Box I-ORG
Office I-ORG
. O

Tyson B-PER
Fury I-PER
former O
trainer O
Ben B-PER
Davison I-PER
, O
tweet O
say O
na O
good O
decision O
Wilder B-PER
corner O
take O
to O
trow O
in O
di O
tower O
. O

Oda O
pipo O
for O
twitter B-ORG
no O
fit O
hide O
dia O
surprise O
and O
joy O
. O

Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
new O
signing O
Odion B-PER
Ighalo I-PER
dey O
train O
separate O
from O
wia O
oda O
players O
of O
di O
club O
dey O
train O
. O

United B-ORG
say O
na O
step O
wey O
dem O
take O
becos O
of O
di O
risk O
of O
Coronavirus O
as O
Ighalo B-PER
dey O
come O
from O
China B-LOC
wia O
di O
virus O
don O
kill O
more O
dan O
1000 O
pipo O
. O

United B-ORG
bin O
decide O
to O
no O
carry O
di O
striker O
go O
dia O
winter O
break O
training O
camp O
for O
Spain B-LOC
becos O
of O
concern O
say O
im O
fit O
experience O
difficulty O
to O
return O
back O
to O
UK B-LOC
. O

Ighalo B-PER
, O
30 B-DATE
, O
dey O
expected O
to O
travel O
with O
di O
squad O
for O
Monday B-DATE
game O
against O
Chelsea B-ORG
. O

BBC B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
understand O
say O
Ighalo B-PER
don O
dey O
train O
with O
support O
from O
di O
club O
as O
im O
dey O
use O
personalised O
fitness O
programme O
to O
ready O
am O
for O
di O
Chelsea B-ORG
Premier O
League O
game O
. O

Na O
for O
di O
National B-ORG
Taekwondo I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
wey O
dey O
close O
to O
Etihad B-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
and O
wia O
im O
don O
dey O
stay O
dem O
dey O
use O
since O
e O
land O
from O
China B-LOC
11 B-DATE
days I-DATE
ago I-DATE
. O

Ighalo B-PER
join O
United B-ORG
on O
loan O
for O
di O
rest O
of O
di O
season O
from O
China B-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
club O
Shanghai B-ORG
Shenhua I-ORG
. O

Di O
current O
medical O
advice O
na O
say O
travellers O
wey O
dey O
come O
into O
di O
UK B-LOC
from O
specific O
kontris O
, O
including O
China B-LOC
, O
dem O
go O
quarantine O
dem O
for O
14 B-DATE
days I-DATE
. O

Nigeria B-ORG
Football I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
don O
appoint O
former O
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
captain O
Joseph B-PER
Yobo I-PER
as O
assistant O
coach O
of O
di O
team O
. O

Yobo B-PER
wey O
play O
for O
six O
Nations O
Cup O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
as O
defender O
go O
replace O
Imama B-PER
Amapakabo I-PER
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
technical O
crew O
. O

Di O
defender O
play O
for O
three O
World O
Cups O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
bin O
be O
di O
captain O
of O
di O
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
wen O
dem O
win O
di O
2013 B-DATE
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
. O

NFF B-ORG
announce O
dis O
appointment O
for O
inside O
statement O
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

Yobo B-PER
wey O
play O
100 O
matches O
for O
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
also O
play O
for O
Everton B-ORG
, O
Fenerbahce B-ORG
, O
Marseille B-ORG
, O
Standard B-ORG
Liege I-ORG
and O
Norwich B-ORG
City I-ORG
. O

Turkey B-LOC
club O
Trabzonspor B-ORG
don O
condemn O
racial O
abuse O
wey O
former O
Nigeria B-LOC
captain O
John B-PER
Mikel I-PER
Obi I-PER
receive O
for O
dia O
win O
over O
Fenerbahce B-ORG
on O
Saturday B-DATE
. O

Fans O
target O
Mikel B-PER
on O
social O
media O
afta O
2 O
- O
1 O
victory O
wey O
move O
Trabzonspor B-ORG
above O
dia O
opponents O
into O
third O
place O
. O

Di O
club O
say O
dem O
don O
file O
"""" O
criminal O
complain O
"""" O
against O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
responsible O
. O

"""" O
Racism O
na O
shelter O
for O
di O
helpless O
and O
ignorant O
, O
"""" O
na O
so O
Trabzonsport B-ORG
tok O
for O
statement O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
. O

Mikel B-PER
wey O
also O
play O
for O
Chelsea B-ORG
tok O
say O
: O
"""" O
We O
all O
be O
one O
and O
equal O
. O

At O
di O
end O
of O
di O
day O
, O
dis O
na O
just O
game O
e O
be O
. O
"""" O

Dis O
na O
di O
biggest O
tori O
for O
English O
football O
dis O
season O
. O

Dem O
don O
kick O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
comot O
from O
Champions O
League O
until O
2022 B-DATE
. O

City B-ORG
dey O
vex O
, O
dem O
claim O
say O
na O
di O
court O
no O
follow O
law O
to O
find O
dem O
guilty O
and O
dem O
promise O
say O
di O
fight O
neva O
finish O
. O

But O
for O
now O
, O
dem O
don O
comot O
from O
any O
European O
competition O
and O
dis O
dey O
raise O
different O
kain O
question O
for O
di O
club O
. O

For O
di O
last O
two B-DATE
weeks I-DATE
, O
City B-ORG
manager O
Pep B-PER
Guardiola I-PER
, O
don O
dey O
ansa O
plenti O
questions O
about O
im O
future O
by O
saying O
, O
im O
plan O
to O
stay O
till O
di O
end O
of O
im O
contract O
wit O
di O
Blues B-ORG
. O

Di O
contract O
go O
expire O
for O
2021 B-DATE
. O

Also O
, O
Guardiola B-PER
continue O
to O
insist O
say O
im O
trust O
di O
City B-ORG
management O
afta O
dem O
assure O
am O
say O
UEFA B-ORG
no O
bin O
get O
any O
basis O
for O
di O
tins O
wey O
dem O
bin O
chook O
eye O
inside O
. O

Guardiola B-PER
feel O
say O
dem O
disappoint O
am O
by O
dis O
decision O
? O

E O
no O
dey O
possible O
to O
say O
. O

Bet O
, O
e O
fair O
to O
assume O
say O
afta O
im O
win O
Premier O
League O
titles O
back O
- O
to O
- O
back O
with O
ogbonge O
points O
for O
table O
, O
plus O
become O
di O
first O
side O
to O
gbab O
all O
di O
three O
domestic O
trophies O
for O
one O
single O
season O
, O
Guardiola B-PER
morale O
fit O
dey O
low O
. O

Even O
if O
City B-ORG
win O
di O
Champions O
League O
this O
season O
, O
Guardiola B-PER
still O
waka O
. O

As O
e O
be O
so O
, O
e O
hard O
to O
imagine O
say O
im O
go O
stay O
with O
all O
di O
rumours O
wey O
dey O
fly O
upandan O
say O
Juventus B-ORG
want O
am O
. O

Wetin O
go O
determine O
di O
future O
of O
Guardiola B-PER
for O
Man B-ORG
City I-ORG
na O
if O
di O
club O
dey O
succesful O
for O
dia O
appeal O
against O
UEFA B-ORG
. O

We O
alreadi O
know O
say O
veteran O
midfielder O
David B-PER
Silva I-PER
go O
comot O
for O
end O
of O
dis O
season O
. O

But O
di O
number O
of O
players O
wey O
dia O
contracts O
go O
expire O
before O
City B-ORG
go O
return O
back O
to O
Champions O
League O
na O
mata O
wey O
dey O
worry O
. O

Striker O
Sergio B-PER
Aguero I-PER
dey O
top O
of O
dat O
list O
. O

Im O
deal O
go O
expire O
for O
2021 B-DATE
. O

Leroy B-PER
Sane I-PER
deal O
go O
ends O
at O
the O
same O
time O
. O

John B-PER
Stones I-PER
deal O
dey O
expire O
one B-DATE
year I-DATE
later O
. O

Di O
same O
for O
Nicolas B-PER
Otamendi I-PER
. O

And O
what O
about O
di O
stars O
wey O
dia O
contract O
dey O
go O
pass O
2022 B-DATE
, O
like O
Kevin B-PER
de I-PER
Bruyne I-PER
, O
Ederson B-PER
, O
Bernardo B-PER
Silva I-PER
, O
Raheem B-PER
Sterling I-PER
, O
Bernardo B-PER
Silva I-PER
and O
Riyad B-PER
Mahrez I-PER
? O

If O
Guardiola B-PER
leave O
, O
e O
go O
easy O
to O
see O
plenti O
players O
follow O
am O
waka O
, O
and O
e O
fit O
make O
Man B-ORG
City I-ORG
begin O
build O
im O
team O
from O
di O
scratch O
. O

Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
brand O
new O
player O
, O
Odion B-PER
Ighalo I-PER
say O
im O
dey O
so O
desperate O
to O
play O
for O
di O
club O
sotey O
im O
agree O
to O
half O
im O
salary O
to O
make O
di O
deal O
happun O
and O
im O
no O
sleep O
di O
night B-DATE
di O
agreement O
take O
place O
. O

Ighalo B-PER
wey O
be O
30 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
from O
Nigeria B-LOC
tok O
say O
im O
mama O
also O
cry O
wen O
she O
hear O
di O
news O
and O
pipo O
trow O
party O
for O
di O
street O
wey O
im O
grow O
up O
. O

Di O
former O
Watford B-ORG
striker O
join O
di O
red O
devil O
on O
load O
from O
Shanghai B-ORG
Shenhua I-ORG
until O
di O
end O
of O
di O
season O
. O

"""" O
Some O
few O
oda O
clubs O
bin O
show O
interest O
, O
I O
tell O
my O
former O
club O
say O
'abeg O
, O
just O
pick O
United B-ORG
, O
if O
e O
go O
dey O
possible' O
, O
"""" O
Ighalo B-PER
tok O
inside O
statement O
ontop O
di O
club O
website O
. O

"""" O
At O
11pm B-DATE
inside O
Shanghai B-LOC
, O
my O
agent O
call O
me O
[ O
to O
say O
] O
United B-ORG
want O
to O
do O
di O
deal O
, O
so O
I O
wake O
up O
dat O
night B-DATE
and O
start O
to O
dey O
look O
for O
translator O
to O
go O
di O
directors' O
room O
and O
knock O
im O
door O
. O

"""" O
'My O
agent O
want O
to O
speak O
to O
you O
, O
United B-ORG
dey O
come O
for O
me O
, O
you O
need O
to O
make O
dis O
happun' O
. O
"""" O

Both O
Ighalo B-PER
, O
im O
agent O
and O
di O
clubs O
spent O
di O
night B-DATE
dey O
negotiate O
and O
sign O
paper O
work O
so O
dat O
everi O
- O
everi O
go O
set O
before O
di O
deadline O
of O
07 B-DATE
: I-DATE
00 I-DATE
Shanghai B-LOC
time O
. O

Meanwhile O
, O
oda O
clubs O
dey O
call O
to O
ask O
Ighalo B-PER
to O
sign O
for O
dem O
. O

"""" O
I O
tell O
my O
agent O
say O
'dis O
na O
wetin O
I O
want O
. O

I O
want O
to O
come O
here' O
, O
"""" O
Ighalo B-PER
add O
. O

"""" O
He O
tell O
me O
say O
: O
'You O
go O
need O
to O
agree O
make O
dem O
reduce O
your O
salary O
for O
you O
to O
fit O
go O
United' B-ORG
. O

"""" O
I O
come O
reply O
say O
: O
'I O
no O
care O
oh O
. O

Make O
dis O
deal O
happun O
. O

I O
want O
to O
go O
join O
United B-ORG
. O

I O
no O
care O
how O
much O
be O
di O
pay O
- O
cut O
, O
I O
know O
dat O
, O
make O
e O
just O
happun' O
. O
"""" O

Ighalo B-PER
say O
e O
don O
tey O
wey O
im O
na O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
fan O
, O
na O
since O
wen O
im O
be O
small O
boy O
and O
e O
dey O
happy O
say O
im O
dream O
to O
play O
for O
di O
Old B-LOC
Trafford I-LOC
club O
don O
come O
through O
. O

"""" O
I O
call O
my O
mama O
and O
she O
dey O
happy O
, O
she O
even O
cry O
"""" O
e O
tok O
. O

"""" O
I O
know O
many O
pipo O
use O
to O
say O
wen O
dem O
join O
a O
team O
, O
dem O
go O
say O
na O
dia O
dream O
to O
play O
for O
dat O
team O
. O

My O
own O
no O
be O
di O
case O
. O

I O
support O
di O
team O
wen O
I O
dey O
young O
. O

"""" O
Pipo O
wey O
know O
me O
, O
even O
back O
den O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
and O
even O
wen O
I O
dey O
play O
for O
Watford B-ORG
, O
my O
team O
- O
mates O
know O
say O
I O
love O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
, O
I O
support O
dem O
. O
"""" O

Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
striker O
Odion B-PER
Ighalo I-PER
go O
miss O
di O
club O
training O
camp O
for O
Spain B-LOC
sake O
of O
fear O
of O
coronavirus O
outbreak O
wey O
fit O
make O
immigration O
for O
UK B-LOC
no O
allow O
enta O
back O
inside O
di O
kontri O
. O

Di O
Nigerian O
striker O
fly O
from O
China B-LOC
come O
Manchester B-LOC
last B-DATE
weekend I-DATE
afta O
di O
club O
sign O
am O
on O
loan O
from O
Shanghai B-ORG
Shenhua I-ORG
. O

United B-ORG
manager O
Ole B-PER
Gunnar I-PER
Solskjaer I-PER
tell O
MUTV B-ORG
say O
"""" O
Im O
for O
like O
come O
with O
di O
players O
so O
dat O
im O
go O
get O
to O
know O
dem O
, O
"""" O
. O

"""" O
But O
di O
risk O
[ O
of O
border O
restrictions O
wey O
don O
tight O
now O
] O
sake O
of O
di O
coronavirus O
we O
know O
want O
take O
chances O
. O
"""" O

Meanwhile O
, O
midfielder O
Scott B-PER
McTominay I-PER
and O
defender O
Axel B-PER
Tuanzebe I-PER
, O
wey O
get O
injury O
, O
go O
travel O
go O
Spain B-LOC
. O

Tori O
be O
say O
United B-ORG
go O
return O
back O
on O
Friday B-DATE
before O
dia O
Premier O
League O
game O
against O
Chelsea B-ORG
for O
Stamford B-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
on O
Monday B-DATE
, I-DATE
17 I-DATE
February I-DATE
. O

Dis O
na O
one O
of O
di O
longest O
running O
transfers O
of O
di O
window O
and O
yes O
but O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
don O
get O
dia O
man O
- O
Bruno B-PER
Fernandes I-PER
don O
sign O
five B-DATE
- I-DATE
and I-DATE
- I-DATE
a I-DATE
- I-DATE
half I-DATE
year I-DATE
deal O
from O
Sporting B-ORG
Lisbon I-ORG
. O

United B-ORG
boss O
Ole B-PER
Gunnar I-PER
Solskjaer I-PER
say O
: O
"""" O
We O
don O
dey O
track O
Bruno B-PER
for O
many O
months O
and O
everyone O
hia O
dey O
very O
impressed O
wit O
all O
im O
attributes O
and O
wetin O
im O
go O
bring O
to O
dis O
team O
. O

Most O
importantly O
him O
na O
correct O
human O
being O
wit O
a O
great O
personality O
and O
im O
leadership O
qualities O
dey O
clear O
for O
all O
to O
see O
. O

United B-ORG
go O
pay O
initial O
fee O
of O
around O
55m O
euros O
( O
£ O
47m O
) O
for O
di O
25 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
, O
plus O
oda O
add O
- O
ons O
wey O
fit O
increase O
di O
overall O
cost O
to O
80m O
euros O
( O
£ O
67 O
. O
6m O
) O
. O

Fernandes B-PER
move O
dey O
subject O
to O
im O
medical O
and O
agreement O
of O
personal O
terms O
. O

Tori O
be O
say O
di O
two O
clubs O
don O
dey O
negotiate O
throughout O
di O
transfer O
window O
until O
Tuesday B-DATE
wey O
dem O
get O
breakthrough O
afta O
reports O
begin O
fly O
up O
and O
down O
say O
Barcelona B-ORG
sef O
dey O
interested O
. O

"""" O
Belle O
dey O
sweet O
me O
well O
- O
well O
say O
we O
don O
agree O
[ O
deal O
] O
with O
Sporting B-ORG
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
United B-ORG
manager O
Ole B-PER
Gunnar I-PER
Solskjaer I-PER
tok O
. O

Di O
negotiation O
between O
di O
club O
dey O
good O
and O
we O
know O
say O
from O
time O
, O
dis O
two O
clubs O
don O
dey O
good O
to O
each O
oda O
. O

"""" O
Now O
wey O
we O
don O
reach O
agreement O
, O
hopefully O
we O
fit O
settle O
di O
boy O
contract O
mata O
and O
finish O
im O
medical O
, O
hopefully O
we O
fit O
announce O
it O
. O
"""" O

Fernandes B-PER
join O
Sporting B-ORG
from O
Sampdoria B-ORG
for O
£ O
7 O
. O
2m O
for O
2017 B-DATE
but O
before O
den O
, O
im O
no O
really O
dey O
popular O
for O
im O
homeland O
. O
"""" O

Wetin O
surprise O
me O
be O
say O
nobody O
really O
look O
im O
side O
until O
Jorge B-PER
Jesus I-PER
, O
di O
current O
Flamengo B-ORG
boss O
decided O
to O
sign O
am O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Portuguese O
football O
writer O
Jose B-PER
Delgado I-PER
. O

"""" O
Pipo O
for O
media O
dey O
ask O
why O
Benfica B-ORG
, O
Sporting B-ORG
or O
Porto B-ORG
no O
go O
for O
Fernandes B-PER
because O
im O
be O
fantastic O
player O
. O
"""" O

Since O
2017 B-DATE
- I-DATE
18 I-DATE
season I-DATE
start O
, O
Fernandes B-PER
don O
top O
di O
Portuguese O
Primeira O
Liga O
rankings O
for O
di O
most O
goal O
involvement O
( O
67 O
) O
, O
most O
goals O
outside O
di O
penalty O
area O
( O
9 O
) O
, O
most O
chances O
created O
( O
239 O
) O
, O
most O
shots O
( O
271 O
) O
and O
most O
shots O
on O
target O
( O
114 O
) O
. O

And O
dat O
na O
before O
you O
get O
to O
di O
32 O
goals O
wey O
im O
score O
for O
all O
competitions O
last O
term O
for O
Sporting B-ORG
or O
di O
14 O
goals O
im O
score O
for O
28 O
matches O
wey O
im O
play O
for O
club O
and O
country O
dis O
season O
. O

Fernandes B-PER
na O
di O
shinning O
light O
for O
Sporting B-ORG
, O
even O
though O
im O
bin O
struggle O
and O
e O
help O
Portugal B-LOC
to O
win O
Nation O
League O
for O
June B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
- O
di O
big O
question O
now O
na O
whether O
im O
fit O
deliver O
for O
United B-ORG
? O

Na O
good O
player O
wey O
get O
potential O
to O
grow O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Italian O
football O
writer O
Danielle B-PER
Vieri I-PER
tok O
. O

Wetin O
im O
don O
do O
for O
Portugal B-LOC
don O
show O
say O
if O
fit O
do O
di O
same O
for O
bigger O
stage O
. O

Di O
pressure O
go O
increase O
, O
im O
opponents O
go O
dey O
stronger O
and O
im O
team O
- O
mates O
go O
dey O
better O
. O

"""" O
I O
no O
think O
say O
I O
fit O
say O
im O
don O
prove O
im O
self O
for O
di O
big O
European O
league O
yet O
but O
dat O
na O
di O
challenge O
. O

For O
Italy B-LOC
, O
im O
do O
well O
. O

For O
Portugal B-LOC
im O
shine O
wella O
, O
so O
now O
na O
di O
right O
time O
to O
buy O
dis O
kain O
player O
. O
"""" O

Di O
wife O
of O
late O
Kobe B-PER
Bryant I-PER
, O
Vanessa B-PER
share O
foto O
of O
her O
daughter O
Gianna B-PER
"""" I-PER
Gigi I-PER
"""" I-PER
Bryant I-PER
, O
for O
social O
media O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

For O
di O
foto O
wey O
dem O
use O
illustration O
do O
, O
her O
daughter O
wear O
Los B-ORG
Angeles I-ORG
Lakers I-ORG
jersey O
, O
with O
her O
papa O
jersey O
number O
, O
24 O
. O

Vanessa B-PER
post O
for O
her O
official O
Instagram O
say O
"""" O
she O
dey O
happy O
once O
again O
as O
she O
see O
foto O
of O
her O
'baby O
girl O
, O
' O
dey O
smile O
with O
basketball O
under O
her O
arm O
. O
"""" O

Di O
post O
don O
already O
get O
ova O
2 O
. O
3m O
likes O
. O

LA B-ORG
Lakers I-ORG
legend O
Kobe B-PER
Bryant I-PER
and O
im O
daughter O
Gianna B-PER
plus O
seven O
oda O
die O
for O
helicopter O
crash O
for O
di O
city B-LOC
of I-LOC
Calabasa I-LOC
, O
California B-LOC
on O
Sunday B-DATE
26 I-DATE
January I-DATE
. O

Kobe B-PER
and O
Vanessa B-PER
get O
four O
daughters O
togeda O
including O
Gianna B-PER
, O
wey O
be O
13 B-DATE
years I-DATE
old I-DATE
wey O
also O
die O
for O
di O
Helicopter O
crash O
. O

Dis O
her O
post O
dey O
come O
afta O
fans O
and O
celebs O
honour O
Kobe B-PER
for O
LA B-ORG
Lakers I-ORG
first O
basketball O
game O
for O
staple O
centre O
against O
Portland B-ORG
Trail I-ORG
Blazers I-ORG
. O

Football O
fans O
shock O
as O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
sign O
Nigeria B-LOC
striker O
Odion B-PER
Ighalo I-PER
from O
Chinese O
club O
Shanghai B-ORG
Shenhua I-ORG
on O
loan O
until O
di O
end O
of O
di O
season O
. O

Ighalo B-PER
deal O
with O
United B-ORG
no O
include O
option O
to O
buy O
afta O
im O
loan O
deal O
end O
wit O
di O
club O
. O

Di O
30 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
Nigerian O
player O
still O
dey O
China B-LOC
but O
dem O
expect O
am O
to O
travel O
come O
UK B-LOC
in O
di O
next O
few O
days O
. O

Ighalo B-PER
bin O
play O
for O
Watford B-ORG
for O
2014 B-DATE
and O
2017 B-DATE
wia O
im O
score O
39 O
goals O
for O
99 O
matches O
. O

Tori O
be O
say O
dis O
na O
United B-ORG
first O
senior O
loan O
signing O
since O
Radamel B-PER
Falcao I-PER
for O
2014 B-DATE
. O

Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
manager O
Ole B-PER
Gunnar I-PER
Solskjaer I-PER
say O
"""" O
Odion B-PER
na O
experienced O
player O
, O
"""" O
"""" O
Im O
go O
come O
, O
come O
give O
us O
different O
option O
to O
type O
of O
strikers O
wey O
we O
get O
for O
di O
short O
time O
wey O
im O
go O
stay O
with O
us O
. O

"""" O
Na O
correct O
pesin O
in O
be O
and O
im O
dey O
very O
professional O
, O
im O
go O
make O
use O
of O
im O
time O
here O
well O
. O
"""" O

Ighalo B-PER
move O
go O
Chinese B-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
for O
2017 B-DATE
, O
first O
with O
Changchun B-ORG
Yatai I-ORG
. O

After O
two B-DATE
seasons I-DATE
im O
move O
go O
Shanghai B-ORG
Shenhua I-ORG
and O
im O
don O
score O
10 O
times O
for O
19 O
games O
. O

United B-ORG
na O
one O
of O
di O
most O
popular O
clubs O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
as O
soon O
as O
fans O
hear O
di O
tori O
about O
Ighalo B-PER
move O
dem O
begin O
chook O
mouth O
ontop O
di O
mata O
for O
social O
media O
. O

Most O
of O
dem O
dey O
surprise O
say O
di O
Red B-ORG
Devils I-ORG
sign O
Ighalo B-PER
. O

Ighalo B-PER
na O
di O
third O
player O
wey O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
sign O
for O
dis O
January B-DATE
transfer O
window O
, O
afta O
dem O
sign O
Bruno B-PER
Fernandes I-PER
from O
Sporting B-ORG
Lisbon I-ORG
and O
Southend B-ORG
goalkeeper O
Nathan B-PER
Bishop I-PER
. O

David B-PER
Barmasai I-PER
from O
Kenya B-LOC
don O
win O
di O
2020 B-DATE
Lagos B-LOC
City O
Marathon O
. O

Oga O
Tumo B-PER
use O
two B-DATE
hour I-DATE
10 I-DATE
mins I-DATE
take O
finish O
di O
42km O
race O
wey O
start O
from O
National O
Stadium O
Surulere B-LOC
and O
end O
for O
Eko B-LOC
Atlantic I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
8 I-DATE
February I-DATE
Im O
fellow O
kontri O
woman O
Sharon B-PER
Cherop I-PER
carry O
first O
for O
female O
category O
. O

Both O
male O
and O
female O
42km O
runners O
bin O
dey O
compete O
for O
the O
grand O
prize O
of O
$ O
50 O
, O
000 O
while O
di O
second O
and O
third O
place O
winners O
go O
pocket O
$ O
40 O
, O
000 O
and O
$ O
30 O
, O
000 O
respectively O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
fourth O
edition O
of O
di O
marathon O
wey O
start O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
commercial O
capital O
city O
for O
2016 B-DATE
. O

West B-ORG
Ham I-ORG
don O
sack O
manager O
Manuel B-PER
Pellegrini I-PER
afta O
dem O
chop O
2 O
- O
1 O
home O
defeat O
at O
di O
hand O
of O
Leicester B-ORG
City I-ORG
- O
dia O
number O
9 O
loss O
for O
di O
last O
12 O
matches O
. O

Di B-ORG
Hammers I-ORG
last O
defeat O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
don O
carri O
dem O
down O
to O
17th O
position O
for O
di O
relegation O
zone O
of O
Premier O
League O
. O

Former O
West B-ORG
Ham I-ORG
boss O
David B-PER
Moyes I-PER
dey O
among O
di O
candidates O
wey O
dem O
dey O
consider O
to O
replace O
Pellegrini B-PER
. O

"""" O
Na O
wit O
great O
disappointment O
we O
don O
decide O
to O
do O
dis O
, O
"""" O
tok O
joint O
- O
chairman O
David B-PER
Sullivan I-PER
. O

"""" O
E O
don O
dey O
clear O
say O
we O
need O
change O
in O
order O
to O
bring O
di O
club O
back O
on O
track O
to O
wetin O
we O
desire O
for O
dis O
season O
. O

"""" O
We O
feel O
say O
e O
dey O
necessary O
to O
act O
now O
in O
order O
to O
give O
di O
new O
manager O
time O
to O
try O
and O
achieve O
that O
goal O
. O
"""" O

Pellegrini B-PER
lose O
im O
West B-ORG
Ham I-ORG
job O
18 B-DATE
months I-DATE
afta O
dem O
employ O
am O
for O
2018 B-DATE
on O
three B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
deal O
, O
and O
dem O
tell O
am O
about O
im O
sack O
small O
time O
afta O
e O
do O
post O
- O
match O
interview O
finish O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
. O

Na O
within O
two B-DATE
hours I-DATE
of O
losing O
to O
Leicester B-ORG
na O
im O
West B-ORG
Ham I-ORG
make O
di O
announcement O
. O

Conor B-PER
McGregor I-PER
retun O
to O
di O
octagon O
ring O
wit O
first O
- O
round O
victory O
over O
American O
fan O
favourite O
Donald B-PER
'Cowboy' I-PER
Cerrone I-PER
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
. O

Na O
just O
40 B-DATE
seconds I-DATE
McGregor B-PER
use O
defeat O
am O
. O

Irishman O
McGregor B-PER
, O
31 B-DATE
, O
claim O
victory O
for O
wetin O
sabi O
pipo O
say O
fit O
be O
im O
best O
performance O
of O
im O
career O
. O

Two O
of O
UFC B-ORG
fighters O
wey O
popular O
pass O
enta O
same O
trouser O
for O
di O
main O
event O
area O
of O
T B-LOC
- I-LOC
Mobile I-LOC
Arena I-LOC
. O

But O
referee O
Herb B-PER
Dean I-PER
step O
inside O
and O
wave O
say O
di O
contest O
contest O
don O
end O
afta O
blow O
afta O
blow O
land O
ontop O
'Cowbow' B-PER
"""" O
I O
make O
history O
tonight B-DATE
. O

I O
set O
new O
record O
. O

Na O
me O
be O
di O
first O
fighter O
in O
UFC B-ORG
history O
to O
give O
knockout O
victory O
for O
featherweight O
, O
lightweight O
and O
now O
welterweight O
- O
across O
three O
weight O
divisions O
, O
so O
I O
dey O
very O
proud O
of O
that O
, O
"""" O
tok O
McGregor B-PER
. O

Di O
last O
time O
im O
win O
inside O
UFC B-ORG
octagon O
ring O
na O
wen O
e O
get O
im O
second O
UFC B-ORG
world O
title O
for O
November B-DATE
2016 I-DATE
, O
and O
afta O
undefeated O
UFC B-ORG
lightweight O
champion O
Khabib B-PER
Nurmagomedov I-PER
defeat O
am O
for O
UFC B-ORG
229 O
for O
October B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
. O

"""" O
I O
like O
dis O
weight O
division O
. O

I O
feel O
really O
good O
. O

God O
willing O
, O
I O
come O
out O
with O
no O
injury O
. O

I O
dey O
in O
shape O
. O

Although O
, O
I O
no O
believe O
say O
I O
don O
reach O
dia O
. O

I O
still O
work O
to O
do O
to O
return O
to O
how O
I O
be O
before O
. O
"""" O

Sadio B-PER
Mane I-PER
and O
Asisat B-PER
Oshoala I-PER
na O
dem O
be O
African O
Player O
of O
di O
Year O
for O
men O
and O
women O
. O

Senegal B-LOC
and O
Liverpool B-ORG
forward O
Mane B-PER
beat O
both O
Egypt B-LOC
player O
Mohammed B-PER
Salah I-PER
and O
Algeria B-LOC
winger O
Riyad B-PER
Mahrez I-PER
to O
win O
di O
award O
wey O
dem O
do O
for O
Egypt B-LOC
on O
Tuesday B-DATE
. O

Na O
di O
first O
time O
CAF B-ORG
go O
name O
Mane B-PER
as O
di O
African O
Footballer O
of O
the O
Year O
afta O
e O
come O
out O
third O
for O
di O
two O
editions O
. O

For O
di O
women O
category O
, O
Asisat B-PER
Oshoala I-PER
beat O
Ajara B-PER
Nchout I-PER
from O
Cameroon B-LOC
and O
Thembi B-PER
Kgatlana I-PER
from O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
to O
win O
her O
fourth O
African O
Women's O
Player O
of O
the O
Year O
. O

Mohamed B-PER
Salah I-PER
( O
Egypt B-LOC
& O
Liverpool B-ORG
) O
Riyad B-PER
Mahrez I-PER
( O
Algeria B-LOC
& O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
) O
Sadio B-PER
Mane I-PER
( O
Senegal B-LOC
& O
Liverpool B-ORG
) O
- O
Winner O
Ajara B-PER
Nchout I-PER
( O
Cameroon B-LOC
& O
Valerenga B-ORG
) O
Asisat B-PER
Oshoala I-PER
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
& O
Barcelona B-ORG
) O
- O
Winner O
Thembi B-PER
Kgatlana I-PER
( O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
& O
Beijing B-ORG
Phoenix I-ORG
FC I-ORG
) O
Anice B-PER
Badri I-PER
( O
Tunisia B-LOC
& O
Esperance B-ORG
) O
Tarek B-PER
Hamed I-PER
( O
Egypt B-LOC
& O
Zamalek B-ORG
) O
Youcef B-PER
Belaïli I-PER
( O
Algeria B-LOC
& O
Esperance B-ORG
/ O
Ahli B-ORG
Jeddah I-ORG
) O
- O
Winner O
Achraf B-PER
Hakimi I-PER
( O
Morocco B-LOC
& O
Borussia B-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG
) O
- O
Winner O
Samuel B-PER
Chukwueze I-PER
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
& O
Villarreal B-ORG
) O
Victor B-PER
Osimhen I-PER
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
& O
Lille B-ORG
) O
Aliou B-PER
Cisse I-PER
( O
Senegal B-LOC
- O
Senegal B-LOC
) O
Djamel B-PER

Belmadi I-PER
( O
Algeria B-LOC
- O
Algeria B-LOC
) O
- O
Winner O
Moïne B-PER
Chaâbani I-PER
( O
Tunisia B-LOC
- O
Esperance B-ORG
) O
Alain B-PER
Djeumfa I-PER
( O
Cameroon B-LOC
) O
Desiree B-PER
Ellis I-PER
( O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
) O
- O
Winner O
Thomas B-PER
Dennerby I-PER
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
) O
Algeria B-LOC
- O
Winner O
Madagascar B-LOC
Senegal I-LOC
Cameroon I-LOC
- O
Winner O
Nigeria B-LOC
South I-LOC
Africa I-LOC
Riyad B-PER
Mahrez I-PER
goal O
against O
Nigeria B-LOC
for O
Afcon O
2019 B-DATE
semi O
final O
Kodjovi B-PER
Obilale I-PER
Egypt B-ORG
Football I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Mois B-PER
Katumbi I-PER
- O
President O
of O
TP B-ORG
Mazembe I-ORG

As O
2019 B-DATE
don O
end O
, O
Former O
Chelsea B-ORG
and O
Ghana B-LOC
star O
Michael B-PER
Essien I-PER
don O
choose O
im O
best O
11 O
African O
players O
from O
2010 B-DATE
to O
2019 B-DATE
. O

Di O
last O
10 B-DATE
years I-DATE
see O
significant O
moments O
for O
African O
football O
, O
starting O
wit O
di O
World O
Cup O
wey O
happun O
for O
di O
first O
time O
for O
African O
soil O
as O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
host O
am O
for O
2010 B-DATE
. O

Di O
decade O
also O
end O
wit O
di O
2019 B-DATE
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
wey O
hold O
for O
June B-DATE
and O
July B-DATE
for O
di O
first O
time O
instead O
of O
di O
usual O
January B-DATE
to O
February B-DATE
calendar O
. O

Essien B-PER
own O
decade O
see O
am O
win O
European O
Champions O
League O
title O
and O
one O
FA B-ORG
Cup O
wit O
Chelsea B-ORG
as O
well O
as O
runners O
- O
up O
medal O
for O
di O
2010 B-DATE
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
. O

We O
ask O
Essien B-PER
who O
be O
im O
top O
players O
from O
di O
last O
decade O
. O

Enyeama B-PER
na O
one O
of O
di O
few O
African O
goalkeepers O
to O
enjoy O
successful O
career O
for O
Europe B-LOC
. O

Im O
win O
di O
Israeli O
League O
title O
with O
Maccabi B-ORG
Tel I-ORG
Aviv I-ORG
for O
2013 B-DATE
. O

Im O
go O
on O
to O
keep O
11 O
consecutive O
clean O
sheets O
while O
with O
Lille B-ORG
and O
bin O
dey O
115 B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
away O
from O
beating O
Ligue O
1 O
all O
- O
time O
record O
of O
minutes O
- O
of O
- O
clean O
- O
sheets O
set O
by O
Gaetan B-PER
Huard I-PER
for O
1993 B-DATE
wia O
e O
play O
1 B-DATE
, I-DATE
176 I-DATE
minutes I-DATE
without O
conceding O
one O
goal O
. O

For O
national O
team O
level O
, O
Enyeama B-PER
help O
Nigeria B-LOC
win O
di O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
for O
2013 B-DATE
, O
as O
di O
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
end O
19 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
wait O
for O
di O
trophy O
. O

Vincent B-PER
Enyeama I-PER
arguably O
be O
Nigeria B-LOC
best O
player O
for O
di O
2014 B-DATE
World O
Cup O
wen O
dem O
qualify O
to O
di O
knockout O
stage O
. O

Di O
former O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
captain O
bin O
be O
key O
member O
of O
di O
Ivory B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
side O
wey O
win O
di O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
for O
2015 B-DATE
. O

For O
club O
level O
, O
he O
was O
one O
of O
di O
first O
signings O
by O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
owners O
Sheikh B-PER
Mansour I-PER
which O
serve O
as O
star O
attraction O
for O
other O
big O
name O
players O
to O
arrive O
. O

Kolo's B-PER
acquisition O
signal O
shift O
in O
power O
for O
City B-ORG
because O
im O
come O
from O
direct O
rival O
, O
Arsenal B-ORG
. O

After O
a O
stint O
with O
Liverpool B-ORG
wey O
see O
am O
reach O
di O
final O
of O
di O
Europa O
League O
im O
end O
e O
club O
career O
for O
Celtic B-ORG
, O
wia O
e O
no O
only O
did O
he O
win O
the O
Scottish O
League O
titles O
but O
also O
bin O
be O
part O
of O
di O
team O
wey O
go O
unbeaten O
for O
di O
league O
just O
as O
im O
do O
with O
Arsenal B-ORG
for O
2003 B-DATE
- I-DATE
4 I-DATE
. O

Di O
Cameroonian O
peak O
for O
Tottenham B-ORG
for O
di O
beginning O
of O
di O
decade O
and O
na O
one O
of O
di O
best O
left O
backs O
for O
Premier O
League O
under O
Harry B-PER
Redknapp I-PER
. O

E O
impressive O
performances O
na O
di O
main O
reason O
why O
Gareth B-PER
Bale I-PER
, O
wey O
be O
left O
- O
back O
before O
, O
move O
to O
play O
advanced O
role O
. O

E O
form O
deadly O
partnership O
with O
Bale B-PER
and O
dem O
become O
problem O
for O
right O
- O
backs O
for O
di O
Premier O
League O
. O

Unfortunately O
for O
Assou B-PER
- I-PER
Ekotto I-PER
, O
knee O
surgery O
mean O
say O
im O
career O
go O
pay O
di O
price O
but O
e O
be O
pesin O
wey O
pass O
expectations O
and O
become O
di O
best O
African O
left O
- O
back O
for O
Premier O
League O
. O

Benatia B-PER
bin O
be O
big O
influence O
for O
Italian O
Serie O
A O
side O
Udinese B-ORG
, O
but O
na O
for O
AS B-ORG
Roma I-ORG
wia O
di O
world O
take O
notice O
of O
am O
. O

Dem O
name O
am O
as O
di O
club O
player O
- O
of O
di O
- O
season O
for O
2014 B-DATE
before O
e O
join O
Pep B-PER
Guardiola I-PER
Bayern B-ORG
Munich I-ORG
for O
di O
end O
of O
dat O
season O
. O

Benatia B-PER
move O
to O
Juventus B-ORG
for O
2016 B-DATE
wia O
e O
help O
dem O
win O
three O
Serie O
A O
titles O
. O

Koulibaly B-PER
na O
di O
best O
defender O
for O
Italy B-LOC
for O
di O
last B-DATE
three I-DATE
seasons I-DATE
. O

Im O
help O
Senegal B-LOC
to O
reach O
dia O
first O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
final O
for O
over O
10 B-DATE
years I-DATE
dis O
year O
and O
many O
pipo O
regard O
am O
as O
one O
of O
di O
best O
centre O
- O
backs O
for O
modern O
day O
football O
. O

Di O
only O
reason O
e O
still O
dey O
Napoli B-ORG
na O
say O
di O
club O
owner O
turn O
down O
many O
offers O
from O
top O
European O
outfits O
so O
far O
. O

Essien B-PER
prowess O
begin O
to O
die O
down O
just O
for O
di O
turn O
of O
di O
decade O
with O
injuries O
taking O
dia O
toll O
but O
e O
bin O
still O
dey O
important O
for O
Ghana B-LOC
as O
dem O
qualify O
for O
di O
World O
Cup O
for O
2014 B-DATE
and O
- O
e O
insists O
say O
im O
deserve O
place O
for O
e O
team O
of O
di O
decade O
! O

For O
club O
level O
im O
play O
key O
role O
and O
help O
spark O
di O
come O
- O
back O
against O
Napoli B-ORG
which O
help O
Chelsea B-ORG
win O
dia O
first O
Champions O
League O
for O
2012 B-DATE
. O

Yaya B-PER
don O
win O
di O
Confederation B-ORG
of I-ORG
African I-ORG
Football I-ORG
( O
Caf B-ORG
) O
African O
Player O
of O
the O
Year O
award O
four O
times O
in O
di O
last O
10 B-DATE
years I-DATE
. O

E O
also O
score O
79 O
goals O
for O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
, O
di O
most O
by O
any O
midfielder O
for O
di O
club O
during O
dat O
period O
. O

Toure B-PER
win O
di O
Premier O
League O
three O
times O
, O
one O
FA B-ORG
Cup O
, O
two O
League O
Cups O
and O
before O
e O
move O
to O
England B-LOC
e O
bin O
don O
win O
di O
2010 B-DATE
La O
Liga O
with O
Barcelona B-ORG
. O

E O
also O
captain O
Ivory B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
to O
dia O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
crown O
for O
2015 B-DATE
. O

Di O
Liverpool B-ORG
star O
don O
be O
breath O
of O
fresh O
air O
for O
di O
last O
few O
years O
and O
many O
see O
am O
as O
one O
of O
di O
best O
players O
of O
dis O
generation O
. O

E O
don O
score O
73 O
goals O
to O
help O
Jurgen B-PER
Klopp I-PER
men O
and O
bin O
dey O
instrumental O
in O
helping O
dem O
reach O
two O
European O
Champions O
League O
finals O
, O
winning O
di O
last O
edition O
. O

From O
im O
days O
for O
Salzburg B-ORG
through O
to O
Southampton B-ORG
and O
Liverpool B-ORG
- O
plus O
e O
performances O
for O
di O
national O
team O
- O
im O
don O
score O
more O
than O
150 O
career O
goals O
with O
more O
than O
60 O
assists O
. O

Di O
"""" O
Egyptian O
King O
"""" O
na O
di O
only O
African O
player O
to O
make O
di O
Fifa B-ORG
Best O
top O
3 O
dis O
decade O
. O

Salah B-PER
don O
exceed O
expectations O
for O
Liverpool B-ORG
wia O
e O
win O
di O
Premier O
League O
Golden O
Boot O
for O
di O
two B-DATE
seasons I-DATE
with O
di O
club O
so O
far O
. O

Im O
be O
di O
reigning O
Caf B-ORG
footballer O
of O
di O
year O
afta O
im O
retain O
di O
crown O
for O
2019 B-DATE
. O

Mohamed B-PER
Salah I-PER
don O
net O
more O
than O
202 O
goals O
for O
club O
and O
kontri O
dis O
decade O
. O

For O
di O
beginning O
of O
di O
decade O
Drogba B-PER
reach O
im O
career O
high O
of O
37 O
goals O
to O
help O
Chelsea B-ORG
win O
domestic O
Cup O
double O
and O
also O
win O
e O
second O
Premier O
League O
Golden O
Boot O
. O

For O
di O
year O
2012 B-DATE
, O
Didier B-PER
Drogba I-PER
cement O
e O
legendary O
status O
for O
European O
football O
as O
im O
score O
di O
equaliser O
and O
di O
winning O
penalty O
as O
Chelsea B-ORG
lift O
di O
European O
Champions O
League O
for O
di O
first O
time O
ever O
. O

E O
trophy O
winning O
continue O
afta O
e O
leave O
Chelsea B-ORG
with O
three O
more O
for O
Turkey B-LOC
as O
e O
help O
Galatasaray B-ORG
win O
di O
league O
, O
FA B-ORG
Cup O
and O
Super O
Cup O
. O

As O
e O
end O
im O
career O
for O
north B-LOC
America I-LOC
e O
show O
say O
e O
still O
get O
dat O
scoring O
touch O
for O
body O
as O
e O
finish O
as O
top O
- O
scorer O
for O
Major O
League O
Soccer O
side O
Montreal B-ORG
Impact I-ORG
and O
den O
made O
it O
into O
The O
MLS O
All O
- O
Star O
team O
one B-DATE
year I-DATE
later O
. O

Arguably O
di O
greatest O
African O
Player O
of O
all O
time O
, O
Samuel B-PER
Eto'o I-PER
win O
e O
second O
treble O
for O
di O
start O
of O
di O
decade O
with O
Inter B-ORG
Milan I-ORG
under O
Jose B-PER
Mourinho I-PER
. O

Di O
following O
season O
e O
be O
Inter B-ORG
Milan I-ORG
top O
scorer O
with O
37 O
goals O
as O
dem O
win O
Fifa B-ORG
Club O
World O
Cup O
and O
Coppa O
Italia O
. O

Those O
feats O
see O
am O
win O
di O
fourth O
of O
e O
Caf B-ORG
African O
Player O
of O
the O
Year O
awards O
for O
2010 B-DATE
. O

Im O
move O
to O
England B-LOC
for O
di O
end O
of O
e O
career O
, O
and O
even O
though O
e O
no O
shine O
at O
dat O
point O
e O
still O
manage O
one O
memorable O
hat O
- O
trick O
for O
Chelsea B-ORG
against O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
. O

"""" O
I O
no O
go O
fit O
continue O
to O
play O
like O
dat O
"""" O
dis O
na O
wetin O
Seven O
time O
champion O
Serena B-PER
Williams I-PER
tok O
afta O
she O
crash O
comot O
from O
Australian O
Open O
on O
Friday B-DATE
morning I-DATE
and O
lose O
6 O
- O
4 O
6 O
- O
7 O
( O
2 O
- O
7 O
) O
7 O
- O
5 O
to O
Wang B-PER
Qiang I-PER
from O
China B-LOC
for O
third O
round O
. O

"""" O
I O
no O
fit O
play O
like O
dat O
. O

I O
literally O
no O
fit O
do O
dat O
again O
. O

E O
dey O
unprofessional O
. O

E O
no O
dey O
cool O
. O
"""" O

Senera B-PER
tok O
As O
e O
be O
so O
Serena B-PER
search O
for O
her O
24th O
grand O
slam O
title O
go O
continue O
. O

Wang B-PER
bin O
dey O
serve O
for O
di O
match O
when O
di O
game O
dey O
5 O
- O
4 O
but O
Williams B-PER
broke O
her O
for O
di O
first O
time O
come O
win O
di O
tie O
- O
break O
to O
level O
di O
game O
. O

Di O
28 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
Wang B-PER
wey O
be O
number O
27th O
seed O
for O
world O
tennis O
ranking O
, O
recover O
come O
seal O
victory O
for O
her O
third O
match O
point O
. O

Wen O
tori O
pipo O
ask O
Serena B-PER
wetin O
she O
think O
afta O
di O
game O
, O
she O
say O
"""" O
I O
honestly O
no O
think O
say O
I O
go O
lose O
datat O
match O
. O
"""" O

She O
add O
say O
"""" O
I O
just O
make O
far O
too O
many O
errors O
to O
be O
professional O
athlete O
today B-DATE
. O
"""" O

Tori O
be O
say O
dis B-DATE
Friday I-DATE
defeat O
na O
Serena B-PER
earliest O
exit O
for O
Australian O
Open O
since B-DATE
2006 I-DATE
, O
when O
she O
lose O
for O
dis O
stage O
to O
Daniela B-PER
Hantuchova I-PER
. O

Dis O
na O
Williams B-PER
23rd B-DATE
year I-DATE
as O
professional O
tennis O
player O
and O
she O
still O
dey O
eye O
Margaret B-PER
Court I-PER
record O
of O
24 O
grand O
slam O
singles O
titles O
. O

Di O
last O
time O
wey O
38 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
Serena B-PER
win O
grand O
slam O
na O
2017 B-DATE
when O
she O
beat O
her O
sister O
for O
Australian O
Open O
final O
to O
win O
her O
23rd O
title O
and O
na O
di O
same B-DATE
year I-DATE
she O
born O
her O
daughter O
too O
. O

Leicester B-ORG
manage O
to O
match O
brake O
for O
di O
ginger O
wey O
Brentford B-ORG
carri O
come O
for O
second O
half O
of O
dem O
two O
FA B-ORG
Cup O
fourth O
round O
match O
. O

Kelechi B-PER
Iheanacho I-PER
score O
di O
only O
goal O
of O
di O
game O
afta O
just O
four B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
when O
e O
tap O
in O
cross O
from O
full O
- O
back O
James B-PER
Justin I-PER
. O

Leicester B-ORG
na O
di O
better O
team O
for O
first O
half O
and O
Ayoze B-PER
Perez I-PER
suppose O
don O
score O
di O
second O
goal O
from O
Iheanacho B-PER
pass O
but O
Brentford B-ORG
keeper O
Luke B-PER
Daniels I-PER
make O
ogbonge O
save O
. O

Afta O
di O
game O
Kelechi B-PER
Iheanacho I-PER
carrri O
di O
award O
for O
Man O
of O
the O
Match O
. O

E O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
MOTD I-ORG
: O
"""" O
We O
dey O
happy O
for O
di O
win O
today B-DATE
and O
to O
go O
to O
di O
next O
round O
. O

Di O
oda O
team O
worry O
us O
well O
well O
. O

"""" O
E O
dey O
very O
important O
as O
one O
team O
and O
as O
one O
group O
of O
players O
. O

We O
work O
really O
hard O
to O
di O
end O
and O
stand O
our O
ground O
. O

Fear O
catch O
me O
small O
because O
dem O
just O
dey O
come O
dey O
come O
. O

We O
defend O
well O
and O
in O
di O
end O
we O
win O
and O
we O
dey O
go O
through O
. O
"""" O

Ogbonge O
football O
fans O
dey O
get O
one O
kain O
deep O
level O
of O
physical O
stress O
wen O
dem O
dey O
watch O
dia O
team O
dey O
play O
and O
dem O
fit O
give O
diasef O
heart O
attack O
, O
na O
so O
research O
tok O
. O

Di O
Oxford B-ORG
study O
test O
saliva O
from O
Brazilian O
fans O
wen O
dem O
lose O
to O
Germany B-LOC
for O
di O
2014 B-DATE
World O
Cup O
. O

Dem O
find O
levels O
of O
di O
hormone O
cortisol O
wey O
bin O
go O
up O
for O
dia O
bodi O
during O
di O
7 O
- O
1 O
home O
defeat O
for O
di O
semi O
- O
final O
. O

Dis O
one O
dey O
very O
dangerous O
as O
e O
dey O
increase O
blood O
pressure O
and O
e O
dey O
put O
pressure O
for O
di O
heart O
. O

Di O
researchers O
no O
find O
any O
difference O
for O
di O
stress O
levels O
between O
men O
and O
women O
during O
di O
game O
, O
despite O
say O
pipo O
dey O
tink O
say O
men O
dey O
like O
football O
pass O
women O
. O

"""" O
Fans O
wey O
too O
join O
togeda O
emotionally O
with O
dia O
team O
, O
wey O
get O
strong O
sense O
say O
dem O
be O
one O
with O
dia O
team O
dey O
experience O
di O
greatest O
psychological O
stress O
response O
wen O
dem O
dey O
watch O
match O
"""" O
, O
Dr O
Martha B-PER
Newson I-PER
, O
researcher O
for O
di O
Centre B-ORG
for I-ORG
di I-ORG
Study I-ORG
of I-ORG
Social I-ORG
Cohesion I-ORG
for O
Oxford B-ORG
tok O
. O

"""" O
Fans O
wey O
be O
casual O
supporters O
dey O
also O
experience O
stress O
but O
e O
no O
dey O
serious O
like O
dat O
. O
"""" O

High O
levels O
of O
cortisol O
wey O
don O
tey O
for O
bodi O
fit O
: O
Cortisol O
wey O
don O
raise O
fit O
also O
give O
pipo O
di O
feeling O
say O
bad O
tin O
wan O
happun O
, O
say O
dia O
life O
dey O
in O
danger O
and O
dem O
dey O
under O
attack O
. O

Former O
research O
don O
show O
say O
heart O
attack O
among O
fans O
wen O
dia O
team O
dey O
play O
important O
match O
dey O
increases O
weda O
dem O
dey O
support O
di O
club O
or O
dia O
kontri O
. O

For O
dia O
study O
, O
di O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oxford I-ORG
sabi O
pipo O
don O
track O
cortisol O
levels O
for O
40 O
fans' O
saliva O
before O
, O
during O
and O
afta O
three O
World O
Cup O
match O
. O

Di O
one O
wey O
dey O
stressful O
pass O
na O
di O
semi O
- O
final O
. O

"""" O
Na O
match O
wey O
dem O
waya O
dem O
- O
so O
many O
pipo O
comot O
dey O
cry O
, O
"""" O
Dr O
Newson B-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
News I-ORG
. O

But O
di O
fans O
don O
use O
coping O
strategies O
like O
jokes O
and O
hugs O
to O
reduce O
dia O
stress O
before O
dem O
bring O
am O
down O
to O
di O
pre O
- O
match O
level O
wen O
dem O
blow O
di O
final O
whistle O
. O

Dr O
Newson B-PER
suggest O
say O
make O
stadiums O
dey O
dim O
light O
, O
play O
music O
wey O
dey O
calm O
bodi O
afta O
games O
wey O
no O
go O
well O
. O

"""" O
Clubs O
fit O
dey O
do O
heart O
screening O
or O
oda O
health O
measures O
for O
dia O
fans O
wey O
dey O
committed O
because O
na O
dem O
dey O
at O
risk O
to O
experience O
stress O
during O
di O
game O
, O
"""" O
she O
add O
. O

On O
8 B-DATE
January I-DATE
2010 I-DATE
, O
di O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
for O
Angola B-LOC
bin O
only O
remain O
few O
days O
before O
e O
start O
. O

I O
bin O
dey O
di O
province O
of O
Cabinda B-LOC
, O
dey O
prepare O
to O
cover O
Group O
B O
for O
di O
BBC B-ORG
World I-ORG
Service I-ORG
, O
and O
bin O
also O
dey O
in O
charge O
of O
handing O
ova O
di O
BBC B-ORG
African O
Footballer O
of O
the O
Year O
trophy O
to O
di O
newly O
- O
crowned O
winner O
, O
Ivory B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
captain O
Didier B-PER
Drogba I-PER
. O

As O
di O
day O
waka O
dey O
go O
, O
unconfam O
reports O
of O
shooting O
, O
wey O
involve O
Togo B-LOC
national O
team O
, O
start O
to O
fly O
evriwia O
. O

Di O
detail O
bin O
no O
clear O
, O
but O
e O
clear O
say O
sometin O
serious O
don O
happun O
. O

How O
serious O
di O
tin O
be O
show O
wen O
I O
meet O
di O
squad O
as O
dem O
dey O
return O
to O
dia O
hotel O
for O
Cabinda B-LOC
city I-LOC
. O

I O
ask O
to O
speak O
to O
someone O
, O
dem O
immediately O
tell O
me O
say O
di O
team O
tok O
- O
tok O
pesin O
na O
dia O
best O
- O
known O
player O
- O
wey O
be O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
star O
Emmanuel B-PER
Adebayor I-PER
. O

Wen O
e O
siddon O
to O
tok O
, O
e O
give O
shocking O
details O
of O
di O
attack O
wey O
kill O
two O
members O
of O
di O
Togo B-LOC
delegation O
and O
result O
in O
life O
changing O
injuries O
to O
some O
odas O
. O

10 B-DATE
years I-DATE
afta O
, O
dis O
na O
di O
tori O
from O
team O
members O
wey O
make O
global O
headlines O
and O
wetin O
happun O
afta O
. O

Togo B-LOC
squad O
bin O
dey O
in O
good O
spirits O
days O
before O
di O
2010 B-DATE
Nations O
Cup O
. O

Dem O
just O
qualify O
back O
for O
di O
tournament O
afta O
dem O
miss O
out O
for O
2008 B-DATE
and O
bin O
dey O
prepare O
to O
take O
on O
group O
wey O
feature O
some O
of O
di O
biggest O
names O
for O
African O
football O
- O
Drogba B-PER
Ivory B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
and O
Michael B-PER
Essien I-PER
Ghana B-LOC
bin O
dey O
di O
same O
group O
. O

Before O
di O
tournament O
, O
Togo B-LOC
decide O
to O
camp O
for O
Pointe B-LOC
Noir I-LOC
for O
Republic B-LOC
of I-LOC
Congo I-LOC
, O
just O
over O
100km O
from O
wia O
dem O
go O
play O
dia O
group O
games O
for O
Angola B-LOC
city O
of O
Cabinda B-LOC
. O

Cabinda B-LOC
dey O
separate O
from O
di O
rest O
of O
Angola B-LOC
, O
and O
instead O
of O
di O
Togo B-LOC
suad O
to O
fly O
from O
wia O
dem O
dey O
to O
di O
capital O
Luanda B-LOC
and O
den O
fly O
back O
north O
again O
, O
dem O
choose O
to O
drive O
. O

Dis O
decision O
later O
end O
with O
bad O
result O
. O

Afta O
di O
suqad O
relax O
in O
di O
evening B-DATE
, O
di O
night B-DATE
before I-DATE
- O
dem O
travel O
go O
di O
border O
. O

Players O
bin O
just O
dey O
laugh O
and O
joking O
amongst O
demselves O
for O
di O
bus O
. O
