Empaka O O O
zaakubeera O O O
mu O O O
kibuga O O O
Liverpool B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
e O O O
Bungereza B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
okutandika O O O
nga O O O
July B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
12 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
. O O O

Liigi O O O
bweneeyongeramu O O O
okuvuganya O O O
, O O O
tujja O O O
kufuna O O O
abazannyi O O O
abalungi O O O
mu O O O
mpaka O O O
ezokunsulamu O O O
eziribeera O O O
mu O O O
South B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Afrika I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
, O O O
Dhamuzungu B-PER B-PER B-PER
bwe O O O
yannyonnyodde O O O
. O O O

City B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Oilers I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
ne O O O
Falcon B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
be O O O
bakyasinze O O O
okuwangula O O O
ekikopo O O O
kino O O O
emirundi O O O
mukaaga O O O
buli O O O
omu O O O
. O O O

VVC B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
eyabakyala O O O
yebadde O O O
ekyali O O O
ku O O O
ntikko O O O
bwe O O O
yakwataekyomusanvu O O O
mu O O O
2014 B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
. O O O

Mu O O O
mpaka O O O
zino O O O
ezeetabiddwamu O O O
abazannyi O O O
370 O O O
okuva O O O
mu O O O
masomero O O O
34 O O O
, O O O
Naluwooza B-PER B-PER B-PER
yakubye O O O
Fadilah B-PER B-PER B-PER
Shamika I-PER I-PER I-PER
mu O O O
bemyaka B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
15 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ne O O O
19 B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
, O O O
sso O O O
nga O O O
mu O O O
balenzi O O O
abemyaka B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
19 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, O O O
Muzafar B-PER B-PER B-PER
Lubega I-PER I-PER I-PER
Kakungulu B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Memorial I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
yakubye O O O
Augustus B-PER B-PER B-PER
Owiny I-PER I-PER I-PER
owa O O O
Kibuli B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
SSS I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
, O O O
ate O O O
Samuel B-PER B-PER B-PER
Wasswa I-PER I-PER I-PER
owa O O O
Kibuli B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
nawangula O O O
Paul B-PER B-PER B-PER
Makande I-PER I-PER I-PER
owa O O O
Kakungulu B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
, O O O
mu O O O
bemyaka B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
15 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
. O O O

Sizoni B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
ewedde I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
baamalira O O O
mu O O O
kyamwenda O O O
ku O O O
ttiimu O O O
21 O O O
. O O O

Sizoni B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
ewedde I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
baamalira O O O
mu O O O
kyamwenda O O O
ku O O O
ttiimu O O O
21 O O O
. O O O

Abayizi O O O
576 O O O
be O O O
beetabye O O O
mu O O O
mizannyo O O O
gino O O O
. O O O

Pulezidenti O O O
wekibiina O O O
ekivunaanyizibwa O O O
ku O O O
muzannyo O O O
guno O O O
, O O O
ekya O O O
Uganda B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Weightlifting I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Federation I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
UWF I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
, O O O
Salim B-PER B-PER B-PER
Musoke I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
ye O O O
yakwasizza O O O
abazannyi O O O
bendeera O O O
e O O O
Lugogo B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
nabakuutira O O O
obutabulira O O O
mu O O O
Amerika B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Sizoni B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
ewedde I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
yaleeta O O O
Brian B-PER B-PER B-PER
Sivachi I-PER I-PER I-PER
okuva O O O
mu O O O
Nkumba B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
, O O O
Geoffrey B-PER B-PER B-PER
Soro I-PER I-PER I-PER
KIU B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
, O O O
Mike B-PER B-PER B-PER
Madol I-PER I-PER I-PER
UCU B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Canons I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
, O O O
Amin B-PER B-PER B-PER
Mkhosa I-PER I-PER I-PER
Savio B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
, O O O
Tanzania B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Philip B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ameny I-PER I-PER I-PER
Warriors B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
, O O O
Stephen B-PER B-PER B-PER
Wundi I-PER I-PER I-PER
UCU B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Canons I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
ne O O O
David B-PER B-PER B-PER
Opolot I-PER I-PER I-PER
okuva O O O
mu O O O
Our B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Savior I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
wabula O O O
era O O O
liigi O O O
negaana O O O
. O O O

Leero B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
ku I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
Lwokuna I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
nga I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
February I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
28 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, O O O
oluzannya O O O
olwokubiri O O O
lwe O O O
luggyibwako O O O
akawuuwo O O O
e O O O
Mengo B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
mu O O O
Kisenyi B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Babu B-PER B-PER B-PER
yawangudde O O O
omudaali O O O
gwa O O O
zaabu O O O
mu O O O
mpaka O O O
za O O O
National O O O
Boxing O O O
Open O O O
Championship O O O
. O O O

Abalala O O O
abali O O O
ku O O O
kakiiko O O O
kuliko O O O
Sophie B-PER B-PER B-PER
Najjemba I-PER I-PER I-PER
omumyuka O O O
wa O O O
pulezidenti O O O
ku O O O
byobukulembeze O O O
nebyensimbi O O O
, O O O
Rogers B-PER B-PER B-PER
Mulundo I-PER I-PER I-PER
omukwanaganya O O O
, O O O
Adam B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ssegawa I-PER I-PER I-PER
muwandiisi O O O
, O O O
Sarah B-PER B-PER B-PER
Namaganda I-PER I-PER I-PER
mumyuka O O O
womuwandiis O O O
, O O O
Shakirah B-PER B-PER B-PER
Nalweyiso I-PER I-PER I-PER
byansimbi O O O
, O O O
Tom B-PER B-PER B-PER
Matovu I-PER I-PER I-PER
mawulire O O O
, O O O
Hakim B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kasirye I-PER I-PER I-PER
byantambula O O O
, O O O
Henry B-PER B-PER B-PER
Mutebi I-PER I-PER I-PER
akiikirira O O O
abayizi O O O
abasajja O O O
, O O O
Gladys B-PER B-PER B-PER
Nakazzi I-PER I-PER I-PER
byampisa O O O
ne O O O
Lillian B-PER B-PER B-PER
Namaganda I-PER I-PER I-PER
akiikirira O O O
abayizi O O O
abakyala O O O
. O O O

Gyebuvuddeko O O O
, O O O
Muhangi B-PER B-PER B-PER
yeemulugunya O O O
ku O O O
ngabanya O O O
yensimbi O O O
mu O O O
bibiina O O O
byemizannyo O O O
ebyenjawulo O O O
, O O O
nagamba O O O
nti O O O
si O O O
kya O O O
bwenkanya O O O
FUFA B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
okutwala O O O
obuwumbi O O O
10 O O O
ku O O O
17 O O O
nobukadde O O O
400 O O O
, O O O
Gavume O O O
nti O O O
ze O O O
yatadde O O O
mu O O O
bajeti O O O
yomwaka B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
201920 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
. O O O

Empaka O O O
zokusunsulamu O O O
mu O O O
distulikiti O O O
zigenda O O O
mu O O O
maaso O O O
, O O O
ngezakamalirizo O O O
ezeggwanga O O O
lyonna O O O
zaakubeerayo O O O
wakati O O O
wa O O O
May B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
4 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ne I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
11 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, O O O
ku O O O
Mbale B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
SS I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
. O O O

Nsubuga B-PER B-PER B-PER
yeebazizza O O O
Gabunga B-PER B-PER B-PER
olwokumulinnyisa O O O
amadaala O O O
, O O O
nawera O O O
nga O O O
bwatagenda O O O
kumuswaza O O O
. O O O

Bazzaako O O O
Ajax B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Queens I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
ku O O O
Ssande B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
nga I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
December I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
9 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
. O O O

Ruth B-PER B-PER B-PER
Meeme I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Halima B-PER B-PER B-PER
Nakachwa I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Peace B-PER B-PER B-PER
Proscovia I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Rachael B-PER B-PER B-PER
Nanyonga I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Stella B-PER B-PER B-PER
Nanfuka I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Lilian B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ajio I-PER I-PER I-PER
ne O O O
Muhayimina B-PER B-PER B-PER
Namuwaya I-PER I-PER I-PER
be O O O
baazannye O O O
. O O O

Harcleroad B-PER B-PER B-PER
yomu O O O
ku O O O
bannabyamizannyo O O O
abalina O O O
ekitone O O O
ekyenjawulo O O O
era O O O
azze O O O
kuzza O O O
muzannyo O O O
gwaffe O O O
ku O O O
ntikko O O O
, O O O
Mubiru B-PER B-PER B-PER
bwe O O O
yategeezezza O O O
. O O O

Emitendera O O O
okuli O O O
oguddirira O O O
ogwabakafulu O O O
MX2 O O O
, O O O
ogwokuna O O O
MX O O O
85cc O O O
nogwokutaano O O O
MX O O O
65cc O O O
, O O O
gye O O O
gisinga O O O
okubaamu O O O
okuvuganya O O O
okwamaanyi O O O
. O O O

Ennyumba O O O
ya O O O
Mars O O O
, O O O
ye O O O
yawangudde O O O
neweebwa O O O
sseddume O O O
wente O O O
, O O O
ekikopo O O O
nebirabo O O O
ebirala O O O
. O O O

Nkumba B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ne O O O
Ndejje B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
zaakukiikirira O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
mu O O O
mpaka O O O
za O O O
African O O O
Women O O O
Volleyball O O O
Championship O O O
omwaka B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
ogujja I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
. O O O

Omusawo O O O
ye O O O
Habiba B-PER B-PER B-PER
Anguyo I-PER I-PER I-PER
ngekibinja O O O
kikulembeddwa O O O
Jackson B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kavuma I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
akola O O O
nga O O O
maneja O O O
. O O O

Jimmy B-PER B-PER B-PER
Enabu I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
kapiteeni O O O
wa O O O
City B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Oilers I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
, O O O
ye O O O
yasinze O O O
okukolera O O O
ttiimu O O O
obugoba O O O
obungi O O O
18 O O O
naddirirwa O O O
Josh B-PER B-PER B-PER
Johnson I-PER I-PER I-PER
17 O O O
, O O O
ate O O O
Paul B-PER B-PER B-PER
Odong I-PER I-PER I-PER
ku O O O
ludda O O O
lwa O O O
Betway B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Power I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
nakola O O O
13 O O O
. O O O

Phillip B-PER B-PER B-PER
Wokorach I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Justin B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kimono I-PER I-PER I-PER
ne O O O
Adrian B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kisito I-PER I-PER I-PER
be O O O
bamu O O O
ku O O O
baayambye O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
eyawangula O O O
empala O O O
zino O O O
omwaka B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
oguwedde I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, O O O
okuva O O O
emabeganefuna O O O
obuwanguzi O O O
. O O O

Kino O O O
kye O O O
kiruubirirwa O O O
kya O O O
City B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Oilers I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
, O O O
eyagala O O O
okuwangula O O O
ensiike O O O
eyookutaano O O O
ku O O O
Ssande B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
, O O O
erangirirwe O O O
ku O O O
buwanguzi O O O
. O O O

Joy B-PER B-PER B-PER
Chemutai I-PER I-PER I-PER
yakoledde O O O
KCCA B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
obugoba O O O
20 O O O
, O O O
Martha B-PER B-PER B-PER
Soigi I-PER I-PER I-PER
16 O O O
, O O O
Sylvia B-PER B-PER B-PER
Nakazibwe I-PER I-PER I-PER
10 O O O
ate O O O
Stella B-PER B-PER B-PER
Nikuze I-PER I-PER I-PER
yalwanye O O O
nafunira O O O
A1 B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Challenge I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
obugoba O O O
13 O O O
, O O O
Charline B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ursula I-PER I-PER I-PER
ne O O O
Priscilla B-PER B-PER B-PER
Sheila I-PER I-PER I-PER
8 O O O
buli O O O
omu O O O
. O O O

Ye O O O
kapiteeni O O O
Michael B-PER B-PER B-PER
Okorach I-PER I-PER I-PER
ategeezezza O O O
nti O O O
bamaze O O O
mu O O O
nkambi O O O
wiiki B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
bbiri I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
nga O O O
beetegekera O O O
empaka O O O
zino O O O
, O O O
era O O O
tebagenda O O O
kuyiwa O O O
Bannayuganda O O O
. O O O

Ebyabakazi O O O
yeeddizza O O O
ekikopo O O O
kye O O O
yali O O O
yatwala O O O
omwaka B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
oguwedde I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ne O O O
kimeeme O O O
wembuzi O O O
, O O O
neyabasajja O O O
netwalaekikopo O O O
ne O O O
4 O O O
, O O O
000 O O O
, O O O
000 O O O
. O O O

Valtteri B-PER B-PER B-PER
Bottas I-PER I-PER I-PER
yakutte O O O
kyakubiri O O O
, O O O
Verstappen B-PER B-PER B-PER
kyakusatu O O O
, O O O
Daniel B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ricciardo I-PER I-PER I-PER
kyakuna O O O
, O O O
Kimi B-PER B-PER B-PER
Raikkonen I-PER I-PER I-PER
kyakutaano O O O
, O O O
Vettel B-PER B-PER B-PER
kyamukaaga O O O
. O O O

Emizannyo O O O
gikomekkerezebwa O O O
nga O O O
October B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
18 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
. O O O

Okufuna O O O
omuwanguzi O O O
wa O O O
sizoni B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
eno I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, O O O
balina O O O
kuzannya O O O
fayinolo O O O
za O O O
mirundu O O O
musanvu O O O
. O O O

Bannabyamizannyo O O O
abalala O O O
abaasiimiddwa O O O
kuliko O O O
ttiimu O O O
yomupiira O O O
eya O O O
Crested B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Cranes I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
eyakutte O O O
ekyokusatu O O O
mu O O O
mpaka O O O
ezaabadde O O O
e O O O
South B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Afrika I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
, O O O
omuzannyi O O O
wa O O O
Golf O O O
omukyala O O O
Martha B-PER B-PER B-PER
Babirye I-PER I-PER I-PER
eyakutte O O O
ekyokubiri O O O
mu O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Open O O O
, O O O
ttiimu O O O
ya O O O
Rugby O O O
eya O O O
Black B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Pirates I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
eyawangudde O O O
eza O O O
Makerere O B-ORG O
Sevens O O O
nomuvuzi O O O
wa O O O
mmotoka O O O
zempaka O O O
Hassan B-PER B-PER B-PER
Alwi I-PER I-PER I-PER
eyawangudde O O O
eza O O O
Kabalega O O O
Rally O O O
. O O O

Amasomero O O O
agayitiddwa O O O
okwetabamu O O O
ye O O O
Trinity B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Senior I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Academy I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
, O O O
Kisubi B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
High I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
, O O O
Turkish B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Light I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Academy I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
, O O O
Bethel B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Covenant I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Academy I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
, O O O
Elite B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
High I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
School I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
, O O O
Watoto B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ne O O O
MST B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Junior I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Academy I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
. O O O

Singa O O O
Hamilton B-PER B-PER B-PER
awangula O O O
empaka O O O
ezo O O O
, O O O
waakwongera O O O
okusemberera O O O
engule O O O
yomwaka B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
guno I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
. O O O

Omuzannyo O O O
guno O O O
gwakamala O O O
emyaka B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
ena I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
mu O O O
ggwanga O O O
nga O O O
gusinga O O O
kwettanirwa O O O
masomero O O O
ga O O O
siniya O O O
. O O O

Bungereza B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
yeyasooka O O O
okuwangula O O O
ekikopo O O O
kino O O O
mu O O O
2014 B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
ekyali O O O
e O O O
South B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Africa I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
, O O O
South B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Africa I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
nekitwala O O O
mu O O O
2016 B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
e O O O
Miyami B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ate O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
yensi O O O
esoose O O O
okutegeka O O O
empka O O O
zino O O O
netwala O O O
nekikopo O O O
2018 B-DATE B-DATE O
. O O O

Ku O O O
ttiimu O O O
zino O O O
kuliko O O O
Busujju B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
, O O O
Ssingo B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
, O O O
Buweekula B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
e O O O
Buddu B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

City B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Oilers I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
be O O O
balina O O O
ekikopo O O O
kyomwaka B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
oguwedde I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
era O O O
nga O O O
baakakiwangula O O O
emirundi O O O
5 O O O
egyomuddiringanwa O O O
ate O O O
nga O O O
KIU B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
enoonya O O O
kisooka O O O
. O O O

Omubaka O O O
wa O O O
Bufalansa B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
mu O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Stephanie B-PER B-PER B-PER
Rivoal I-PER I-PER I-PER
yagambye O O O
ebisaawe O O O
bino O O O
tebigenda O O O
kukoma O O O
ku O O O
kuyamba O O O
bayizi O O O
bokka O O O
, O O O
wabula O O O
nabantu O O O
abalala O O O
abalinaanye O O O
amasomero O O O
. O O O

Eno O O O
ye O O O
semi O O O
esoose O O O
, O O O
nga O O O
baakuzannya O O O
emirundi O O O
etaano O O O
okufunako O O O
anaakwatagana O O O
nomuwanguzi O O O
wakati O O O
wa O O O
Betway B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Powers I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
ne O O O
JKL B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Men I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
. O O O

Eno O O O
ye O O O
semi O O O
esoose O O O
wabula O O O
nga O O O
baakuzannya O O O
emirundi O O O
etaano O O O
okufunako O O O
agenda O O O
ku O O O
Fayinolo O O O
ya O O O
Basketball O O O
sizoni B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
eno I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
. O O O

Amawanga O O O
ageetabye O O O
mu O O O
mpaka O O O
kuliko O O O
Nigeria B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Kenya B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Zimbabwe B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ne O O O
Namibia B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

City B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Oilers I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
be O O O
balina O O O
ekikopo O O O
kya O O O
sizoni B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
ewedde I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
era O O O
nga O O O
baakakiwangula O O O
emirundi O O O
5 O O O
egyomuddiringanwa O O O
. O O O

Eno O O O
ye O O O
sizoni B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
eyo I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
7 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
nga O O O
K B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
. I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
U I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
ne O O O
MUBS B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
bagiwangudde O O O
emirundi O O O
2 O O O
buli O O O
omu O O O
, O O O
UMU B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ne O O O
MUK B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
omulundi O O O
gumu O O O
ate O O O
abalala O O O
banoonya O O O
kisooka O O O
. O O O

Ate O O O
mu O O O
nsitaano O O O
eyabadde O O O
ku O O O
Vox B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Lounge I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
e O O O
Makindye B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
abazannyi O O O
munaana O O O
okuli O O O
Martin B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ssenyonjo I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Moses B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ssesanga I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Bashir B-PER B-PER B-PER
Nsubuga I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Kranimer B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kibirige I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Randy B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kayongo I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Henry B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kalyango I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Augustine B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kamulegeya I-PER I-PER I-PER
ne O O O
Emmanuel B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kabaaya I-PER I-PER I-PER
be O O O
baayiseemu O O O
okwesogga O O O
oluzannya O O O
lwa O O O
ligyoni O O O
. O O O

Osaka B-PER B-PER B-PER
yawangudde O O O
engule O O O
ya O O O
US O O O
Open O O O
omulundi O O O
ogusoose O O O
mu O O O
byafaayo O O O
. O O O

Eno O O O
ye O O O
sizoni B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
eyokubiri I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
nga O O O
Liigi O O O
yomuzannyo O O O
gwa O O O
Woodball O O O
etegekebwa O O O
mu O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Ttiimu O O O
eno O O O
yakubye O O O
Zimbabwe B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ku O O O
fayinolo O O O
yeza O O O
Afrika B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
nesitukira O O O
mu O O O
kikopo O O O
ssaako O O O
okuyitamu O O O
okugenda O O O
mu O O O
World O O O
Cup O O O
. O O O

Enkya B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ezannya O O O
emipiira O O O
ebiri O O O
ne O O O
Kenya B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ku B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
makya I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ku I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ssaawa I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
5 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
nogwokubiri O O O
ku O O O
ssaawa B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
11 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ngettunka O O O
ne O O O
Botswana B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Vicent B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kiwanuka I-PER I-PER I-PER
omutendesi O O O
wa O O O
She B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Cranes I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
ngayita O O O
ku O O O
mukutu O O O
gwe O O O
ogwa O O O
twitter B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
yategeezezza O O O
nga O O O
bwe O O O
batera O O O
okusanga O O O
obuzibu O O O
okuwangula O O O
ensiike O O O
esooka O O O
mu O O O
mpaka O O O
zino O O O
naye O O O
ku O O O
luno O O O
Mukama O O O
abagonderezza O O O
ensonga O O O
. O O O

Empaka O O O
zaawanguddwa O O O
National B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Youth I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
bawala O O O
ne O O O
Kitgum B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Rwot I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Ker I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
balenzi O O O
okuva O O O
mu O O O
ligyoni B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ya I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
Northern I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
, O O O
ate O O O
mu O O O
West B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Nile I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
ne O O O
wavaayo O O O
FHL B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Simba I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
bawala O O O
ne O O O
Yumbe B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Heroes I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
. O O O

Agatha B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kamwada I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Bronnie B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kusiima I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Aisha B-PER B-PER B-PER
Namakula I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Winnie B-PER B-PER B-PER
Alice I-PER I-PER I-PER
Isoto I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Fildauce B-PER B-PER B-PER
Namulema I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Bridget B-PER B-PER B-PER
Aber I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Shadia B-PER B-PER B-PER
Mbwali I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Ramurah B-PER B-PER B-PER
Nakato I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Patience B-PER B-PER B-PER
Mauso I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Martha B-PER B-PER B-PER
Nandutu I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Emilly B-PER B-PER B-PER
Katurina I-PER I-PER I-PER
Nerima I-PER I-PER I-PER
ne O O O
Aziidah B-PER B-PER B-PER
Nabayunga I-PER I-PER I-PER
. O O O

KIU B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
esigazza O O O
ensiike O O O
ya O O O
mulundi O O O
gumu O O O
ne O O O
Ndejje B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Angels I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
okuwunzika O O O
enzannya O O O
zekibinja O O O
sizoni B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
eno I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
. O O O

Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ezzaako O O O
Zimbabwe B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
nga O O O
August B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
10 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
2017 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
e O O O
Lugogo B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Ttiimu O O O
eneewangula O O O
ejja O O O
kwegatta O O O
ku O O O
South B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Africa I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
okuvuganya O O O
mu O O O
mpaka O O O
za O O O
World O O O
Cup O O O
eza O O O
Rugby O O O
eza O O O
2019 B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
e O O O
Japan B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Kino O O O
kyogerwako O O O
ngakabenje O O O
kekidyeri O O O
akakyasinze O O O
okubeera O O O
akomutawaana O O O
mu O O O
kyasa B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
ekya I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
20 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
. O O O

Kasadha B-PER B-PER B-PER
yakubirizza O O O
nti O O O
okwewala O O O
nga O O O
bino O O O
, O O O
abantu O O O
batambulenga O O O
nendagamuntu O O O
kuba O O O
buli B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
ssaawa I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
tutambulira O O O
mu O O O
kufa O O O
. O O O

Mu O O O
katono O O O
ye O O O
Muhammad B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kateregga I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
ssentebe O O O
wa O O O
disitulikiti O O O
ye O O O
Bukomansimbi B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Tulina O O O
abaserikale O O O
batono O O O
nga O O O
bwe O O O
tusalawo O O O
okuwa O O O
buli O O O
muntu O O O
abaserikale O O O
kitubeerera O O O
kizibu O O O
okumatiza O O O
bannayuganda O O O
bonna O O O
kwe O O O
kusalawo O O O
essira O O O
okulissa O O O
ku O O O
bukuumi O O O
obwawamu O O O
mu O O O
byalo O O O
abantu O O O
gye O O O
bakolera O O O
, O O O
gye O O O
basula O O O
, O O O
oba O O O
mu O O O
nguudo O O O
gye O O O
bayitira O O O
, O O O
Kayima B-PER B-PER B-PER
bwe O O O
yayongeddeko O O O
. O O O

Oluvannyuma O O O
yaddukira O O O
mu O O O
Zimbabwe B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ngakozesa O O O
Paasipooti O O O
eyali O O O
mu O O O
mannya O O O
ga O O O
David B-PER B-PER B-PER
Mubiru I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
kyokka O O O
aboobuyinza O O O
baamuyigga O O O
ne O O O
bamukomyawo O O O
mu O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
mu O O O
November B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
2016 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, O O O
okumalayo O O O
ekibonerezo O O O
ekyemyaka B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
ena I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
nemyaka I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
emirala I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ebiri I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, O O O
egyamwongerwako O O O
olwokutoloka O O O
mu O O O
kkomera O O O
. O O O

Ekibiina O O O
kino O O O
kiteeseteese O O O
olukuhhaana O O O
olwawamu O O O
okusonyiwagana O O O
olugenda O O O
okubeerawo O O O
nga O O O
October B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
29 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ku O O O
Twin B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Towers I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
wansi O O O
womulamwa O O O
Okusonyiwagana O O O
nokussa O O O
ekitiibwa O O O
mu O O O
ddembe O O O
lyobuntu O O O
byebiseera O O O
bya O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ebyomu O O O
maaso O O O
okusinziira O O O
ku O O O
Ernest B-PER B-PER B-PER
Benjamin I-PER I-PER I-PER
Kivumbi I-PER I-PER I-PER
pulezidenti O O O
, O O O
waakyo O O O
. O O O

Ate O O O
Haruna B-PER B-PER B-PER
Walusimbi I-PER I-PER I-PER
yategeezezza O O O
nti O O O
abazigu O O O
bano O O O
baamenye O O O
ekisenge O O O
kyabaana O O O
ne O O O
babakuba O O O
kibooko O O O
nomu O O O
ne O O O
bamukuba O O O
akatayimbwa O O O
ku O O O
mutwe O O O
. O O O

Ku O O O
mukolo O O O
guno O O O
, O O O
Ssaabalabirizi O O O
wekkanisa O O O
ya O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Stanley B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ntagali I-PER I-PER I-PER
yeebazizza O O O
nnyo O O O
abakulira O O O
ettendekero O O O
lya O O O
Uganda B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Christian I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
University I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
olwokuvaayo O O O
ne O O O
batunula O O O
mu O O O
kizibu O O O
kyebyobulamu O O O
kye O O O
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
kino O O O
kya O O O
kwongera O O O
okubitumbula O O O
mu O O O
ggwanga O O O
. O O O

Kabanda B-PER B-PER B-PER
nate O O O
, O O O
akuutidde O O O
avunaanyizibwa O O O
ku O O O
mbeera O O O
yabakozi O O O
mu O O O
Mukono B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ayitibwa O O O
George B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ntulume I-PER I-PER I-PER
okukola O O O
kyonna O O O
ekisoboka O O O
okulaba O O O
nga O O O
bayambibwa O O O
nga O O O
kwogasse O O O
nabakozi O O O
abalala O O O
abagwa O O O
mu O O O
ttuluba O O O
elyo O O O
erimu O O O
, O O O
okukola O O O
ku O O O
nsonga O O O
zaabwe O O O
kuba O O O
ssente O O O
ze O O O
babanja O O O
nyingi O O O
ate O O O
nga O O O
nobuvunaanyizibwa O O O
balina O O O
bungi O O O
. O O O

Yanguwa O O O
weekwate O O O
Bukedde O O O
wo O O O
ku O O O
1 O O O
, O O O
000 O O O
zokka O O O
. O O O

Bwanika B-PER B-PER B-PER
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
enteekateeka O O O
eno O O O
eyambye O O O
okufuula O O O
abakulembeze O O O
babayizi O O O
abakulembeze O O O
abalungi O O O
era O O O
abomugaso O O O
. O O O

Aboludda O O O
oluvuganya O O O
baagamba O O O
nti O O O
obukuumi O O O
tebabwagala O O O
era O O O
oluvannyuma O O O
lwokukayana O O O
gavumenti O O O
nebiggyamu O O O
enta O O O
. O O O

Wabula O O O
okuggyawo O O O
ogwa O O O
social O O O
media O O O
ogwokweyunga O O O
ku O O O
yintanenti O O O
ngokozesa O O O
essimu O O O
kyo O O O
pulezidenti O O O
yakisimbira O O O
ekkuuli O O O
era O O O
gulabise O O O
obutaggyibwawo O O O
. O O O

Abasinga O O O
ku O O O
bbo O O O
babadde O O O
tebalina O O O
mirimu O O O
gye O O O
bakola O O O
wabula O O O
nga O O O
beerimbika O O O
mu O O O
kifaananyi O O O
ekyokuba O O O
nti O O O
bakozi O O O
, O O O
Ssebaggala B-PER B-PER B-PER
bwe O O O
yagambye O O O
. O O O

Omuduumizi O O O
wa O O O
poliisi O O O
e O O O
Jinja B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Vincent B-PER B-PER B-PER
Irama I-PER I-PER I-PER
yategeezezza O O O
ngomuliro O O O
bwe O O O
gwavudde O O O
mu O O O
leediyo O O O
mwennyini O O O
. O O O

Kuba O O O
ye O O O
omusango O O O
gwali O O O
munene O O O
nga O O O
tasobola O O O
kuba O O O
na O O O
buyambi O O O
bwonna O O O
. O O O

Dduwa O O O
ya O O O
Kirumira B-PER B-PER B-PER
yaakulombebwa O O O
nga O O O
October B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
21 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
2018 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, O O O
nasaba O O O
abaziirakisa O O O
bamudduukirire O O O
nobusobozi O O O
bwensimbi O O O
ku O O O
ssimu O O O
ze O O O
0772394982 O O O
ne O O O
0703878544 O O O
mu O O O
mannya O O O
ga O O O
Abubaker B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kawooya I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
okumuyambako O O O
munteekateeka O O O
za O O O
dduwa O O O
. O O O

Newankubadde O O O
omukazi O O O
gwe O O O
yattiddwa O O O
naye O O O
kigambibwa O O O
nti O O O
yabadde O O O
mukwano O O O
gwe O O O
, O O O
bambega O O O
bagamba O O O
nti O O O
naye O O O
bagenda O O O
kumunoonyerezaako O O O
bazuule O O O
oba O O O
teyali O O O
mu O O O
lukwe O O O
nabatemu O O O
. O O O

Bwe O O O
yabuuziddwa O O O
ku O O O
byabaana O O O
abebbali O O O
, O O O
Mariam B-PER B-PER B-PER
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
, O O O
takimanyi O O O
era O O O
abadde O O O
tabalabangako O O O
wabula O O O
nagattako O O O
nti O O O
tabalinaako O O O
mutawaana O O O
kubanga O O O
bonna O O O
baana O O O
ate O O O
abatalina O O O
musango O O O
ekikulu O O O
kati O O O
kusalira O O O
wamu O O O
magezi O O O
ku O O O
nkuza O O O
yaabwe O O O
. O O O

Nakimbowa B-PER B-PER B-PER
yaliko O O O
munnamawulire O O O
wa O O O
Star B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
FM I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
, O O O
Voice B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Teso I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
naye O O O
nga O O O
mu O O O
kiseera B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
kino I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
akola O O O
nekibiina O O O
kyobwannakyewa O O O
ekiyamba O O O
abantu O O O
ku O O O
byobulamu O O O
. O O O

Kawooya B-PER B-PER B-PER
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
mutabani O O O
we O O O
obutamukubira O O O
mizinga O O O
kyavudde O O O
ku O O O
ffujjo O O O
lyabantu O O O
naye O O O
nga O O O
poliisi O O O
ebikola O O O
byonna O O O
yabadde O O O
ebireese O O O
. O O O

Yayongeddeko O O O
nti O O O
olwomukwano O O O
Kirumira B-PER B-PER B-PER
gwabadde O O O
nagwo O O O
eri O O O
abantu O O O
, O O O
abasinga O O O
ebigambo O O O
bino O O O
babadde O O O
babigumira O O O
era O O O
nga O O O
tebatya O O O
kutuula O O O
mu O O O
mmotoka O O O
ye O O O
yadde O O O
azze O O O
akyogera O O O
lwatu O O O
nti O O O
waliwo O O O
abamulondoola O O O
. O O O

Omuvubuka O O O
yagambye O O O
twabadde O O O
tulowooza O O O
nti O O O
osanga O O O
bamuwadde O O O
abakuumi O O O
abambadde O O O
engoye O O O
ezaabulijjo O O O
kyokka O O O
twagenze O O O
okuwulira O O O
ekiro O O O
nti O O O
bamusse O O O
. O O O

Yagambye O O O
nti O O O
yamukubidde O O O
ku O O O
ssimu O O O
ne O O O
banyumyamu O O O
namugumya O O O
nti O O O
ekiseera O O O
kyonna O O O
agenda O O O
kusiibulwa O O O
era O O O
akomewo O O O
ku O O O
butaka O O O
. O O O

Kampala B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
nemirirwano O O O
egenda O O O
kussibwamu O O O
kamera O O O
3 O O O
, O O O
233 O O O
mu O O O
bifo O O O
1 O O O
, O O O
248 O O O
era O O O
kkampuni O O O
yAbachina O O O
eya O O O
Huawei B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
yegenda O O O
okukola O O O
omulimu O O O
guno O O O
. O O O

Wabula O O O
akakiiko O O O
kaalemeddwa O O O
okulaga O O O
ekibonerezo O O O
ekisaana O O O
okumuweebwa O O O
, O O O
era O O O
ensonga O O O
baazirekedde O O O
Palamenti O O O
eyawamu O O O
yeba O O O
esalawo O O O
. O O O

Yasabye O O O
etteeka O O O
lissibwemu O O O
akawaayiro O O O
akassaawo O O O
ensawo O O O
omusobola O O O
okuggyibwa O O O
ssente O O O
zokuliyirira O O O
abantu O O O
ababa O O O
batyobooleddwa O O O
eddembe O O O
lyabwe O O O
kuba O O O
abamu O O O
kkooti O O O
ziragira O O O
okubasasula O O O
nga O O O
gavumenti O O O
terina O O O
ssente O O O
ne O O O
balwawo O O O
okusasulwa O O O
. O O O

Ne O O O
yeemulugunya O O O
olwa O O O
gavumenti O O O
okuyiwa O O O
amagye O O O
ku O O O
nguudo O O O
ne O O O
geddiza O O O
omulimu O O O
ogwandibadde O O O
ogwa O O O
poliisi O O O
. O O O

Omulamuzi O O O
wabula O O O
yeeremye O O O
okulagira O O O
abaasingisiddwa O O O
emisango O O O
okuliyirira O O O
ekitongole O O O
kya O O O
UNRA B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
olwokubulawo O O O
embalirira O O O
yensasaanya O O O
eyakolebwa O O O
ku O O O
luguudo O O O
okusobozesa O O O
okumanya O O O
obungi O O O
bwensimbi O O O
ezaabafiirizibwa O O O
. O O O

Kinajjukirwa O O O
nti O O O
, O O O
akatambi O O O
akalaga O O O
Omuzungu O O O
ono O O O
ngakuba O O O
, O O O
okuvuma O O O
nokuboggolera O O O
omukozi O O O
wa O O O
woteeri O O O
kaatambula O O O
nnyo O O O
ku O O O
mikutu O O O
gya O O O
yintanenti O O O
era O O O
abaserikale O O O
ba O O O
Poliisi O O O
okuva O O O
ku O O O
CPS B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
mu O O O
Kampala B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
kwe O O O
baasinziira O O O
ne O O O
bamukwata O O O
naggalirwa O O O
. O O O

Aba O O O
Famire O O O
bamusabidde O O O
mu O O O
kkanisa O O O
e O O O
Kibiri B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
oluvannyuma O O O
yatwaliddwa O O O
mu O O O
kyalo O O O
Kalamba B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
okuziikibwa O O O
. O O O

Era O O O
nasiima O O O
omulimu O O O
ogukolebwa O O O
ebibiina O O O
ebirwanirira O O O
eddembe O O O
lyabantu O O O
. O O O

Mu O O O
kiseera B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
kino I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
Ntibimana B-PER B-PER B-PER
akuumirwa O O O
mu O O O
kaduukulu O O O
ka O O O
poliisi B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ye I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Mpigi I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
ngokunoonyereza O O O
bwe O O O
kugenda O O O
mu O O O
maaso O O O
. O O O

Lusiba B-PER B-PER B-PER
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
omuzirakisa O O O
asobola O O O
okuweereza O O O
obuyambi O O O
bwa O O O
ssente O O O
bwonna O O O
ku O O O
ssimu O O O
ya O O O
Lusiba B-PER B-PER B-PER
0703337432 O O O
ne O O O
0774991228 O O O
oba O O O
akawunti O O O
nnamba O O O
mu O O O
mannya O O O
ga O O O
Lusiba B-PER B-PER B-PER
Mahd I-PER I-PER I-PER
Jamada I-PER I-PER I-PER
. O O O

Ahimbisibwe B-PER B-PER B-PER
agambye O O O
nti O O O
Nabirye B-PER B-PER B-PER
baamugguddeko O O O
omusang O O O
. O O O

Nkwagaliza O O O
olunaku B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
olulungi O O O
mukwano O O O
, O O O
Barbie B-PER B-PER B-PER
bwe O O O
yayayongeddeko O O O
. O O O

Baawaddeyo O O O
engoye O O O
, O O O
sukaali O O O
, O O O
ppampa O O O
, O O O
sabbuuni O O O
, O O O
sooda O O O
, O O O
amazzi O O O
, O O O
emigaati O O O
, O O O
obuwunga O O O
, O O O
amata O O O
nebirala O O O
. O O O

Yawabudde O O O
bamulamu O O O
okutwala O O O
bakyala O O O
ba O O O
bannyinaabwe O O O
ngekikulu O O O
. O O O

Nagamba O O O
nti O O O
NRM B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
egenda O O O
kusigala O O O
ku O O O
mulamwa O O O
gwokukuuma O O O
eddembe O O O
lyabantu O O O
. O O O

Baabagambye O O O
nti O O O
ssente O O O
bwe O O O
ziba O O O
zibabuze O O O
, O O O
omulambo O O O
bagusange O O O
e O O O
Katende B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ku O O O
lwe O O O
Masaka B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Abamu O O O
ku O O O
bano O O O
bagundiivu O O O
mu O O O
byamateeka O O O
era O O O
bassibwamu O O O
nnyo O O O
ekitiibwa O O O
. O O O

Nabuuma B-PER B-PER B-PER
yagasseeko O O O
nti O O O
waliyo O O O
nabayimbi O O O
abagenda O O O
okusanyusa O O O
abantu O O O
omuli O O O
Ykee B-PER B-PER B-PER
Benda I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Vink B-PER B-PER B-PER
, O O O
bekibiina O O O
kya O O O
Dance B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
and I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Beats I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
ekya O O O
Namulindwa B-PER B-PER B-PER
nabalala O O O
. O O O

Abalongo O O O
bano O O O
okwetaba O O O
mu O O O
kkivulu O O O
kino O O O
bakiikiridde O O O
bannaabwe O O O
mu O O O
kibiina O O O
ekibagatta O O O
e O O O
Zimbabwe B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

DPC O O O
wa O O O
Rakai B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Patience B-PER B-PER B-PER
Baganzi I-PER I-PER I-PER
yategeezezza O O O
nti O O O
bagenda O O O
kumukwasa O O O
poliisi B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ye I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Katwe I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
mu O O O
Kampala B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
gye O O O
yaddiza O O O
omusango O O O
avunaanibwe O O O
. O O O

Baatemezza O O O
ku O O O
poliisi B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ye I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Mpigi I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
era O O O
ngekulembeddwaamu O O O
agikulira O O O
, O O O
Erias B-PER B-PER B-PER
Twesigye I-PER I-PER I-PER
yagenze O O O
okutuukawo O O O
nga O O O
Kayiira B-PER B-PER B-PER
ali O O O
mu O O O
mbeera O O O
mbi O O O
ne O O O
bamuddusa O O O
mu O O O
ddwaaliro O O O
. O O O

Omwogezi O O O
wa O O O
poliisi O O O
mu O O O
Wamala B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Region I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
, O O O
Nobert B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ochom I-PER I-PER I-PER
yavumiridde O O O
nnyo O O O
ekikolwa O O O
kyabatuuze O O O
ekyokwekalakasa O O O
nategeeza O O O
nga O O O
bwe O O O
basaanidde O O O
okusooka O O O
okutemya O O O
ku O O O
poliisi O O O
okusobola O O O
okubawa O O O
obukuumi O O O
obumala O O O
nga O O O
bagenda O O O
mu O O O
maaso O O O
nokwekalakaasa O O O
. O O O

Ono O O O
asabye O O O
Gavumenti O O O
okuwa O O O
ababaka O O O
ba O O O
Palamenti O O O
ekitiibwa O O O
wamu O O O
nabawagizi O O O
baabwe O O O
, O O O
okukomya O O O
okukozesa O O O
amaanyi O O O
agayitiridde O O O
nga O O O
bakkakkanya O O O
abantu O O O
wamu O O O
nokuwanga O O O
ssemateeka O O O
ekitiibwa O O O
kuba O O O
akkiriza O O O
Bannayuganda O O O
okukozesa O O O
eddembe O O O
lyabwe O O O
. O O O

Yasaba O O O
eyali O O O
amukuuma O O O
amukkirize O O O
afuke O O O
ku O O O
musulo O O O
kyokka O O O
bwe O O O
yagufuka O O O
nalaba O O O
nga O O O
gulimu O O O
omusaayi O O O
. O O O

Yagambye O O O
nti O O O
balina O O O
essuubi O O O
mu O O O
kakiiko O O O
aka O O O
UMA B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
kajja O O O
kuwa O O O
Bobi B-PER B-PER B-PER
Wine I-PER I-PER I-PER
obujjanjabi O O O
obutuufu O O O
kubanga O O O
ekibiina O O O
kirina O O O
abasawo O O O
abakugu O O O
mu O O O
buli O O O
ndwadde O O O
, O O O
so O O O
ngamagye O O O
tebabalina O O O
. O O O

Ensonga O O O
eyokubiri O O O
yalabudde O O O
omubaka O O O
Francis B-PER B-PER B-PER
Zaake I-PER I-PER I-PER
nti O O O
yatolose O O O
ku O O O
poliisi O O O
era O O O
emuyigga O O O
. O O O

Zaake B-PER B-PER B-PER
era O O O
amanyiddwa O O O
ngomusajja O O O
atanyigirwa O O O
mu O O O
nnoga O O O
naddala O O O
nga O O O
waliwo O O O
ekinyiga O O O
abatuuze O O O
era O O O
olumu O O O
yakulemberamu O O O
abatuuze O O O
ne O O O
beekalakaasa O O O
nga O O O
bawakanya O O O
amakubo O O O
gomu O O O
kibuga O O O
agali O O O
mu O O O
mbeera O O O
embi O O O
ennyo O O O
. O O O

Kyokka O O O
bwe O O O
baagezezzaako O O O
okwogera O O O
nabebyokwerinda O O O
baabagambye O O O
nti O O O
si O O O
be O O O
bamulina O O O
. O O O

Wabula O O O
ku O O O
byokusibwa O O O
kwomuwanguzi O O O
Wadri B-PER B-PER B-PER
ne O O O
Bobi B-PER B-PER B-PER
Wine I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Museveni B-PER B-PER B-PER
agamba O O O
nti O O O
ebikolwa O O O
byabwe O O O
bye O O O
byavaako O O O
Yasin B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kawuma I-PER I-PER I-PER
ddereeva O O O
wa O O O
Bobi B-PER B-PER B-PER
Wine I-PER I-PER I-PER
okufa O O O
, O O O
abantu O O O
abalala O O O
okulumizibwa O O O
nokwonoona O O O
ebintu O O O
mu O O O
Arua B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Wabula O O O
bino O O O
Moses B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ali I-PER I-PER I-PER
yabiwakanyizza O O O
nagamba O O O
nti O O O
abaakwatiddwa O O O
baabadde O O O
bafunyeemu O O O
obuzibu O O O
mu O O O
kavuvuhhano O O O
nga O O O
bakwatibwa O O O
wabula O O O
nti O O O
embeera O O O
yaabwe O O O
okuli O O O
ne O O O
Bobi B-PER B-PER B-PER
Wine I-PER I-PER I-PER
yateredde O O O
. O O O

Akulira O O O
okunoonyereza O O O
ku O O O
buzzi O O O
bwemisango O O O
mu O O O
disitulikiti O O O
ye O O O
Mpigi B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Andrew B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ainembabazi I-PER I-PER I-PER
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
Arinitwe B-PER B-PER B-PER
yagguddwaako O O O
omusango O O O
gwokwewamba O O O
. O O O

Atwala O O O
Poliisi B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ye I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Matugga I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
ASP O O O
Kirya B-PER B-PER B-PER
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
baliko O O O
gwe O O O
baakutte O O O
abayambeko O O O
mu O O O
kunoonyereza O O O
ngomusango O O O
guli O O O
ku O O O
fayiro O O O
nnamba O O O
SD O O O
3813082018 O O O
. O O O

Yaliko O O O
omukulembeze O O O
wabayizi O O O
ku O O O
yunivasite B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
e I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Makerere I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
. O O O

Mu O O O
kiseera B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
kino I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
olumbe O O O
lukumiddwa O O O
e O O O
Munyonyo B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
mu O O O
maka O O O
ga O O O
Muzeeyi O O O
Luyinda B-PER B-PER B-PER
. O O O

Abasajja O O O
abaakoze O O O
ettemu O O O
babadde O O O
bamaze O O O
ennaku B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
nga O O O
basula O O O
mu O O O
wooteeri O O O
kuba O O O
bajjamu O O O
ku O O O
Mmande B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
era O O O
bulijjo O O O
babadde O O O
bapangisa O O O
obusenge O O O
bubiri O O O
nga O O O
buli O O O
kamu O O O
bakasasulira O O O
50 O O O
, O O O
000 O O O
olunaku B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
. O O O

Newankubadde O O O
Moses B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ali I-PER I-PER I-PER
ategezezza O O O
nti O O O
abaakwatiddwa O O O
tewali O O O
yatulugunyiziddwa O O O
, O O O
kigambibwa O O O
nti O O O
ku O O O
bantu O O O
33 O O O
, O O O
abasinga O O O
ku O O O
bo O O O
, O O O
bapooca O O O
na O O O
biwundu O O O
oluvannyuma O O O
lwokukubibwa O O O
abebyokwerinda O O O
bwe O O O
baabadde O O O
e O O O
Gulu B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ku O O O
Lwokubiri B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
. O O O

Gen O O O
. O O O
Elly B-PER B-PER B-PER
Tumwine I-PER I-PER I-PER
agambye O O O
nti O O O
baakukwatagana O O O
nebitongole O O O
byebyokwerinda O O O
byonna O O O
okulaba O O O
nga O O O
balwanyisa O O O
obulwadde O O O
bwente O O O
okuli O O O
kalusu O O O
nendala O O O
. O O O

Ate O O O
Omubaka O O O
omukazi O O O
owa O O O
Lwengo B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
mu O O O
Palamenti O O O
, O O O
Cissy B-PER B-PER B-PER
Namujju I-PER I-PER I-PER
yawaddeyo O O O
900 O O O
, O O O
000 O O O
. O O O

Omuwawabirwa O O O
talina O O O
musango O O O
yejjeredde O O O
omulamuzi O O O
bwe O O O
yawunzise O O O
. O O O

Omuwandiisi O O O
wakakiiko O O O
, O O O
Lawrence B-PER B-PER B-PER
Banyoya I-PER I-PER I-PER
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
ebifo O O O
ebimu O O O
we O O O
bandiggye O O O
emisolo O O O
nga O O O
ppaaka O O O
zemmotoka O O O
nobutale O O O
kizibu O O O
okugufunamu O O O
kuba O O O
teri O O O
nkola O O O
nnungamu O O O
erambikiddwa O O O
egobererwa O O O
mu O O O
kugiwoozaamu O O O
. O O O

Agambye O O O
nti O O O
ebikolwa O O O
byeffujjo O O O
nga O O O
bino O O O
byavaako O O O
omuntu O O O
okufa O O O
mu O O O
kulonda O O O
e O O O
Bugiri B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
kati O O O
ne O O O
Arua B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
wafuddeyo O O O
omu O O O
nabivumirira O O O
nokugamba O O O
nti O O O
abaabyenyigiddemu O O O
bajja O O O
kukolwako O O O
ngamateeka O O O
bwe O O O
galagira O O O
. O O O

Poliisi O O O
ngeri O O O
ne O O O
ssentebe O O O
wekyalo O O O
, O O O
Richard B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kirabira I-PER I-PER I-PER
Kasaijja I-PER I-PER I-PER
baatandise O O O
omuyiggo O O O
ku O O O
yakoze O O O
ekikolwa O O O
kino O O O
. O O O

Abenganda O O O
za O O O
Majambere B-PER B-PER B-PER
baagambye O O O
nti O O O
tebaamatidde O O O
na O O O
kibonerezo O O O
kino O O O
era O O O
omu O O O
ku O O O
baana O O O
ba O O O
Ivan B-PER B-PER B-PER
Majambere I-PER I-PER I-PER
nagamba O O O
bagenda O O O
kujulira O O O
. O O O

Mu O O O
kiseera B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
kino I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
amaanyi O O O
agamba O O O
nti O O O
yasalawo O O O
kugateeka O O O
mu O O O
baana O O O
kuba O O O
bakola O O O
ebitundu O O O
53 O O O
ku O O O
buli O O O
100 O O O
. O O O

Enkyukakyuka O O O
zino O O O
we O O O
zijjidde O O O
nga O O O
Ssempebwa B-PER B-PER B-PER
ali O O O
mu O O O
kugugulana O O O
ne O O O
Bakansala O O O
ku O O O
Town B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Couincil I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
ye I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
Wakiso I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
nabamu O O O
ku O O O
bakozi O O O
banne O O O
ate O O O
nga O O O
nakakiiko O O O
Lokuda B-PER B-PER B-PER
ke O O O
yateekawo O O O
okumunoonyerezaako O O O
nga O O O
kamaze O O O
okufulumya O O O
lipooti O O O
eraga O O O
engeri O O O
gyabadde O O O
agootanyizzaamu O O O
enzirukanya O O O
yemirimu O O O
. O O O

Bano O O O
bagguddwaako O O O
omusango O O O
gwokumenya O O O
akaduukulu O O O
ku O O O
fayiro O O O
nnamba O O O
SD O O O
REF O O O
1409082018 O O O
. O O O

Navuga B-PER B-PER B-PER
yagguddewo O O O
omusango O O O
ku O O O
poliisi O O O
yoku O O O
Kaleerwe B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ku O O O
fayiro O O O
nnamba O O O
SD O O O
REF1513082018 O O O
. O O O

Bagenda O O O
kutuula O O O
mu O O O
bwangu O O O
okusalawo O O O
ekyokubakolera O O O
. O O O

okuggyako O O O
nga O O O
bamuviiridde O O O
ku O O O
ttaka O O O
lye O O O
asobole O O O
okulikulaakulanya O O O
. O O O

Poliisi O O O
yagguddewo O O O
omusango O O O
gwobutemu O O O
ngokunoonyereza O O O
bwe O O O
kugenda O O O
mu O O O
maaso O O O
. O O O

Omwogezi O O O
wa O O O
poliisi O O O
e O O O
Masaka B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Lameck B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kigozi I-PER I-PER I-PER
yasabye O O O
abatuuze O O O
okubuulira O O O
abakulembeze O O O
baabwe O O O
nga O O O
waliwo O O O
abantu O O O
. O O O

Omusango O O O
gwobubbi O O O
gwamugguddwaako O O O
ku O O O
Ref O O O
37110818 O O O
. O O O

Omulamuzi O O O
Karazarwe B-PER B-PER B-PER
yategeezezza O O O
nti O O O
wadde O O O
yeegaana O O O
omusango O O O
, O O O
omukadde O O O
owemyaka B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
65 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
tayinza O O O
kweswaza O O O
kwesimba O O O
mu O O O
kaguli O O O
namuwaako O O O
obujulizi O O O
. O O O

Yabuuliridde O O O
abavubuka O O O
bano O O O
obutadda O O O
mu O O O
kwejalabya O O O
wabula O O O
bakole O O O
nga O O O
batereka O O O
okwekulakulanya O O O
. O O O

Kyokka O O O
Tugume B-PER B-PER B-PER
teyannyonnyodde O O O
lwaki O O O
Kayihura B-PER B-PER B-PER
yali O O O
asigazza O O O
ekyuma O O O
kino O O O
ate O O O
nga O O O
yali O O O
amaze O O O
emyezi B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
esatu I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ngamaze O O O
okuggyibwa O O O
ku O O O
buduumizi O O O
bwa O O O
poliisi O O O
. O O O

Abawagizi O O O
be O O O
baasigadde O O O
bamutenda O O O
nti O O O
musajja O O O
muli O O O
wa O O O
sswaga O O O
. O O O

Yagasseeko O O O
nti O O O
olugendo O O O
lwabwe O O O
terugenda O O O
kubasala O O O
kubanga O O O
baakufunamu O O O
nnyo O O O
era O O O
nti O O O
waliwo O O O
abasawo O O O
abagenda O O O
okutuuka O O O
mu O O O
ggwanga O O O
okuva O O O
e O O O
Bungereza B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
abasoba O O O
mu O O O
40 O O O
abagenda O O O
okujjanjaba O O O
abatuuze O O O
be O O O
Kooki B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
era O O O
omulimu O O O
guno O O O
gwakubeera O O O
mu O O O
ddwaaliro O O O
lye O O O
Rakai B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
General I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Hospital I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
. O O O

Ssempijja B-PER B-PER B-PER
ne O O O
minisita O O O
Mbayo B-PER B-PER B-PER
bajjukizza O O O
Bannayuganda O O O
nti O O O
eddagala O O O
eririwo O O O
teriwonya O O O
siriimu O O O
wazira O O O
limuweweezaako O O O
buweweeza O O O
ngekyokubwekuuma O O O
kyekisinga O O O
obukulu O O O
. O O O

Yagambye O O O
nti O O O
waakusisinkana O O O
akulira O O O
ekitongole O O O
kyebyenguudo O O O
. O O O

Eriku B-PER B-PER B-PER
era O O O
agambye O O O
nti O O O
omusawo O O O
wa O O O
poliisi O O O
yeekebejja O O O
omwana O O O
ono O O O
ne O O O
kizulibwa O O O
nga O O O
yali O O O
yakabassanyizibwa O O O
, O O O
nasaba O O O
alina O O O
amawulire O O O
agakwata O O O
ku O O O
basajja O O O
bano O O O
okutuukirira O O O
poliisi O O O
yonna O O O
ebanguyira O O O
mu O O O
ggwanga O O O
. O O O

Bano O O O
bwe O O O
baakitegedde O O O
ne O O O
batandika O O O
okwogerera O O O
poliisi O O O
ebisongovu O O O
nga O O O
bagamba O O O
nti O O O
omuntu O O O
waabwe O O O
tayinza O O O
kumala O O O
nnaku B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
ezo I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
zonna O O O
ngali O O O
mu O O O
ggwanika O O O
ngaatalinaako O O O
abantu O O O
be O O O
era O O O
wano O O O
poliisi O O O
nayo O O O
kwekubawa O O O
ebbaluwa O O O
ebatwala O O O
mu O O O
ggwanika O O O
e O O O
Mulago B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Kigambibwa O O O
nti O O O
ente O O O
eziwera O O O
98 O O O
, O O O
ze O O O
zazuuliddwa O O O
okuva O O O
ku O O O
faamu O O O
ye O O O
, O O O
wamu O O O
nembuzi O O O
167 O O O
. O O O
Poliisi O O O
okuva O O O
e O O O
Kazo B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ekyagaanye O O O
okubaako O O O
kyeyogera O O O
ku O O O
nsonga O O O
eno O O O
, O O O
wabula O O O
ngensonda O O O
ezesigika O O O
ziraga O O O
nti O O O
okunoonyereza O O O
ku O O O
nsonga O O O
eno O O O
kukyagenda O O O
mu O O O
maaso O O O
okuzuula O O O
bannanyini O O O
bisolo O O O
abatuufu O O O
. O O O

Fred B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kayima I-PER I-PER I-PER
nga O O O
ye O O O
taata O O O
womugenzi O O O
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
bakumuziika O O O
Mbarara B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

William B-PER B-PER B-PER
Matovu I-PER I-PER I-PER
akola O O O
ku O O O
byokuliyirira O O O
abakoseddwa O O O
enguudo O O O
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
abantu O O O
16 O O O
bokka O O O
be O O O
bakyabulayo O O O
okusasulwa O O O
kuba O O O
bakyalina O O O
enkaayana O O O
ku O O O
bwannannyini O O O
ku O O O
ttaka O O O
ezikyali O O O
mu O O O
kkooti O O O
. O O O

Yategeezeza O O O
nti O O O
omwana O O O
atayonseddwa O O O
bulungi O O O
asobola O O O
okufuna O O O
endwadde O O O
okuli O O O
kansa O O O
ne O O O
sukaali O O O
mu O O O
bukulu O O O
ekiyinza O O O
nokumuviirako O O O
okufa O O O
. O O O

Richard B-PER B-PER B-PER
Karemire I-PER I-PER I-PER
yabalabudde O O O
nabawa O O O
amagezi O O O
obutagezaako O O O
kwegugunga O O O
kubanga O O O
kye O O O
bakola O O O
ngamagye O O O
bakimanyi O O O
, O O O
bakikola O O O
mu O O O
bukugu O O O
bwabwe O O O
era O O O
teri O O O
ayinza O O O
kubapakusa O O O
okukolera O O O
ku O O O
kutiisatiisa O O O
kwabwe O O O
. O O O

Yayongeddeko O O O
nti O O O
amataawo O O O
ge O O O
Kawaala B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Bwaise B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Kyebando B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Kaleerwe B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
okuwera O O O
ssaawa B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
2 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ezekiro I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
abakazi O O O
bandibadde O O O
beesonyiwa O O O
okugayitako O O O
kuba O O O
abavubuka O O O
bbo O O O
tebalina O O O
kye O O O
batya O O O
olwokuba O O O
bakozesa O O O
ebiragalalaga O O O
, O O O
akaka O O O
omukwano O O O
nakuleka O O O
mu O O O
maziga O O O
sinakindi O O O
okukusiiga O O O
siriimu O O O
. O O O

Ensonga O O O
zaalanda O O O
ne O O O
batuuka O O O
nokumuyita O O O
mu O O O
palamenti O O O
abinnyonnyole O O O
era O O O
endagaano O O O
ze O O O
baalina O O O
nga O O O
ziraga O O O
nti O O O
NSSF B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
yasasula O O O
Nzeyi B-PER B-PER B-PER
8 O O O
, O O O
700 O O O
, O O O
000 O O O
, O O O
000 O O O
. O O O

Fred B-PER B-PER B-PER
Eriku I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
akulira O O O
okunoonyereza O O O
ku O O O
buzzi O O O
bwemisango O O O
ku O O O
poliisi B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ye I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Katwe I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
, O O O
bagenda O O O
kunoonya O O O
nnannyini O O O
kikomera O O O
abannyonnyole O O O
engeri O O O
gye O O O
kyazimbibwaamu O O O
bwe O O O
wanaabawo O O O
ekikyamu O O O
bamuvunaane O O O
. O O O

Omusango O O O
gwa O O O
Zziwa B-PER B-PER B-PER
guli O O O
ku O O O
SD1021072018 O O O
. O O O

Omugenzi O O O
alese O O O
abakyala O O O
basatu O O O
nabaana O O O
abawerako O O O
nga O O O
waakuziikibwa O O O
ku O O O
kyalo O O O
Kiteredde B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
mu O O O
ggombolola O O O
ye O O O
Kifamba B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
mu O O O
disitulikiti O O O
ye O O O
Rakai B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Era O O O
waliwo O O O
okusaba O O O
kwensimbi O O O
eziwera O O O
ddoola O O O
za O O O
Amerika B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
182 O O O
okussa O O O
amasanyalaze O O O
mu O O O
bibangirizi O O O
byamakkolero O O O
e O O O
Kapeeka B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Sukuru B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ne O O O
Mbale B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Akulira O O O
Poliisi B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ye I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Masuuliita I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Martin B-PER B-PER B-PER
Karekyezi I-PER I-PER I-PER
yategeezezza O O O
nti O O O
amaze O O O
ebbanga O O O
ngabuuza O O O
kkampuni O O O
eno O O O
ku O O O
bakuumi O O O
bano O O O
kyokka O O O
nga O O O
buli B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
lwatuukawo I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
bamutegeeza O O O
ng O O O
ababakulira O O O
bwe O O O
bataliiwo O O O
. O O O

Nabusaayi B-PER B-PER B-PER
era O O O
ategeezezza O O O
nti O O O
, O O O
omugenzi O O O
asuubirwa O O O
okuziikibwa O O O
mu O O O
disitulikiti O O O
ye O O O
Bugiri B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
gyasibuka O O O
, O O O
ku O O O
Lwokubiri B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
lwa I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
wiiki I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
eno I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
kyokkatalambuludde O O O
ngeri O O O
Maj O O O
. O O O
Bogere B-PER B-PER B-PER
gye O O O
yafuddemu O O O
. O O O

James B-PER B-PER B-PER
Abraham I-PER I-PER I-PER
Byandala I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Ruth B-PER B-PER B-PER
Katushabe I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Sylivia B-PER B-PER B-PER
Nayebale I-PER I-PER I-PER
baateesezza O O O
emirundi O O O
musanvu O O O
ne O O O
John B-PER B-PER B-PER
Bosco I-PER I-PER I-PER
Lubyayi I-PER I-PER I-PER
emirundi O O O
5 O O O
. O O O

Ababaka O O O
era O O O
beemulugunya O O O
nti O O O
ekitongole O O O
ekivunaanyizibwa O O O
ku O O O
kulondoola O O O
abagwiira O O O
ababa O O O
bayingidde O O O
mu O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
tekirina O O O
bakozi O O O
bamala O O O
kutuukiriza O O O
mirimu O O O
gyakyo O O O
. O O O
Beemulugunya O O O
nti O O O
tewali O O O
mateeka O O O
gamala O O O
kutangira O O O
Bannayuganda O O O
kumalibwa O O O
mirimu O O O
gye O O O
basobola O O O
kufunamu O O O
ssente O O O
egitwalibwa O O O
abagwiira O O O
. O O O

Basalirwa B-PER B-PER B-PER
yafunye O O O
obululu O O O
3 O O O
, O O O
928 O O O
, O O O
Francis B-PER B-PER B-PER
Okecho I-PER I-PER I-PER
owa O O O
NRM B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
nafuna O O O
3 O O O
, O O O
267 O O O
, O O O
ate O O O
Namatende B-PER B-PER B-PER
owa O O O
FDC B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
nafuna O O O
928 O O O
. O O O

Wabula O O O
Mary B-PER B-PER B-PER
Bata I-PER I-PER I-PER
bwe O O O
yasoose O O O
okulaba O O O
ku O O O
Mawanda B-PER B-PER B-PER
ku O O O
poliisi O O O
yabadde O O O
aswakidde O O O
ngalinga O O O
ayagala O O O
okumugwa O O O
mu O O O
bulago O O O
ngawulira O O O
obusungu O O O
bumutta O O O
. O O O

Omwogezi O O O
wa O O O
poliisi O O O
mu O O O
Kampala B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
nemiriraano O O O
, O O O
Lukas B-PER B-PER B-PER
Owesigyire I-PER I-PER I-PER
yakakkasizza O O O
ettemu O O O
lino O O O
nategeeza O O O
nga O O O
Kagaba B-PER B-PER B-PER
bwe O O O
yaddusiddwa O O O
Poliisi O O O
mu O O O
ddwaaliro O O O
e O O O
Mulago B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
okufuna O O O
obujjanjabi O O O
nga O O O
bwe O O O
bayigga O O O
omukuumi O O O
eyakoze O O O
ettemu O O O
lino O O O
avunaanibwe O O O
olwokutwalira O O O
amateeka O O O
mu O O O
ngalo O O O
. O O O

Ku O O O
bano O O O
kubaddeko O O O
nabayizi O O O
Kayihura B-PER B-PER B-PER
baweerera O O O
abali O O O
ku O O O
yunivasite O O O
ezenjawulo O O O
abagambye O O O
nti O O O
tebamanyi O O O
kiddako O O O
oluvanyuma O O O
lwa O O O
Kayihura B-PER B-PER B-PER
okukwatibwa O O O
. O O O

Moses B-PER B-PER B-PER
Mutebi I-PER I-PER I-PER
Nsubuga I-PER I-PER I-PER
Konkomebi I-PER I-PER I-PER
NRM B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
yawangudde O O O
Haruna B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ssali I-PER I-PER I-PER
DP B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ku O O O
bululu O O O
25 O O O
ku O O O
21 O O O
okuba O O O
ssentebe O O O
womuluka O O O
gwa O O O
Makerere B-LOC B-ORG B-LOC
III I-LOC B-LOC I-LOC
e O O O
Kawempe B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Naye O O O
wadde O O O
omusango O O O
gugobeddwa O O O
omu O O O
ku O O O
basirikale O O O
ababadde O O O
ku O O O
musango O O O
guno O O O
era O O O
yakwatibwa O O O
ku O O O
misango O O O
egyekuusa O O O
ku O O O
kukukusa O O O
abantu O O O
, O O O
gyavunaanibwa O O O
ne O O O
Nixon B-PER B-PER B-PER
Agasirwe I-PER I-PER I-PER
era O O O
ngali O O O
mu O O O
kkomera O O O
. O O O

Yasuubizza O O O
nokwongera O O O
okuzimbira O O O
abasawo O O O
mu O O O
bizinga O O O
bino O O O
ennyumba O O O
mwe O O O
basula O O O
basobole O O O
okubeera O O O
okumpi O O O
namalwaliro O O O
. O O O

John B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kalagiro I-PER I-PER I-PER
avunaana O O O
Paul B-PER B-PER B-PER
Nsubuga I-PER I-PER I-PER
52 O O O
, O O O
kwossa O O O
Fulugensio B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ssegujja I-PER I-PER I-PER
ne O O O
famire O O O
zaabwe O O O
okusaalimbira O O O
nokwesenza O O O
ku O O O
ttaka O O O
lye O O O
yagula O O O
ku O O O
maneja O O O
wa O O O
KT B-ORG B-ORG O
, O O O
Musa B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kavuma I-PER I-PER I-PER
. O O O

Baroza B-PER B-PER B-PER
yabula O O O
okuva O O O
mu O O O
mwezi B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
gwa I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
June I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
era O O O
nga O O O
kyalagidde O O O
omuduumuzi O O O
wa O O O
poliisi B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ye I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Mbarara I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
okwaza O O O
amaka O O O
ga O O O
Yovas B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kabiguruka I-PER I-PER I-PER
ku O O O
kyalo O O O
Karora B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
e O O O
Rugando B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Ku O O O
Bashir B-PER B-PER B-PER
, O O O
Kadaga B-PER B-PER B-PER
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
tasobola O O O
kumala O O O
gakwatibwa O O O
kuba O O O
alina O O O
omugaso O O O
munene O O O
mu O O O
kutereeza O O O
obutabanguko O O O
obuli O O O
mu O O O
South B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Sudan I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
nga O O O
bukosa O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ne O O O
Sudan B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Poliisi B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ye I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Kabulasoke I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Kakooza B-PER B-PER B-PER
yamusanze O O O
mu O O O
ddwaaliro O O O
ne O O O
bamwekebejja O O O
era O O O
ne O O O
bategeeza O O O
nti O O O
batandise O O O
okuyigga O O O
abatemu O O O
bano O O O
. O O O

Wabula O O O
bakansala O O O
oluwulidde O O O
nti O O O
olukiiko O O O
lwa O O O
minisita O O O
Kamya B-PER B-PER B-PER
ne O O O
Lukwago B-PER B-PER B-PER
ne O O O
Jennifer B-PER B-PER B-PER
bo O O O
balekeddwa O O O
bbali O O O
ne O O O
bagamba O O O
nti O O O
Lukwago B-PER B-PER B-PER
tebasobola O O O
kumukkiriza O O O
kulutuulamu O O O
okuggyako O O O
nga O O O
nabo O O O
bayitiddwa O O O
. O O O

Bo O O O
abatwala O O O
tiimu O O O
eno O O O
babadde O O O
tebannavaayo O O O
kwogera O O O
ku O O O
mutendesi O O O
agenda O O O
kuddira O O O
Da B-PER B-PER B-PER
costa I-PER I-PER I-PER
mu O O O
bigere O O O
. O O O

Anthony B-PER B-PER B-PER
Musisi I-PER I-PER I-PER
yagambye O O O
gwa O O O
kumuyamba O O O
nnyo O O O
ngalambula O O O
amasomero O O O
. O O O

Ekibinja O O O
BG O O O
XXV O O O
kigenda O O O
kuduumirwa O O O
Col O O O
. O O O
Paul B-PER B-PER B-PER
Muhanguzi I-PER I-PER I-PER
amyukibwe O O O
Lt O O O
. O O O
Col O O O
. O O O
CK B-PER B-PER B-PER
Asiimwe I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
ate O O O
Col O O O
. O O O
Stuart B-PER B-PER B-PER
Agaba I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
aduumire O O O
ekibinja O O O
kya O O O
UNGU O O O
V O O O
, O O O
amyukibwe O O O
Maj O O O
. O O O
Edward B-PER B-PER B-PER
Mugisha I-PER I-PER I-PER
. O O O

Mu O O O
buvumu O O O
Isiko B-PER B-PER B-PER
yategeeza O O O
omubaka O O O
Rwabogo B-PER B-PER B-PER
nti O O O
, O O O
aludde O O O
ngamwegomba O O O
buli O O O
lwamulaba O O O
ku O O O
ttivvi O O O
era O O O
nga O O O
notulo O O O
twali O O O
twamubula O O O
olwensonga O O O
nti O O O
yal O O O
. O O O

Abe O O O
Katwe B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
baamuweerezza O O O
ku O O O
poliisi B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ye I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Mityana I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
gye O O O
yaddiza O O O
omusango O O O
. O O O

Omusango O O O
gwawulirwa O O O
abalamuzi O O O
bataano O O O
abaakulemberwaamu O O O
amyuka O O O
ssaabalamuzi O O O
Alfred B-PER B-PER B-PER
Owiny I-PER I-PER I-PER
Dollo I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Elizabeth B-PER B-PER B-PER
Musoke I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Cheborion B-PER B-PER B-PER
Barishaki I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Kenneth B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kakuru I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
ne O O O
Remmy B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kasule I-PER I-PER I-PER
. O O O

Omulamuzi O O O
yabategeezezza O O O
nti O O O
, O O O
kkooti O O O
ye O O O
terina O O O
buyinza O O O
kuwulira O O O
musango O O O
gwabwe O O O
kubanga O O O
gwa O O O
nnaggomola O O O
oguwulirwa O O O
kkooti B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
enkulu I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
yokka O O O
. O O O

Yagambye O O O
nti O O O
bwe O O O
kiba O O O
ngebyokwerinda O O O
kweggwanga O O O
bye O O O
biri O O O
obubi O O O
ensonga O O O
ekolerweko O O O
wamu O O O
so O O O
ssi O O O
kukuuma O O O
babaka O O O
bokka O O O
nayongerako O O O
nti O O O
ekizibu O O O
bwe O O O
kiba O O O
nti O O O
abantu O O O
bakyaye O O O
bukulembeze O O O
kyekiseera O O O
budde O O O
ebbali O O O
. O O O

Omari B-PER B-PER B-PER
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
, O O O
poliisi O O O
enoonya O O O
Faruq B-PER B-PER B-PER
Bukenya I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Joseph B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ssemanda I-PER I-PER I-PER
ne O O O
Kyeyune B-PER B-PER B-PER
Lugya I-PER I-PER I-PER
be O O O
yayogeddeko O O O
nti O O O
be O O O
baamuyambe O O O
mu O O O
ttemu O O O
lino O O O
. O O O

Mu O O O
kiseera B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
kino I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
emyalo O O O
14 O O O
gyokka O O O
egiri O O O
mu O O O
mateeka O O O
okuva O O O
ku O O O
myalo O O O
21 O O O
egyali O O O
gikozesebwa O O O
ngekikwekweto O O O
tekinnatandika O O O
nga O O O
May B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
25 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
2018 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
. O O O

Era O O O
yasabye O O O
abatuuze O O O
okubeera O O O
abakkakkamu O O O
, O O O
kuba O O O
kijja O O O
kuggwa O O O
. O O O

Kadaga B-PER B-PER B-PER
era O O O
akunze O O O
Bannayuganda O O O
okujjumbira O O O
okulambula O O O
ensi O O O
yaabwe O O O
. O O O

Kalungi B-PER B-PER B-PER
agamba O O O
nti O O O
, O O O
Edward B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kitaamirike I-PER I-PER I-PER
yagenda O O O
okufa O O O
ngamuguzizza O O O
ettaka O O O
lino O O O
era O O O
nga O O O
yali O O O
yalabula O O O
dda O O O
abatuuze O O O
okulivaako O O O
. O O O

Nnaalongo O O O
Mirembe B-PER B-PER B-PER
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
, O O O
yabadde O O O
anaaza O O O
omwana O O O
mwannyina O O O
namumusikako O O O
namukwata O O O
mu O O O
bulago O O O
namutuga O O O
. O O O

Yakubirizza O O O
abantu O O O
obutatya O O O
kugenda O O O
kulonda O O O
olwokutya O O O
effujjo O O O
kuba O O O
Poliisi O O O
ejja O O O
kubeerawo O O O
okukwata O O O
buli O O O
muntu O O O
aneenyigira O O O
mu O O O
bikolwa O O O
byeffujjo O O O
. O O O

Omulamuzi O O O
waakumusalira O O O
ekibonerezo O O O
kye O O O
nga O O O
July B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
11 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
2018 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
era O O O
namusindika O O O
ku O O O
limanda O O O
mu O O O
kkomera O O O
e O O O
Luzira B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ne O O O
banne O O O
bwe O O O
bali O O O
ku O O O
musango O O O
guno O O O
okuli O O O
Kazahura B-PER B-PER B-PER
ne O O O
Kibirango B-PER B-PER B-PER
. O O O

Ensonda O O O
zigamba O O O
nti O O O
, O O O
Kayihura B-PER B-PER B-PER
akyalina O O O
okukkiriza O O O
kwa O O O
maanyi O O O
nti O O O
mukama O O O
we O O O
akyamulinamu O O O
obwesige O O O
era O O O
asobola O O O
okumunnyonnyola O O O
ekintu O O O
kyonna O O O
ne O O O
bakkaanya O O O
era O O O
kino O O O
asuubira O O O
nti O O O
kye O O O
kigenda O O O
okuyamba O O O
okusinga O O O
okuddukira O O O
mu O O O
kkooti O O O
ate O O O
ekiyinza O O O
okunyiiza O O O
Pulezidenti O O O
. O O O

Kieran B-PER B-PER B-PER
Murphy I-PER I-PER I-PER
ku O O O
lwekitongole O O O
kya O O O
General B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Electric I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
, O O O
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
bagenda O O O
kukolagana O O O
bulungi O O O
ne O O O
Gavumenti B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ya I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Uganda I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
okukakasa O O O
nga O O O
batuusa O O O
empeereza O O O
zobujjanjabi O O O
eziri O O O
ku O O O
mutindo O O O
gwensi O O O
yonna O O O
eri O O O
Bannayuganda O O O
okuyita O O O
mu O O O
kuwa O O O
amalwaliro O O O
ebikozesebwa O O O
ebyomulembe O O O
nokubikanika O O O
era O O O
nakakasa O O O
nti O O O
enkolagana O O O
eno O O O
yaakumala O O O
akaseera O O O
akawera O O O
. O O O

Machar B-PER B-PER B-PER
yasooka O O O
okubeera O O O
omumyuka O O O
wa O O O
Pulezidenti O O O
okuva O O O
nga O O O
July B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
9 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
2011 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, O O O
South B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Sudan I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
lwe O O O
yatondebwawo O O O
nga O O O
yeekutula O O O
ku O O O
Sudan B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
wabula O O O
baafunamu O O O
obutakkaanya O O O
ne O O O
Gen O O O
. O O O
Kiir B-PER B-PER B-PER
nagoba O O O
Dr O O O
. O O O
Machar B-PER B-PER B-PER
nga O O O
July B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
23 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
2013 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
olwebigambibwa O O O
nti O O O
yali O O O
ateekateeka O O O
okuwamba O O O
gavumenti O O O
nekyaddirira O O O
lutalo O O O
kubalukawo O O O
mu O O O
December B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
2013 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ne O O O
bakubagana O O O
okutuuka O O O
mu O O O
July B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
2015 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
lwe O O O
bassa O O O
wansi O O O
ebyokulwanyisa O O O
ne O O O
batandika O O O
okuteesa O O O
. O O O

Okukuba O O O
akamyufu O O O
ku O O O
bassentebe O O O
bebyalo O O O
nemiruka O O O
kwa O O O
July B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
16 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, O O O
okunoonya O O O
akalulu O O O
kutandike O O O
nga O O O
July B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
20 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
olwo O O O
okulonda O O O
kubeewo O O O
nga O O O
July B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
20 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
omwaka I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
guno I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
. O O O

Isiko B-PER B-PER B-PER
yategeezezza O O O
nti O O O
ennamba O O O
ye O O O
yagiggya O O O
ku O O O
yintaneti O O O
. O O O

Ye O O O
kwe O O O
kwesowolayo O O O
nakuba O O O
ekitngole O O O
ekivunaanyizibwa O O O
ku O O O
mutindo O O O
mu O O O
mbuga O O O
zamateeka O O O
ngayagala O O O
bamuliyirire O O O
. O O O

Tarek B-PER B-PER B-PER
Eldakdoky I-PER I-PER I-PER
maneja O O O
mu O O O
kkampuni O O O
ya O O O
Arab B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Contructors I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
agamba O O O
nti O O O
bamalirizza O O O
byonna O O O
era O O O
baakuwaayo O O O
emirimu O O O
egyabakwasibwa O O O
mu O O O
August B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
2018 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
. O O O

Gamukama O O O
ategeezezza O O O
nti O O O
Makerere B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
erudde O O O
ngeyagala O O O
okwongeza O O O
ebisale O O O
bya O O O
bitundu O O O
15 O O O
ku O O O
100naye O O O
nga O O O
buli O O O
kiteeso O O O
bwe O O O
kiyisibwa O O O
kiwakanyizibwa O O O
abayizi O O O
nokwekalakaasa O O O
. O O O

Omulamuzi O O O
Nyadoi B-PER B-PER B-PER
era O O O
yamulagidde O O O
asasule O O O
emitwalo O O O
50 O O O
ezobuliwo O O O
ate O O O
abamweyimiridde O O O
ne O O O
balagirwa O O O
okusasula O O O
obukadde O O O
2 O O O
ezitali O O O
za O O O
buliwo O O O
era O O O
nagwo O O O
nagwongerayo O O O
okutuusa O O O
nga O O O
August B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
3 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
2018 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
okuwulirwa O O O
. O O O

Omusolo O O O
tegwakomye O O O
ku O O O
bakozesa O O O
WhatApp B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
, O O O
wabula O O O
nabakozesa O O O
Mobile O O O
Money O O O
okusindika O O O
ssente O O O
bakaaba O O O
kubanga O O O
ssente O O O
ezisalibwako O O O
ngoteeka O O O
ssente O O O
ku O O O
ssimu O O O
nokuggyayo O O O
zeeyongedde O O O
. O O O

Gavumenti O O O
okuleeta O O O
omusolo O O O
guno O O O
kyaddiridde O O O
Pulezidenti O O O
okuwa O O O
ekiragiro O O O
nti O O O
abantu O O O
basusse O O O
okuwolokosa O O O
nga O O O
beeyambisa O O O
emikutu O O O
egya O O O
Social O O O
media O O O
, O O O
noolwekyo O O O
kye O O O
kiseera O O O
okubabinika O O O
omusolo O O O
bakendeeza O O O
ku O O O
kwonoona O O O
ebiseera O O O
nga O O O
bali O O O
mu O O O
bitazimba O O O
. O O O

Ssente O O O
akakadde O O O
kamu O O O
bwakaggyako O O O
10 O O O
, O O O
000 O O O
eza O O O
URA B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
nagattako O O O
1 O O O
, O O O
800 O O O
aba O O O
Mobile O O O
ze O O O
batwala O O O
kiba O O O
kitegeeza O O O
nti O O O
ogenda O O O
kusaasaanya O O O
ssente O O O
28 O O O
, O O O
000 O O O
nga O O O
ssente O O O
zino O O O
ziba O O O
nnyingi O O O
nnyo O O O
eziyinza O O O
okuviirako O O O
okutta O O O
ekigendererwa O O O
kya O O O
mobile O O O
Money O O O
. O O O

Wilfred B-PER B-PER B-PER
Tweituk I-PER I-PER I-PER
eyatomerwa O O O
bbaasi O O O
ya O O O
kampuni O O O
ya O O O
Divine B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ku O O O
Lubaga B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Road I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
. O O O

Okulonda O O O
kwa O O O
August B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
15 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
omwaka I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
guno I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
. O O O

Obudikoni O O O
lyeddaala O O O
erisooka O O O
mu O O O
bwawule O O O
bwEklesia O O O
nga O O O
liddirirwa O O O
Obufaaza O O O
ngerisembayo O O O
mu O O O
kwawulibwa O O O
lya O O O
Bisopu O O O
olwo O O O
ebitiibwa O O O
ebirala O O O
ebiddako O O O
bubeera O O O
buvunaanyizibwa O O O
obukolebwa O O O
oyo O O O
abeera O O O
abuweereddwa O O O
. O O O

Lipoota O O O
zabasawo O O O
ziraga O O O
nti O O O
omugenzi O O O
yafa O O O
nga O O O
4th B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
September I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
2018 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, O O O
ateomulambo O O O
gwe O O O
ne O O O
gukomezebwawo O O O
mu O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
nga O O O
24th B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
September I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
2018 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, O O O
kyokka O O O
ebyembi O O O
ngensigo O O O
ze O O O
zombi O O O
tazirina O O O
. O O O

Oluvannyuma O O O
lwobutakkaanya O O O
obubaddewo O O O
mu O O O
byobufuzi O O O
mu O O O
ggwanga O O O
eryo O O O
wakati O O O
wa O O O
Pulezidenti O O O
Salva B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kiir I-PER I-PER I-PER
neyali O O O
omumyuka O O O
we O O O
, O O O
Riak B-PER B-PER B-PER
Machar I-PER I-PER I-PER
okumalibwawo O O O
Bannayuganda O O O
basuubirwa O O O
okweyongera O O O
okweyiwa O O O
e O O O
South B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Sudan I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
okukolerayo O O O
emirimu O O O
. O O O

Wabula O O O
ngomusango O O O
gwokusangibwa O O O
nemmundu O O O
ogwali O O O
gumussiddwaako O O O
gwamuggyibwako O O O
kkooti O O O
yamagye O O O
nga O O O
kati O O O
ye O O O
banne O O O
bwe O O O
baakwatibwa O O O
bavunaanibwa O O O
gwa O O O
kulya O O O
mu O O O
nsi O O O
lukwe O O O
. O O O

David B-PER B-PER B-PER
Muwanga I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Pulezidenti O O O
wa O O O
UNAA B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Causes I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
ngayogera O O O
. O O O

Mu O O O
mbeera O O O
endala O O O
poliisi O O O
namagye O O O
byeyambisibwa O O O
kutiisatiisa O O O
bantu O O O
butenyigira O O O
mu O O O
kulonda O O O
bantu O O O
gavumenti O O O
beba O O O
teyagala O O O
. O O O

Omubuulizi O O O
wenjiri O O O
Ssajjabbi B-PER B-PER B-PER
yategeezezza O O O
abagoberezi O O O
nti O O O
, O O O
enteekateeka O O O
zokukungubagira O O O
Ayinza B-PER B-PER B-PER
zaabadde O O O
zigenda O O O
kubategeezebwa O O O
oluvannyuma O O O
kyokka O O O
teyalambise O O O
oba O O O
omulambo O O O
gwakukomezebwawo O O O
mu O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
oba O O O
gwabadde O O O
gwa O O O
kuziikibwa O O O
mu O O O
limbo O O O
e O O O
. O O O

Era O O O
agamba O O O
nti O O O
abantu O O O
balina O O O
okuba O O O
neriiso O O O
eryogi O O O
okulaba O O O
abantu O O O
bano O O O
. O O O

Yagasseeko O O O
nti O O O
Kiggala B-PER B-PER B-PER
okumusalako O O O
ebigambo O O O
nokumwonoonera O O O
erinnya O O O
, O O O
amulinako O O O
obuzibu O O O
ngomuntu O O O
. O O O

Yalabudde O O O
nomusajja O O O
Alex B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ndyezekire I-PER I-PER I-PER
eyassa O O O
essimu O O O
ye O O O
ku O O O
yintaneeti O O O
ngayita O O O
abantu O O O
okubakolera O O O
ku O O O
nsonga O O O
zaabwe O O O
ezeekuusa O O O
ku O O O
mirimu O O O
gya O O O
Interpol B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
. O O O

Museveni B-PER B-PER B-PER
yawerekeddwako O O O
Minisita O O O
webyamasanyalaze O O O
Irene B-PER B-PER B-PER
Muloni I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
owebyobulambuzi O O O
Ephrahim B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kamuntu I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
owokusikiriza O O O
bannamakolero O O O
okutandika O O O
wano O O O
emirimu O O O
Evelyne B-PER B-PER B-PER
Anite I-PER I-PER I-PER
ne O O O
ambasada O O O
Nimishi B-PER B-PER B-PER
Madvani I-PER I-PER I-PER
. O O O

Asiimwe B-PER B-PER B-PER
bwava O O O
e O O O
Misiri B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
agenda O O O
kukyalako O O O
e O O O
Sweden B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
noluvannyuma O O O
ayolekere O O O
South B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Africa I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
ku O O O
ntandikwa B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
yomwaka I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ogujja I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
. O O O

Asiimwe B-PER B-PER B-PER
akyagenda O O O
mu O O O
maaso O O O
nokulambula O O O
amawanga O O O
agenjawulo O O O
ngagenda O O O
akunga O O O
Bannayuganda O O O
abaliyo O O O
okwegatta O O O
ku O O O
NRM B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
era O O O
ngazzaako O O O
Misiri B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Egypt I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
oluvannyuma O O O
lwokuva O O O
e O O O
Turkey B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

June B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
2016 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
Matthew B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kitandwe I-PER I-PER I-PER
muzannyi O O O
womupiira O O O
yafumitibwa O O O
ebiso O O O
bwe O O O
yali O O O
ayingira O O O
awaka O O O
mu O O O
London B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Mu O O O
basinze O O O
okwesunga O O O
olugendo O O O
ye O O O
Minah B-PER B-PER B-PER
Inzah I-PER I-PER I-PER
alabika O O O
ngagendayo O O O
omulundi O O O
ogusooka O O O
, O O O
King B-PER B-PER B-PER
Saha I-PER I-PER I-PER
gwakubiri O O O
ne O O O
David B-PER B-PER B-PER
Lutalo I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
Geo B-PER B-PER B-PER
Steady I-PER I-PER I-PER
naye O O O
agendayo O O O
gusooka O O O
wamu O O O
ne O O O
Sheebah B-PER B-PER B-PER
ate O O O
nga O O O
Juliana B-PER B-PER B-PER
abeerayo O O O
nnyo O O O
. O O O

Ensonda O O O
Ku O O O
poliisi B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ye I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Katwe I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
zategeezeza O O O
nti O O O
Nabisere B-PER B-PER B-PER
yakwatiddwa O O O
namala O O O
enaku B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
sattu I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
mu O O O
kaddukulu O O O
ka O O O
poliisi O O O
kyokka O O O
nateekwa O O O
Ku O O O
kakalu O O O
ka O O O
poliisi O O O
naye O O O
bagenze O O O
okufuna O O O
amawulire O O O
agamukwatako O O O
ngalinnye O O O
ennyonyi O O O
nafuluma O O O
eggwanga O O O
. O O O

Ffe O O O
tulwanyisa O O O
abo O O O
abaagala O O O
okutabangula O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Kimuli B-PER B-PER B-PER
bwe O O O
yategeezezza O O O
. O O O

Bino O O O
we O O O
bijjidde O O O
ngobugulumbo O O O
obuliwo O O O
bwa O O O
bahhanda O O O
za O O O
Ssemwanga B-PER B-PER B-PER
kutiisa O O O
kwasa O O O
byama O O O
bya O O O
Ssemwanga B-PER B-PER B-PER
eyali O O O
agobeddwa O O O
e O O O
South B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Afrika I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
nadda O O O
e O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
nakyusa O O O
amannya O O O
nafuna O O O
paasipooti O O O
mu O O O
mannya O O O
ga O O O
Ali B-PER B-PER B-PER
Ssenyomo I-PER I-PER I-PER
naddayo O O O
ngomuntu O O O
omulala O O O
era O O O
ngebyobugagga O O O
biri O O O
mu O O O
mannya O O O
ga O O O
Ssenyomo B-PER B-PER B-PER
, O O O
wabula O O O
abaana O O O
bamanyiddwa O O O
nga O O O
ba O O O
Ssemwanga B-PER B-PER B-PER
ekitegeeza O O O
nti O O O
omuntu O O O
yenna O O O
ayinza O O O
okuleeta O O O
obujulizi O O O
nti O O O
Ssenyomo B-PER B-PER B-PER
yafa O O O
tazadde O O O
ne O O O
yeesiba O O O
ku O O O
bintu O O O
bya O O O
Ssemwanga B-PER B-PER B-PER
abaana O O O
ne O O O
baviiramu O O O
awo O O O
. O O O

Asabye O O O
abo O O O
bonna O O O
abaweereddwa O O O
obuvunaanyizibwa O O O
okubutuukiriza O O O
era O O O
nabaagaliza O O O
okuweereza O O O
obulungi O O O
okulaba O O O
nga O O O
tebava O O O
ku O O O
mulamwa O O O
ogwokwegatta O O O
nokukulaakulana O O O
. O O O

Omwezi B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
oguwedde I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
Abafirika O O O
20 O O O
baakwatibwa O O O
olwokuyingira O O O
ne O O O
viza O O O
enkyamu O O O
mu O O O
ggwanga O O O
lino O O O
. O O O

Bayiga B-PER B-PER B-PER
alumiriza O O O
bba O O O
okusulanga O O O
mu O O O
bbaala O O O
ne O O O
loogi O O O
e O O O
London B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
awaka O O O
naddayo O O O
ngemmambya B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
esala I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
nga O O O
nolumu O O O
asanga O O O
lisiiti O O O
za O O O
wooteeri O O O
mwe O O O
yasuze O O O
nabakazi O O O
mu O O O
ngoye O O O
ze O O O
. O O O

Bishop O O O
Graham B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kings I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
eyakulembeddemu O O O
okusaba O O O
ngabuulira O O O
mu O O O
kkanisa O O O
. O O O

Rogers B-PER B-PER B-PER
Namanya I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
akulira O O O
poliisi B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ye I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Nakulabye I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
yategeezezza O O O
nti O O O
bagenda O O O
kumuggulako O O O
ogwobubbi O O O
. O O O

Yawabudde O O O
abavubuka O O O
be O O O
yasanze O O O
batendekebwa O O O
okutwalibwa O O O
e O O O
Dubai B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Oman B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
namawanga O O O
amalala O O O
abasukka O O O
100 O O O
, O O O
okusookanga O O O
okwetegereza O O O
bye O O O
babasuubiza O O O
okukola O O O
. O O O

Yayongeddeko O O O
nti O O O
Gavumenti O O O
egenda O O O
kukola O O O
kyonna O O O
ekisoboka O O O
okulondoola O O O
abakolera O O O
ebweru O O O
, O O O
okulaba O O O
nga O O O
bayisibwa O O O
bulungi O O O
, O O O
basasulibwa O O O
bulungi O O O
. O O O

Kiremerwa B-PER B-PER B-PER
yabakubirizzaokutumbula O O O
ebyobulambuzi O O O
bwa O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ebikyakula O O O
era O O O
nga O O O
byetaaga O O O
okukwatirako O O O
ennyo O O O
nga O O O
bayita O O O
mu O O O
kusendasenda O O O
mikwano O O O
gyabwe O O O
okujja O O O
okulaba O O O
ebyobulambuzi O O O
omuli O O O
ensolo O O O
nobutonde O O O
bwensi O O O
obulungi O O O
okuzaama O O O
bye O O O
bayinza O O O
nokusigamu O O O
ensimbi O O O
. O O O

Walusimbi B-PER B-PER B-PER
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
olukuhhana O O O
lugenda O O O
kubeera O O O
London B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
mu O O O
Bungereza B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ate O O O
Wakame B-PER B-PER B-PER
nategeeza O O O
nti O O O
beetegefu O O O
okuyambako O O O
okuteeka O O O
manifesito O O O
ya O O O
NRM B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
mu O O O
nkola O O O
. O O O

Mu O O O
ngeri O O O
yeemu O O O
Kimuli B-PER B-PER B-PER
eteekateeka O O O
ku O O O
sisinkana O O O
ba O O O
mmemba O O O
bekibiina O O O
mu O O O
kibuga O O O
Instambul B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
e O O O
Kya O O O
Turkey B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
nekigendererwa O O O
kyokugaziya O O O
nokunoonyeza O O O
ebyamaguzi O O O
bya O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
akatale O O O
mu O O O
nsi O O O
zebweru O O O
. O O O

Yabadde O O O
mu O O O
mikono O O O
gya O O O
poliisi O O O
nga O O O
tekkiriza O O O
bantu O O O
abagamba O O O
nti O O O
bamumanyi O O O
okubeera O O O
waali O O O
. O O O

Schwarzenegger B-PER B-PER B-PER
yagugumbudde O O O
Trump B-PER B-PER B-PER
nti O O O
Obwapulezidenti O O O
bumulemye O O O
, O O O
yandibadde O O O
asalawo O O O
naddayo O O O
mu O O O
katemba O O O
, O O O
ye O O O
Schwarzenegger B-PER B-PER B-PER
nakwatamu O O O
kubanga O O O
omukululo O O O
gwe O O O
yaleka O O O
e O O O
California B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
nga O O O
Gavana O O O
gweyogerera O O O
. O O O

Bannayuganda O O O
abaalabye O O O
obutambi O O O
bwa O O O
Ssemwanga B-PER B-PER B-PER
ngagaba O O O
ssente O O O
abamu O O O
baamulumbye O O O
ate O O O
abalala O O O
ne O O O
bamusaba O O O
okukola O O O
ekintu O O O
kye O O O
kimu O O O
ne O O O
mu O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
kubanga O O O
we O O O
wasinga O O O
abantu O O O
abali O O O
mu O O O
bwetaavu O O O
mu O O O
kifo O O O
kyokuzimalira O O O
mu O O O
mabbaala O O O
buli O O O
lwajja O O O
. O O O

Omulambo O O O
gwa O O O
Walusimbi B-PER B-PER B-PER
gusuubirwa O O O
okukomezebwawo O O O
wiiki B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
ejja I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
oluvannyuma O O O
lwokukola O O O
ku O O O
mitendera O O O
egyetaagisa O O O
. O O O

Omukolo O O O
guno O O O
gwasombodde O O O
Bannayuganda O O O
okuva O O O
mu O O O
masaza O O O
gaWestern B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Cape I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
, O O O
Eastern B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Cape I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
, O O O
Free B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
State I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
, O O O
Durban B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Gauteng B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
namalala O O O
. O O O

Mu O O O
South B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Afrika I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
amazeeyo O O O
emyaka B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
mukaaga I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ngakolagana O O O
nabamu O O O
ku O O O
bayimbi O O O
abaatendekebwako O O O
omugenzi O O O
Lucky B-PER B-PER B-PER
Dube I-PER I-PER I-PER
ne O O O
Yvonne B-PER B-PER B-PER
Chaka I-PER I-PER I-PER
Chaka I-PER I-PER I-PER
. O O O

Yalondeddwa O O O
nokuvuganya O O O
mu O O O
mpaka O O O
ze O O O
Bungereza B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
eza O O O
Befta O O O
Awards O O O
. O O O

Aba O O O
kkampuni O O O
baasuubizza O O O
nti O O O
wiiki B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
eno I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
weneggweerako O O O
omulambo O O O
gwa O O O
Mudambo B-PER B-PER B-PER
gujja O O O
kuba O O O
gutuuse O O O
nasaba O O O
abafamire O O O
okubeera O O O
abagumiikiriza O O O
. O O O

Ekivvulu O O O
kinokyategekeddwaokuyamba O O O
nokugattaBannayuganda O O O
ababeera O O O
e O O O
Bungereza B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
okusomesaabaana O O O
abatoobuwangwa O O O
nennono O O O
zaabwe O O O
. O O O

Olukuaana O O O
lwa O O O
Ugandan B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
North I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
American I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Association I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
UNAA I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
luggulwawo O O O
ku O O O
Lwamukaaga B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
luno I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
nga I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
September02016 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
mu O O O
kibuga O O O
Boston B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Yagambye O O O
nti O O O
kati O O O
yeewogomye O O O
wa O O O
mukwano O O O
gwe O O O
kubanga O O O
ewuwe O O O
atyayo O O O
kuba O O O
omusajja O O O
ayinza O O O
okujja O O O
namutta O O O
kubanga O O O
ebigendererwa O O O
bye O O O
bya O O O
kukakasa O O O
nti O O O
Nakacwa B-PER B-PER B-PER
afa O O O
era O O O
essaawa O O O
yonna O O O
ayagala O O O
kukituukiriza O O O
. O O O

Amuriat B-PER B-PER B-PER
ategeezezza O O O
nti O O O
enkyukakyuka O O O
zonna O O O
zitandikiddewo O O O
okukola O O O
. O O O
Wammanga O O O
zenkyukakyuka O O O
. O O O

Ssengoba B-PER B-PER B-PER
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
ddigi O O O
Mbuga B-PER B-PER B-PER
kwe O O O
yabadde O O O
yayonoonese O O O
nnyo O O O
era O O O
baagisitudde O O O
ne O O O
bagiteeka O O O
mu O O O
kikomera O O O
kyamaka O O O
ga O O O
Mbuga B-PER B-PER B-PER
e O O O
Kkonge B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Buziga I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
mu O O O
Kampala B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Nakaweesi B-PER B-PER B-PER
yasabye O O O
poliisi O O O
enoonyereze O O O
aleme O O O
kubeera O O O
mu O O O
kunyolwa O O O
okwemirundi O O O
ebiri O O O
. O O O

Abamu O O O
babadde O O O
basomesa O O O
mu O O O
masomero O O O
ge O O O
nabakozi O O O
be O O O
nga O O O
Diana B-PER B-PER B-PER
Nyanzi I-PER I-PER I-PER
owa O O O
Horizon B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Campus I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
. O O O

Kagina B-PER B-PER B-PER
yawadde O O O
amagezi O O O
nti O O O
gavumenti O O B-ORG
ya O O I-ORG
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC I-ORG
ekoppe O O O
enkola O O O
egobererwa O O O
mu O O O
mawanga O O O
amalala O O O
nga O O O
baliyirira O O O
abantu O O O
nga O O O
bwe O O O
kiri O O O
mu O O O
Buyindi B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Bwe O O O
baalaba O O O
nga O O O
bafunye O O O
obujjulizi O O O
obumala O O O
kwe O O O
kumukwata O O O
ngomusango O O O
guli O O O
ku O O O
fayiri O O O
nnamba O O O
SD O O O
. O O O

Wabula O O O
bazudde O O O
nti O O O
ate O O O
ennamba O O O
zino O O O
tezaawandiisibwa O O O
era O O O
mu O O O
kiseera B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
kino I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
teziriiko O O O
. O O O

Mu O O O
kiseera O O O
kye O O O
kimu O O O
mbega O O O
eyeekozesa O O O
yekka O O O
Freddie B-PER B-PER B-PER
Egesa I-PER I-PER I-PER
agambye O O O
nti O O O
ssinga O O O
yabadde O O O
anoonyereza O O O
ku O O O
nfa O O O
ya O O O
Kaweesi B-PER B-PER B-PER
yanditunuulidde O O O
ebintu O O O
bino O O O
. O O O

Baabano O O O
abajaasi O O O
50 O O O
abaasooka O O O
okwesogga O O O
ensiko O O O
. O O O

Abamu O O O
ku O O O
bantu O O O
54 O O O
abagambibwa O O O
okwegabanya O O O
ssente O O O
obuwumbi O O O
omukaaga O O O
ye O O O
. O O O

Wennundira O O O
nomuddo O O O
gugenze O O O
gukendeera O O O
gwe O O O
tuliisa O O O
ebisolo O O O
. O O O
ate O O O
nga O O O
ente O O O
nnunda O O O
za O O O
mu O O O
kiyumba O O O
wabula O O O
ewasinga O O O
okuva O O O
omuddo O O O
abantu O O O
baazimbawo O O O
dda O O O
. O O O

Musubi B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Farm I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Abagiddukanya O O O
bagenda O O O
kusomesa O O O
abalimi O O O
ennima O O O
ya O O O
ovakedo O O O
, O O O
enkungula O O O
nengeri O O O
yokufunamu O O O
ssente O O O
ku O O O
Ssande B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
okutandika I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ku I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ssaawa I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
800 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
1000 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ezolweggulo I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
. O O O

Mbakuutira O O O
okukolagana O O O
obulungi O O O
mutambuze O O O
emirimi O O O
gyeggombolola O O O
, O O O
nnina O O O
obweraliikirivu O O O
nti O O O
ekyokweyawula O O O
kyandizaala O O O
ebizibu O O O
mu O O O
ggombola O O O
eno O O O
abamu O O O
ne O O O
muwunzika O O O
ngobwami O O O
bubafudde O O O
, O O O
mubeere O O O
bumu O O O
musobole O O O
okubeera O O O
ekyokulabirako O O O
eri O O O
Bannabukunja O O O
, O O O
Bogere B-PER B-PER B-PER
bwe O O O
yagambye O O O
. O O O

Okugeza O O O
amatooke O O O
tutwala O O O
bika O O O
binnansi O O O
okusingira O O O
ddala O O O
Musakala O O O
kuba O O O
ono O O O
abeera O O O
neminwe O O O
eminene O O O
ate O O O
ngawangaala O O O
nga O O O
tannayonooneka O O O
naddala O O O
nga O O O
tumutwala O O O
mu O O O
Bulaaya B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Matovu B-PER B-PER B-PER
bwagamba O O O
. O O O

Yeebazizza O O O
ekitongole O O O
kya O O O
MUZARDI B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ne O O O
kkampuni O O O
ya O O O
Engineering B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Solution I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
abayambye O O O
ku O O O
NAADS B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
okubangula O O O
abavuzi O O O
ba O O O
tulakita O O O
bano O O O
nategeeza O O O
nti O O O
, O O O
gavumenti O O O
nayo O O O
eyanguyirwa O O O
emirimu O O O
bwefuna O O O
abagikwatirako O O O
ku O O O
mirimu O O O
gyayo O O O
egyokutumbula O O O
ebyobulimi O O O
mu O O O
ggwanga O O O
. O O O

Agamba O O O
nti O O O
, O O O
okutondebwawo O O O
kwenkola O O O
eno O O O
awankuhhaanira O O O
abakugu O O O
abenjawulo O O O
, O O O
kyakuyamba O O O
okuwa O O O
abalimi O O O
obukugu O O O
bwe O O O
beetaaga O O O
okulaba O O O
ngomulimu O O O
gwabwe O O O
bagukola O O O
mu O O O
ngeri O O O
yekikugu O O O
. O O O

Kino O O O
kikuyamba O O O
obutatawaanyizibwa O O O
ngotandise O O O
okulunda O O O
. O O O

Ssaabasajja O O O
Kabaka O O O
Ronald B-PER B-PER B-PER
Muwenda I-PER I-PER I-PER
Mutebi I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
ngayita O O O
mu O O O
kitongole O O O
kye O O O
ekya O O O
Gavumenti O O O
ezebitundu O O O
yateekawo O O O
enkola O O O
eyokugabira O O O
amasaza O O O
neggombolola O O O
ezisinze O O O
zinnaazo O O O
okukolaebirabo O O O
ate O O O
nomuvubuka O O O
asinze O O O
banne O O O
okwerwanako O O O
mu O O O
bulimi O O O
ngenkola O O O
eno O O O
eyongedde O O O
okukubiriza O O O
amasaza O O O
okwerwanako O O O
. O O O

Yakyukidde O O O
aboogezi O O O
boku O O O
mikolo O O O
be O O O
yayise O O O
ababaka O O O
ba O O O
Buganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
nabakubiriza O O O
okunnyikiza O O O
empagi O O O
za O O O
Buganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
kwerina O O O
okutambulira O O O
nga O O O
balungamya O O O
abantu O O O
ku O O O
mpisa O O O
zaabwe O O O
. O O O

Immaculate B-PER B-PER B-PER
Daisy I-PER I-PER I-PER
omukungu O O O
okuva O O O
mu O O O
kitongole O O O
kya O O O
Hivos B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
yagambye O O O
nti O O O
, O O O
Hivos B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
ejja O O O
kukolaganira O O O
wamu O O O
ne O O O
Gavumenti O O O
okutumbula O O O
obulimi O O O
bwemmere O O O
ennansi O O O
mu O O O
bitundu O O O
byeggwanga O O O
ebitali O O O
bimu O O O
nannyonnyola O O O
nti O O O
emmere O O O
eno O O O
emanyiddwa O O O
mu O O O
nsi O O O
yonna O O O
nti O O O
yaamugaso O O O
eri O O O
obulamu O O O
bwabantu O O O
nebisolo O O O
. O O O

Yasuubizza O O O
nti O O O
amangu O O O
nga O O O
bamaze O O O
okufuna O O O
ensimbi O O O
ze O O O
beetaaga O O O
bajja O O O
kutongoza O O O
ennima O O O
eno O O O
. O O O

Ssinga O O O
tuzitunda O O O
ku O O O
1 O O O
, O O O
200 O O O
buli O O O
liita O O O
kitegeeza O O O
tubeera O O O
tufuna O O O
144 O O O
, O O O
000 O O O
olunaku B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
olwo I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
omwezi I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ne O O O
tufuna O O O
4 O O O
, O O O
320 O O O
, O O O
000 O O O
, O O O
Kzibwe B-PER B-PER B-PER
bwagamba O O O
. O O O

Bano O O O
bagamba O O O
nti O O O
boogerezeganya O O O
nabakulembeze O O O
okulaba O O O
nga O O O
batambulira O O O
wamu O O O
mu O O O
kusomesa O O O
abantu O O O
nokulaba O O O
nga O O O
beegatta O O O
ku O O O
kibiina O O O
beeyongera O O O
. O O O

Twatondawo O O O
ekibiina O O O
kyabalimi O O O
bentangawuuzi O O O
mu O O O
Nsanja B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
nekigendererwa O O O
kino O O O
era O O O
nsaba O O O
Pulezidenti O O O
Museveni B-PER B-PER B-PER
atuyambeko O O O
ku O O O
nsonga O O O
eno O O O
tufune O O O
ekyuma O O O
emirimu O O O
emirala O O O
mingi O O O
gijja O O O
okutondebwawo O O O
ate O O O
ne O O O
ssente O O O
okweyongera O O O
okujja O O O
mu O O O
kitundu O O O
kino O O O
. O O O

Mu O O O
ngeri O O O
yemu O O O
asabye O O O
gavumenti O O O
nebitongole O O O
ebikola O O O
ku O O O
kunoonyereza O O O
okwongera O O O
okunoonyereza O O O
ku O O O
butonde O O O
bwente O O O
ekika O O O
kya O O O
Ankole O O O
, O O O
zagamba O O O
nti O O O
ze O O O
zisinga O O O
nga O O O
zeetaaga O O O
kwongera O O O
kunoonyerezebwako O O O
zive O O O
ku O O O
liita O O O
essatu O O O
okutuuka O O O
mu O O O
liita O O O
kkumi O O O
nokusoba O O O
kuba O O O
zikisobola O O O
. O O O

Okwewandiisa O O O
weereza O O O
erinnya O O O
lyo O O O
ku O O O
jkato O O O
@ O O O
newvision O O O
. O O O
co O O O
. O O O
ug O O O
oba O O O
weereza O O O
obubaka O O O
bwa O O O
ssimu O O O
ku O O O
0789353585 O O O
/ O O O
0712841688 O O O
oba O O O
whatsApp B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
+ O O O
256789353585 O O O
. O O O
. O O O
Okwewandiisa O O O
weereza O O O
erinnya O O O
lyo O O O
ku O O O
jkato O O O
newvision O O O
. O O O
co O O O
. O O O
ug O O O
oba O O O
weereza O O O
obubaka O O O
bwa O O O
ssimu O O O
ku O O O
07893535850712841688 O O O
oba O O O
whatsApp B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
256789353585 O O O
. O O O

Ebyuuma O O O
byokugattako O O O
omutindo O O O
nabyo O O O
bya O O O
buseere O O O
kuba O O O
njagala O O O
okutandika O O O
okugattako O O O
omutindo O O O
wabula O O O
ebyuuma O O O
biseerebwa O O O
. O O O

Mu O O O
ngeri O O O
yemu O O O
gavumenti O O O
yeddizza O O O
obuvunaanyizibwa O O O
bwokugula O O O
eddagala O O O
lino O O O
okuva O O O
mu O O O
balikola O O O
nokulituusa O O O
ku O O O
balunzi O O O
era O O O
ngabaaweebwa O O O
eryebiccupuli O O O
beebagenda O O O
okusokkerwako O O O
. O O O

Oluvannyuma O O O
lwettaka O O O
okunnyikira O O O
oba O O O
asobola O O O
okusimba O O O
enva O O O
zo O O O
endiirwa O O O
era O O O
mu O O O
bbanga O O O
eritali O O O
ddene O O O
oba O O O
ogenda O O O
kutandika O O O
okwenogera O O O
ensimbi O O O
ate O O O
ngabantu O O O
bo O O O
bwe O O O
balya O O O
kasita O O O
ogoberera O O O
obulungi O O O
emitendera O O O
egyo O O O
. O O O

Enteekateeka O O O
zomumaaso O O O
Matovu B-PER B-PER B-PER
alina O O O
enteekateeka O O O
yokwongera O O O
amaanyi O O O
mu O O O
mmwaanyi O O O
okulaba O O O
ngafuuka O O O
omulimi O O O
owokulabirako O O O
eri O O O
abalala O O O
bonna O O O
mu O O O
kitundu O O O
kino O O O
, O O O
okulaba O O O
ngakyusa O O O
endowooza O O O
zabalimi O O O
mu O O O
kitundu O O O
mu O O O
kulima O O O
emmwaanyi O O O
. O O O

Robert B-PER B-PER B-PER
Migadde I-PER I-PER I-PER
Ndugwa I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
yabasuubizza O O O
okutuusa O O O
ensonga O O O
zaabwe O O O
eri O O O
minisita O O O
azivunaanyizibwako O O O
ne O O O
mu O O O
Palamenti O O O
ziteesebweko O O O
naddala O O O
ku O O O
kyokukendeeza O O O
ku O O O
muwendo O O O
gwensimbi O O O
ogwebintu O O O
bye O O O
bakozesa O O O
okuvuba O O O
okuli O O O
obutimba O O O
, O O O
amaato O O O
nebirala O O O
nga O O O
bino O O O
bye O O O
bivuddeko O O O
okugula O O O
obutimba O O O
obwa O O O
layisi O O O
obubalemezza O O O
mu O O O
nvuba O O O
embi O O O
. O O O

Kati O O O
obulwadde O O O
obulala O O O
obulabika O O O
ngobunafu O O O
bwe O O O
bwo O O O
bwosobola O O O
okugoba O O O
ngokozesa O O O
eddagala O O O
erifuuyirwa O O O
. O O O

Mu O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ekibiina O O O
kino O O O
kyanokoddeyo O O O
ekitundu O O O
kye O O O
Karamoja B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ngekimu O O O
ku O O O
ebyo O O O
ebigenda O O O
okukosebwa O O O
enjala O O O
. O O O
Omwezi B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
oguwedde I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
ekibiina O O O
ekitaba O O O
bannamawulire O O O
abasaka O O O
agembeera O O O
yobudde O O O
ekya O O O
Network B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Climate I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Journalists I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
the I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Greater I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Horn I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Africa I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
NECJOGHA I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
kyawandiika O O O
nti O O O
abenteebereza O O O
yobudde O O O
mu O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Kenya B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ne O O O
Tanzania B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
baali O O O
bannyonnyodde O O O
nti O O O
ekivudde O O O
enkuba O O O
okulwawo O O O
okutonnya O O O
gwe O O O
muyaga O O O
ogwayita O O O
mu O O O
bitundu O O O
bya O O O
Mozambique B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ne O O O
gunywa O O O
empewo O O O
ezandibadde O O O
zireeta O O O
enkuba O O O
nga O O O
ziva O O O
mu O O O
liyanja O O O
lya O O O
Buyindi B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O
Bulijjo O O O
okuva B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
mu I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
mwezi I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
gwa I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
March I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
okutuuka I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
nga I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
June I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
gutandika I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
bibeera O O O
biseera B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
bya I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
nkuba I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
eyomwero O O O
mu O O O
mawanga O O O
nga O O O
Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
kyokka O O O
kumpi O O O
omwezi B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
gwa I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
March I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
gwonna I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
gwaweddeko O O O
nga O O O
teri O O O
nkuba O O O
etonnye O O O
ate O O O
ne O O O
April B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
mwe O O O
yabadde O O O
esuubira O O O
mu O O O
bitundu O O O
ebimu O O O
yalumaggamagga O O O
. O O O
Ate O O O
ku O O O
Lwokubiri B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
lwa I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
wiiki I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
eno I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
lipoota O O O
eyawamu O O O
eyafulumiziddwa O O O
omukago O O O
gwa O O O
Bulaaya B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
wamu O O O
nebitongole O O O
byEkibiina B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
kyAmawanga I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Amagatte I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
bibiri O O O
ebivunaanyizibwa O O O
ku O O O
byemmere O O O
okuli O O O
ekya O O O
Food B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
and I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Agriculture I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Organization I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
FAO I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
, O O O
ne O O O
World B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Food I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Programme I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
WFP I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
yalaze O O O
nti O O O
amawanga O O O
53 O O O
mu O O O
nsi O O O
yonna O O O
ge O O O
goolekedde O O O
okugwamu O O O
enjala O O O
nga O O O
ku O O O
gano O O O
kuliko O O O
aga O O O
Africa B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
ataano O O O
okuli O O O
Democratic B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Republic I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
of I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
the I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
Congo I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
, O O O
Ethiopia B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
Nigeria B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
South B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
Sudan I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC
ne O O O
Sudan B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Olina O O O
okutegeka O O O
byonoobikkisa O O O
ngessanja O O O
lye O O O
lisinga O O O
okukola O O O
obulungi O O O
naye O O O
bwoba O O O
tolirina O O O
ofuna O O O
essubi O O O
nalyo O O O
likola O O O
. O O O

Tusuubira O O O
nti O O O
enkuba O O O
yakutonnya O O O
okutuusa O O O
mu O O O
makkati B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
ga I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
June I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, O O O
Bataze B-PER B-PER B-PER
bwagamba O O O
. O O O

Kabushenga B-PER B-PER B-PER
yategeezezza O O O
nti O O O
omwoleso O O O
gwomwaka B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
ogujja I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
2020 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
gwakubeerawo O O O
nga O O O
February B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
14 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
16 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
, I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
2020 I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
era O O O
ngenteekateeka O O O
egenda O O O
kwongera O O O
okubeera O O O
eyomulembe O O O
. O O O

Abavubi O O O
bali O O O
mu O O O
kutya O O O
nti O O O
, O O O
tekinologiya O O O
wa O O O
GMO O O O
ono O O O
ayinza O O O
okutta O O O
ebyennyanja O O O
nebitonde O O O
ebirala O O O
bingi O O O
mu O O O
nnyanja O O O
ebyomugaso O O O
ne O O O
bafiirwa O O O
emirimu O O O
, O O O
obutonde O O O
bwennyanja O O O
nobuwangwa O O O
, O O O
kuba O O O
bangi O O O
ku O O O
bo O O O
balina O O O
emizizo O O O
egyekuusa O O O
ku O O O
nnyanja O O O
ngebika O O O
ebimu O O O
ebiva O O O
mu O O O
nnyanja O O O
. O O O

Ebisigala O O O
nga O O O
butto O O O
amaze O O O
okukamulibwa O O O
era O O O
bisobola O O O
okukola O O O
ngebigimusa O O O
mu O O O
nnimiro O O O
nga O O O
na O O O
bino O O O
osobola O O O
okubitunda O O O
nofunamu O O O
ssente O O O
oba O O O
okubikozesa O O O
mu O O O
nnimiro O O O
yo O O O
. O O O

Basabye O O O
gavumenti O O O
okwongera O O O
ssente O O O
mu O O O
kitongole B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
kyabasawo I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
bebisolo I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
kuba O O O
okujjanjaba O O O
ebisolo O O O
okutuufu O O O
kitangira O O O
endwadde O O O
nnyingi O O O
ezandibadde O O O
zisiigibwa O O O
mu O O O
bantu O O O
okuva O O O
ku O O O
ebisolo O O O
nga O O O
bulusera O O O
, O O O
akafuba O O O
, O O O
kkookolo O O O
nendala O O O
. O O O

Enkota O O O
328 O O O
buli O O O
emu O O O
bwogitunda O O O
ku O O O
20 O O O
, O O O
000 O O O
ofuna O O O
6 O O O
, O O O
560 O O O
, O O O
000 O O O
. O O O

Wabula O O O
nsuubira O O O
okuddayo O O O
omwaka B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
guno I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
era O O O
kyekimu O O O
ku O O O
bye O O O
nnina O O O
okussaako O O O
omutima O O O
okulaba O O O
nga O O O
naffe O O O
tusobola O O O
okussa O O O
amata O O O
gaffe O O O
mu O O O
mikebe O O O
. O O O

Engeri O O O
gye O O O
weeteekateeka O O O
okulima O O O
ennyaanya O O O
ku O O O
musana O O O
nga O O O
. O O O

Yategeezezza O O O
nti O O O
, O O O
mu O O O
kiseera B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
kino I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
nga O O O
bali O O O
mu O O O
byobulimi O O O
nobulunzi O O O
, O O O
balina O O O
nenteekateeka O O O
egenda O O O
okutandika O O O
eyokuweerera O O O
abaana O O O
ku O O O
bwereere O O O
okuva O O O
mu O O O
pulayimare O O O
okutuuka O O O
ku O O O
yunivasite O O O
. O O O

Ekiri O O O
mu O O O
mwoleso O O O
gwa O O O
Harvest O O O
Money O O O
Expo O O O
olunaku B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
olwokubiri I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
Guli O O O
mu O O O
kisaawe O O O
e O O O
Namboole B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
. O O O

Ennyaanya O O O
ze O O O
nobutungulu O O O
bwanaabikungula O O O
bazadde O O O
be O O O
tebaggya O O O
kuddamu O O O
kugula O O O
nnyaanya O O O
na O O O
butungulu O O O
anti O O O
bajja O O O
kuba O O O
babiggya O O O
mu O O O
nnimiro O O O
. O O O

Bonna O O O
abanajja O O O
mu O O O
mwoleso O O O
baakumanyisibwa O O O
ku O O O
mpeereza O O O
zaffe O O O
zonna O O O
. O O O

Abalala O O O
abaabaddewo O O O
, O O O
ye O O O
Toyota B-PER B-PER B-PER
Nzaire I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
muto O O O
wa O O O
Pulezidenti O O O
Museveni B-PER B-PER B-PER
, O O O
ssentebe O O O
wa O O O
NCS B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
, O O O
akulira O O O
UBF B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
, O O O
Moses B-PER B-PER B-PER
Muhangi I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
nomubaka O O O
wa O O O
UN B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
mu O O O
ggwanga O O O
Rosa B-PER B-PER B-PER
Malago I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
akulira O O O
ekitongole O O O
kya O O O
sirimu O O O
ekya O O O
UNAIDS B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
, O O O
Dr O O O
. O O O
Kalusa B-PER B-PER B-PER
Kiragu I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
omukungu O O O
wa O O O
Pepsi B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
, O O O
Amos B-PER B-PER B-PER
Nzeyi I-PER I-PER I-PER
, O O O
omuyimbi O O O
Bebe B-PER B-PER B-PER
Cool I-PER I-PER I-PER
nabalala O O O
. O O O

Okuyingira O O O
mu O O O
mwoleso O O O
kwa O O O
kusasulira O O O
10 O O O
, O O O
000 O O O
ate O O O
okwetaba O O O
mu O O O
misomo O O O
nakwo O O O
kwa O O O
10 O O O
, O O O
000 O O O
nga O O O
wateekeddwateekeddwawo O O O
emisomo O O O
egyenjawulo O O O
. O O O

Abalimi O O O
ssekinnoomu O O O
nabeegattira O O O
mu O O O
bibiina O O O
ebyenjawulo O O O
beetabye O O O
mu O O O
lukuhhaana O O O
luno O O O
nomulanga O O O
eri O O O
gavumenti O O O
okubayamba O O O
okussaawo O O O
enkola O O O
ezisobozesa O O O
okukuuma O O O
nokutumbula O O O
emmere O O O
ennansi O O O
. O O O

Asabye O O O
Muhoozi B-PER B-PER B-PER
okutuusa O O O
eri O O O
be O O O
kikwatako O O O
okukaaba O O O
kwabalimi O O O
nabalunzi O O O
olwebikozesebwa O O O
byebicupuli O O O
ebikyalemedde O O O
ku O O O
katale O O O
omuli O O O
eddagala O O O
, O O O
ensigo O O O
nebirala O O O
ebifiiriza O O O
abalimi O O O
nabalunzi O O O
. O O O

Ssentebe O O O
wa O O O
disitulikiti O O O
Benon B-PER B-PER B-PER
Mugabi I-PER I-PER I-PER
yawabudde O O O
nti O O O
nabalina O O O
ensuku O O O
nabo O O O
bayambibwe O O O
. O O O

Nasobola O O O
okumaliriza O O O
enju O O O
yange O O O
gye O O O
nali O O O
ntandiseeko O O O
nokugulayo O O O
emmotoka O O O
, O O O
ate O O O
nkyalina O O O
bingi O O O
bye O O O
nkolako O O O
. O O O

Kino O O O
omulunzi O O O
alina O O O
okukyettanira O O O
amanye O O O
oba O O O
byakola O O O
bitambula O O O
bulungi O O O
oba O O O
nedda O O O
. O O O

Ffaamu O O O
enteekako O O O
obwetaavu O O O
bwokwongera O O O
okugaziya O O O
obwongo O O O
nga O O O
nsoma O O O
ebintu O O O
ebitali O O O
bimu O O O
naddala O O O
ku O O O
yintaneeti O O O
kubanga O O O
kubaako O O O
ebintu O O O
bingi O O O
. O O O

Amatooke O O O
gannyambye O O O
kuba O O O
sikyayinza O O O
kubulwa O O O
20 O O O
, O O O
000 O O O
ate O O O
nge O O O
nemmere O O O
ndya O O O
. O O O

Tulina O O O
ekibiina O O O
kyabalimi O O O
bentula O O O
era O O O
nze O O O
omuyima O O O
waakyo O O O
nga O O O
kirimu O O O
. O O O

Uganda B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
omwaka B-DATE B-DATE B-DATE
guno I-DATE I-DATE I-DATE
yayolesezza O O O
amenvu O O O
omuli O O O
bogoya O O O
, O O O
ndiizi O O O
, O O O
omubisi O O O
gwenjuki O O O
, O O O
ennaanansi O O O
, O O O
omwenge O O O
oguva O O O
mu O O O
kayinja O O O
we O O O
Bugerere B-LOC B-LOC B-LOC
, O O O
ebigaaga O O O
, O O O
ebinyeebwa O O O
, O O O
kyetutumula O O O
, O O O
balugu O O O
, O O O
ebyennyanja O O O
nebintu O O O
ebiruke O O O
nemikono O O O
. O O O

Twagala O O O
okwongera O O O
okugaziya O O O
ekibiina O O O
kyaffe O O O
era O O O
nga O O O
twakikozeemu O O O
ekibiina O O O
kyobwegassi O O O
ekya O O O
Nile B-ORG B-ORG B-ORG
Goat I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
Cooperation I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG
omuli O O O
ba O O O
memba O O O
37 O O O
nga O O O
muno O O O
tuyitamu O O O
okuwahhana O O O
amagezi O O O
nokweyigiriza O O O
ebintu O O O
ebitali O O O
bimu O O O
. O O O
